<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Azarinth Healer</title><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 465 Moving Pieces</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/503348</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 465 Moving Pieces&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea returned the two enchanters to the Sentinel headquarters, leaving them in two unoccupied rooms to not wake them up. &lt;em&gt;Unconsciousness might just be the only way to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;make them get some sleep &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;at this point. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Workaholics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She herself hadn't slept much either lately but there was just so much to do. &lt;em&gt;I'm one of them too, am I not?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wondered if she could do the same without her Mental Resistance, eating a few bites of food as she rushed to the arena. She was a little late but the pay made most of the adventurers stay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the Shadows were present still.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Welcome everyone. Let's get back to it, shall we," Ilea said as she appeared before them, a smile on her face as an ashen mist formed around her. &lt;em&gt;Give me your magic, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;my minions!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The training passed without major incidents, quite a few of her resistances leveling in the process. She spent her time healing herself and thinking about the past night. The Basilisk made it clear that she might just not be ready yet to kill a level one thousand being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor did it seem morally acceptable to her. The Sand Elemental, maybe. The Ascended, definitely. The Basilisk and Trakorov on the other hand seemed to her like somewhat intelligent animals, nor mindless monsters that attacked with abandon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If she killed the creature, it would feel like killing Bambi's mom. She had become rather ruthless but Ilea hadn't joined the dark side entirely. At the very least she thought that was the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She proceeded with lunch at the Sentinel headquarters, surprising some of the students eating nearby. Some even joined her but remained quiet, reading her mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So no four mark achievement for the third class… if they're all as powerful as the ones I've met so far. And the way levels are calculated for monsters, it would seem they all should be. Which means I could get my third class soon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She checked her advancements from the morning session, tapping her cheek as she shoveled food into her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Oxygen Repository reaches lvl 5'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Arcane Magic Resistance reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 13'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Crystal Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 6'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Dark Magic Resistance reaches lvl 20'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Dark Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 1'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dark Magic Resistance – 2nd lvl 1&lt;br/&gt;You have stood against a being of true darkness. Its magic was not able to pierce your defenses and you stand to tell the tale. This skill will help you repeat such actions.&lt;br/&gt;Your body is attuned to the effects of the dark. You may traverse areas imbued by it without harm, nor will all creatures that dwell within see you as something not part of their domain.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Earth Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 8'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Earth Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 9'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Mist Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 13'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Mist Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 14'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Poison Resistance reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 2'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Smoke Magic Resistance reaches lvl 4'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Smoke Magic Resistance reaches lvl 7'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sound Magic Resistance reaches lvl 9'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Sound Magic Resistance reaches lvl 11'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Void Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 14'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Water Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 9'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another set of levels. Not enough for another third tier point nor perhaps an achievement. Every resistance in the second tier would add to the potential density of her ash, in this case most certainly the most impacting change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I wonder if the element is inherently magical, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought and swirled around a little bit of ash, to the surprise and terror of the nearby students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A marble formed, reflecting little light as its form turned smooth, more ash added to it as its size remained the same. The added weight did not impact her ability to move it. &lt;em&gt;Could I reach a point where its structure changes? What would ash become? Charcoal? Diamond? I wish there was a chemistry professor in these lands… on the other hand, they might just go insane because everything they learned didn't make any sense around here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wondered if the marbles she created could theoretically reach a density where they had a graspable pull on their surrounding. &lt;em&gt;A long way off for that, &lt;/em&gt;she thought. The sheer weight of a projectile like that would make for a wonderful impact, more so than a benefit like gravity would have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You seem lost," Trian said as he joined the table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Things to consider… plus I might have started something stupid in Riverwatch," she said with a sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The request for help?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes… slavers coming to reclaim their taken, property," she said, saying the last word with disdain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You took them down?" Trian said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Killed those that attacked. The rest fled," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should have killed them all," the man replied, continuing to eat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The result would be the same. Now at least some people might rethink their choices," she retorted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They will know who did it. And they will respond in kind. It's difficult to change someone's beliefs, if they have been taught that they are true for the duration of their whole life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She shrugged. "That's a good thing. They might look for me instead of focusing on Riverwatch," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But it was them who called for you. All they know is that a Shadow came and slaughtered their people," Trian said. "The nobles of Baralia are… more individualistic. They rarely consider their king or country when making decisions. Do you know who sent them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Harken," she replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm, I know little of him. Lord Rowan Harken. I believe he is known to be strict but fair, a man of principle, though you and me may not agree with his views on things. His lands may not be the worst to live in as a slave, compared to some of the others," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That doesn't change the fact that he holds people, as property," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"True. You understand however, that many believe slavery to be beneficial. I know of a few families in Lys that would gladly introduce the concept again in the empire," Trian said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Again?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh yes, that was centuries past however. The economic stability without slavery present shows that it isn't necessary. Let alone the misery, death and pain it brought. You could argue that some of the training facilities the nobles manage are borderline slavery but most ignore them. A few children are not enough to antagonize a powerful noble house," Trian explained. He shook his head at the thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is an argument to be made that incredible structures as seen in many of Baralia's cities cannot be build in lands without slavery but I would say with enough gold and capable mages, the same could be achieved. It may take more time," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Virilya seems pretty impressive to me," Ilea said, ignoring the comments about training facilities. She would confront the responsible people if she came across something like that but getting involved without any knowledge was foolish. Her money and Claire could maybe achieve more on that front. Maybe the rejects could be bought up and brought to Ravenhall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is. And yet you haven't been to Baralia. Their cities are… monuments to their power and wealth. It's like a competition between clusters of noble families. Same goes for their assassin orders, mages and other trained and brainwashed individuals," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm, I met the Vowed. Implants in their teeth that explode in case they get too far from a ring. Nasty that," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oho? They're quite famous. Did you fight them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She waved him off. "No, I took out the implants and told them to go report to a guard captain I know in Riverwatch."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, I see. They will probably find it difficult to adjust to a free life," he mused. "Your lesson should start in a few minutes by the way."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah yes, the torture chamber," Ilea said and finished her plate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She smiled at the students sitting at the table, listening to the whole conversation. They'd have a lot to gossip about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea continued with her training, using the bow while injuring and healing the class with her ash. Trian and the enchanters had joined as well. Perhaps it would help the students to see some of the teachers going through the same pain and torment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It filled her with pride that every last one of the students participated this afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few would soon reach the second tier of Pain Tolerance, something that likely wasn't possible without a healer present. One that could take care of mental strains too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rest of her day Ilea spent with a short dancing lesson, telling Claire of her job in Riverwatch, and lastly a visit to the Caverns of Rot and her newfound silent friends, the Specters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was back in her routine, now once again having enough time to eat in between. Sometimes even for a nap. The next few days passed without a major incident, if one didn't consider the dangerous near death experiences with the Specters as incidents. They didn't invent new tactics to pin her down luckily, otherwise she might have had to find new dancing partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Azarinth Awakening reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 27'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Azarinth Awakening reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 28'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Blink reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 23'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Blink reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 24'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Sphere reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 17'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Sentinel Sphere reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 19'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Core reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 26'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Sentinel Core reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 27'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Azarinth Fighting reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 28'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Azarinth Perception reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 15'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Azarinth Perception reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 16'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Azarinth Reversal reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 18'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Aspect of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 27'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Aspect of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 28'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'True Ash Creation reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 25'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Ash and Ember Unity reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 23'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Ashen Wings reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 18'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Ashen Wings reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 19'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Eyes of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 10'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Eyes of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 11'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Avatar of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 24'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Avatar of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 25'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Keeper of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 24'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Deviant of Humanity reaches lvl 6'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Heavy Archery reaches lvl 8'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Monster Hunter reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 8'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Oxygen Repository reaches lvl 6'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Oxygen Repository reaches lvl 8'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sage of Torment reaches lvl 4'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Sage of Torment reaches lvl 6'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Veteran reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 2'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Arcane Magic Resistance reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 14'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' Blood Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 19'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' Blood Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 20'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea reached the Blood Magic milestone on the second day, immediately investing a point to advance it to the third tier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Blood Magic Resistance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have made masters of blood magic your enemies, pushing through and surviving despite the odds. Your body has been ravaged by this school of magic so many times, any count would be meaningless. Creatures beyond your imagination have tried to kill you, without success.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blood Magic Resistance – 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 1&lt;br/&gt;The arts of blood manipulation can be deceptive and dangerous to both ally and foe. You have stood against the old magic and lived. Next time your chance of survival will be even higher.&lt;br/&gt;2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; stage: Masters of this ancient art have found ways to use the very essence of your life against you. With sheer ferocity, you have shown that not every creature born of blood is prey alone. They will find it a challenge to invade and use what belongs to you alone.&lt;br/&gt;3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; stage: Your very blood has changed and evolved. While it may still be susceptible to change and foreign influence, it will not take the abuse lightly. Enemies will find their blood magic will demand a sacrifice should they choose to injure you. You may deactivate this effect.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;She found the effect would result in a reduced effect of the spells hitting the casters themselves. The Specters had minor ruptures ravaging their bodies after they used the ability against her. Not enough to kill them luckily. The creatures regenerated and didn't seem to feel pain, making them a great party to test the third tier on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;Ilea wondered if &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;she would get some form of Blood Magic &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;as a general skill if she &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;used &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;the feedback &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;often enough. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;Realistically, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;it would just level &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;the Resistance &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;but one &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="en-US"&gt;could hope.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Bone Magic Resistance reaches lvl 11'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Bone Magic Resistance reaches lvl 16'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Crystal Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 7'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Crystal Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 8'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Dark Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 2'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Divination Magic Resistance reaches lvl 3'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Earth Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 10'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Earth Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 11'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Flesh Magic Resistance reaches lvl 6'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Heat Resistance reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 6'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Mist Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 15'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Rot Resistance reaches lvl 2'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Rot Resistance reaches lvl 4'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Smoke Magic Resistance reaches lvl 8'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Smoke Magic Resistance reaches lvl 12'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sound Magic Resistance reaches lvl 12'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Sound Magic Resistance reaches lvl 13'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Void Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 15'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Void Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 16'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Water Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 10'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Wind Resistance reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 2'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_______________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The officer bowed, going to one knee as he addressed Lord Harken. "The scout reports are conclusive. We estimate heavy losses should you wish to take the city within the week."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rowan scowled, his eyes going from the officer to the map situated on a wooden table within the command tent. A variety of figures had been placed on top of it, carved from wood and stone, each symbolizing one of the many troops at his beck and call. Paid, trained, enslaved or otherwise employed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His most loyal guards and troops were situated close by. The scouts had been thorough, probing the independent city for the past few days. As annoying as it was, he could only commend the efforts that had gone into strengthening the town.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riverwatch had been a miserable frontier city when he had last visited eight years prior. A mismatched town of adventurers and people seeking to accomplish their hopes and dreams in the uncivilized and crime ridden independence of the west. A foolish notion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One that had cost them dearly, only two cities remaining of the downright ridiculous experiment. Rules and laws were there for a reason. Strict and guiding, for all blood lines, be it low born, slave or even noble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed Alistair Gallian proved to be worthy of his reputation, having taken control of the city despite his low birth. There were exceptions even among slaves and adventurers. Patrols and guards had been strengthened immensely, not just in numbers but in character too. Few could be paid for even scraps of information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the scouts had to be called back, to not alarm the competent leadership and officers of the city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rowan had thought the town an easy target and yet Nipha's indecision to conquer the lone standing target proved to be based on more than just incompetence. An attack by storm would cause heavy losses, not just among the soldiers but the population of the town as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sighed, still confident in the operation but annoyed at the set back. A challenge was welcome but at a time like this, he had to keep order in his ranks. Never had he marched with all his people, every soldier, cook, slave, and noble. The logistics was a nightmare. He was carrying supplies in his own storage ring and had to make everyone who possessed an item like that follow suit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He balled his fists as he thought about his lands, the ridiculous orders from his king. To be driven out of one's own lands. He saw it as his only option. The attempts to retrieve slaves from his territory by Riverwatch proved a perfect opportunity. His reputation would keep the king guessing. Was he responding to the theft with an iron hand or was he defecting? His son's demise at the hands of a Shadow forced him to act. Earlier than he had planned. His useless offspring had wasted all he had been given.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once Baralia fell, it would be too late for the king's realization, Rowan and his people too far away and not a concern. Lys moved slower than he had anticipated but his advisors had rarely been wrong. Baralia was doomed and so was Wynehold. The only way to escape the fires of war was to relocate, form new alliances and to rebuild Baralia out of the ashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If only he had acted when the first signs of incompetence showed in the high king thirty years back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He pushed the thought back. This wasn't a time for regrets. It was a time for war. A time for change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What of the Shadow?" he asked, looking at the dark winged figurine standing within the forest between his camp and the city of Riverwatch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is possible she was employed by the city, or she had a personal reason to attack the camp. Most soldiers had been caught off guard, under equipped, tired or drunk. We estimate her to be of minor concern in the conflict, if she is even still in the area," one of his officers explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harken looked at the man, his gaze making him wince. "She slaughtered forty men in the span of mere seconds. If she shows up we have to be prepared. Make sure the Vowed are informed. Focus their efforts on ash magic resistance and add more healers to their squads."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The reports may be exaggerated, my Lord," a nobleman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They may be. Her description and the abilities observed coincide with a new song a few bards have started singing in these parts. Lilith of Ravenhall. She too is said to be the main reason Riverwatch and Ravenhall formed an alliance," an officer said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harken let them talk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Songs and an uncertain alliance. Ravenhall doesn't have a standing military, the Shadow's Hand acting merely as a mercenary group."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And yet many have been seen participating in the war. It isn't unrealistic to assume her standing on the side of Riverwatch. As to the songs, they may be exaggerated but don't dismiss myths. Our research suggests the bards have not been paid to spread her name."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They could have easily been manipulated," another said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rowan stopped them with a gesture. "Be it as it may, we have to consider Shadows moving in to assist the town. Prepare gold and make sure our elite is ready to group up in case the reports have not been exaggerated and distorted by fear."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If only they knew more about this alliance. An extended siege was the only way he could make sure his people weren't decimated but it brought with it uncertainties. An exciting time indeed, one he deemed himself entirely too old to live through. Rowan ground his teeth, anger flowing through him as he wished he was powerful enough to kill King Baron himself.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">503348</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 10:54:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 464 Thresholds</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/502472</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 464 Thresholds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lightning surged from the being, yellow and bright like the suns. Thunder did not follow, the power sneaking through the sky without so much as a whisper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea was ripped out of her amazed stupor when the lightning crashed into the stone, ripping through with little resistance as she blinked away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not far enough, &lt;/em&gt;she thought as the shockwave sent her flying, residue lightning slowly flowing through her body as the damage was healed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wave of mana washed over her as she floated with her ashen wings, locking eyes with the being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le ave&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its voice rumbled through the vicinity like a spell of sound and air, broken by Ilea's resistances and her mental fortitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea's own aura marked her as a human of not quite the ordinary sort, her second tier Veteran skill keeping her moving, despite the level difference. And yet the creature seemed unimpressed. Still, it gave her a chance to flee, asking her to leave them in peace. Or perhaps it was asking her to die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not until you make me," she said with a smile, ashen spears forming around her, looking pitifully small against the thing they were supposed to injure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Battle, &lt;/em&gt;she sent and charged the being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It floated, without reaction, moving its wings before its mana manifested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lightning and air surged out, homing in on Ilea as she twirled and moved through the air with all the speed, precognition and maneuverability she could muster. The spells were dodged and still she was seared by lightning, its sheer proximity enough to burn through her armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slowly, the magic spread through her, leaving heavy damage that was instantly healed, the magic cost more than replenished by the spells themselves. The waves of air did nothing but push her further, her form circling the Basilisk as she was pushed away and closed in again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spells that missed her slammed into Karth itself, leaving deep gashes in the stone, the magic sending debris and boulders flying that would surely result in catastrophic avalanches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the lightning elemental was a machine gun, this creature was the orbital artillery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea knew very well that a direct hit would be catastrophic to her but the intervals made her confident that her third tier healing could keep her alive. She wondered if this creature too was holding back, like the Griffin had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that it hadn't obliterated their caravan on their first meeting spoke for such a theory and yet there could have been other reasons entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Doesn't hurt to play a little, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought as she circled the massive being. She narrowly avoided the attacks coming at her without pause, realizing shortly after that they were increasing in number. At the same time they came at her far quicker, the power in each bolt however reduced compared to before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Clever girl, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and pushed forward, a wave of air pushing her back and towards the mountain side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A blink let her avoid a swath of lightning projectiles, only to make her realized thirty more had already reached her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spells broke into her ash, spreading slowly as she counterhealed, using the third tier a few times as she was pushed back into the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fuck&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spells subsided only to let through a massive beam of lightning, aiming at her exposed torso.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea knew what to do, happy to see her perception slowing down to allow for an easier maneuver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lightning hit, the power surging through her, now even further slowed down as she focused on the energy. First to her core and out of her right arm. She couldn't aim it, barely holding it away from herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arm swelled up as the lightning spread through it, exploding in a splatter of gore and bone, the energy rushing out and into the night, most of the damage mitigated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her arm reformed as she pushed herself out of the stone, ash covering her once more, her bone set back inside of her necklace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Basilisk moved its wings lazily, yellow eyes looking at her from hundreds of meters away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea looked back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Okay, &lt;/em&gt;she sent and let herself fall down. &lt;em&gt;I got the memo. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Basilisk is a no no.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She couldn't help but summon her bow, sending one last arrow at the creature as she descended down the side of the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few bolts of lightning came as a response, moving after her like living beings before she dodged and weaved through them, using blink to avoid the last one right when she entered a sea of clouds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her sphere let her maneuver through without any fear of collision. She broke out below and slowed down, letting herself fall towards the dark landscape below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The small excursion was most definitely worth it, not only because of her quick test of strength against the being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Reconstruction reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 30'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Blink reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 22'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Sphere reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 16'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Core reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 25'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Azarinth Perception reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 14'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Armor of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 30'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Ashen Wings reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 17'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Eyes of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 9'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Avatar of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 23'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Deviant of Humanity reaches lvl 3'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Deviant of Humanity reaches lvl 4'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Deviant of Humanity reaches lvl 5'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Heavy Archery reaches lvl 7'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Veteran reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 19'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Veteran reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 20'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She checked while falling, moving her wings from time to time to make sure she wouldn't splat against the mountain side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Veteran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have faced creatures completely out of your league, since arriving here and up to this very moment. Not just that but you mostly faced them alone, even managed to get two four marks to fight each other. It's hard to say if you're a veteran or just a plain lunatic. Either way, you may unlock the third tier of Veteran.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Damn right I can!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Veteran reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 1'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Veteran - 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 1&lt;br/&gt;You have experienced the shouts and spells of beings completely out of your range of imagination. You will not survive but at least you won't be completely immobilized while you get eaten. Good luck warrior.&lt;br/&gt;2nd stage: You are immune to the fear of facing that which you do not understand. Be wary, some might sense your arrogance in the face of power, others might fear it.&lt;br/&gt;3rd stage: It seems you don't just happen upon impossible fights, you outright look for them. Your confidence and experience is obvious, not just to yourself but others too. Your second tier now extends to allies within a fifty meter radius, should you allow for such to happen. Additionally, your ability to gauge an unknown enemy's power is vastly improved.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Most definitely worth it, &lt;/em&gt;she thought with a smile. The buff to allies was welcome but she was more intrigued by the second part. &lt;em&gt;Might just check again. Should I?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea smirked and changed directions, flying up once more and through the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Basilisk was flying close to the mountain, not immediately taking note of her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Basilisk – lvl ????]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She knew instinctively that the creature was at least a thousand levels higher than her but anything more than that was a mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thousand three hundred at least, interesting. I wonder what I can tell about the Hatchling.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea decided against checking when the monster turned her way once more, instead blinking away and down back through the clouds. &lt;em&gt;It's just that I'm not interested. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;I could've easily &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;sneaked past. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Easily. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Definitely.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She respected the Basilisk, knowing most importantly that it had given her several chances, likely not killing her intentionally. &lt;em&gt;To think that caravan nearly &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;got wiped out &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;by &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;the warning of an illusion. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let's not tell that to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;relatives, &lt;/em&gt;she thought on her descent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I wonder what I'd get from the Fae with the third tier, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and pushed on, realizing that she had little idea of where exactly she was on the mountain. &lt;em&gt;Could check on Dawntree. Claire said they had a revolution or something going on?&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Ah, this was enough human conflicts for tonight. Maybe Iana and Christopher are done with their research.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She used Dale's mark to find Riverwatch and continued on from there, once again flying low and through the forest until she reached the Azarinth temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A blink brought her down and to the two enchanters. "Back," she said and waved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good," Iana said. "I believe this has been frustrating enough. We can leave," she added with a sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That bad hmm?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The fountain is in some way connected to the grass that should grow on the walls. Without it we can't reproduce its effects, not that it would be easily possible with the grass present," Iana explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Both enchantments are quite interesting however, they should help with our research," Christopher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, but we can't just copy them. Why would they use such overly complicated layouts? And this azarinth type of arcane magic is just frustrating," Iana said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I could demonstrate it," Ilea said with a smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman held up a hand and rubbed her temple. "No thanks, I've seen it enough already. Your class changed up your body to an extent where the study of your mana won't provide anything. Either the enchanters of this order were extraordinarily stupid or brilliant."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Often goes hand in hand," Christopher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea laughed, the enchantress didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Come on, it's funny," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you have anything else that you wanted to show us?" Iana asked, clearly tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Show? Hmm, well more someone you two could meet," she said. "You can sleep there too but I plan to leave again a few hours before dawn."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That doesn't leave much time," Christopher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Exactly, so let's move. His name is Weavy and he's a master of mind magic as well as a… user of demonic runes. Some other people there could also be of interest to you two," Ilea explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Where is there?" Iana asked, the three of them back out in the open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea formed cocoons of ash around them, leaving their heads uncovered this time. "The Vultures Brotherhood of course, an order of necromancers and dark mages."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Great," Iana said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Great!" Christopher confirmed, a broad smile on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's the most terrifying thing I've ever seen," Iana whispered, not able to take her eyes off the creature in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good! Not all of you humans are lost," Weavy said into their minds. "Mistress Ilea… you have, changed once more," he said, looking at her with an apprehensive air about him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't worry, demon. I still don't eat your kind," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No… you merely slaughter us," he whispered, not afraid but inspired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"From time to time," she said and walked past the being. "Be so kind and teach them something about demonic runes… and the Ascended stuff."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The secrets of my kind… so easily pried from my claws," he said and looked at his hands with the two abyss like holes within his skull.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She has that effect on people. Christopher, nice to meet you. A mind weaver? Fascinating. I'm sadly just a boring human," the enchanter said and laughed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weavy laughed as well but he had some work to do on that front, the sound more demonic gargle than anything else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey Eyn," Ilea said, waving to the boy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He bowed. "Mistress," he said with respect, joining his teacher after she had passed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, it's you. With visitors, again," Walter said as he stepped out of his inn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I flew here. Shouldn't have left a trace, don't worry," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your expedition to the north went well then?" he asked and walked back inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everybody else seemed to be out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So and so. Maro didn't come back yet?" Ilea asked. She was sure the necromancer would join them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He came in, chose a room and left again. Said something about needing some sea air for a while. Ah, Ilea. The red haired elf really wants to meet you again, said something about his evolution. He is… eager," Walter said and poured two mugs of ale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They'll have to wait. I'll have Elfie meet them soon enough but I should avoid the north for a little while at least," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Want to tell me about it?" the man asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure, the others are busy for a little while. Hey, you're a dark mage, right? Can you attack me while we talk?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Still working on those resistances, hmm?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yep. Plus third tier general skills by now. Each level is helpful," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You don't cease to surprise. Do tell. Maro only mentioned some annoying orange goo. He seemed a little down," Walter said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you think he'll be alright?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He patted her back and sat down. "I think so. Don't worry too much about him. He was a king, wasn't he? I'm sure he has been through worse. Now tell me. It's been dreadfully negative lately, with the war and all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You found them. And they're still alive… four mark. That is dangerous, really dangerous," he said and shook his head. "To think we fought a war against them thousands of years ago. And nobody remembers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sure some do," Ilea said. "Not like most humans would care about a war fought so long ago. Speaking of four mark, I found the Basilisk again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You did? The one from that caravan you traveled with years ago?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mhm… turns out they have some kind of mirage or illusion ability. Its real form completely destroyed me. Might even have managed to seriously injure me if it wasn't for my third tier lightning resistance."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man shot a dark projectile at her arm and smiled. "Good thing you had that then. You know… if I wouldn't meet elves from time to time, I'd forget how ridiculous things are out there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Walter… you live with a mind weaver and a literal skeleton. How does that surprise you?" Ilea said, downing her ale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those things are normal. Fighting Basilisks, ancient corruption, Griffins and Sand Elementals… those are stories of legend. Do you mind if I write some of it down? I'd change the name of course."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea stood up and smiled. "Just call me Lilith. Plenty of people already do," she said. "I have a training course to catch. Hope you don't mind us leaving again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are always welcome," Walter said, opening his eyes wide. "Wait, Lilith… from the songs?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That one," she said and winked, leaving the inn in search of her companions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That makes a lot of sense actually," Walter grumbled to himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She found them puzzling over a few runes scratched into a wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eyn, Iana and Christopher were staring at it, blood dripping from their noses as Weavy watched them intently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A capable bunch," he said to her when she entered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course they are," Ilea said. "Guys, we're leaving again. Or should I get you in a few days?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iana shook her head and turned. "No… no I believe it is best for us to get back to work. I will lose my mind if I continue this study. The world is a dangerous place," she said with a sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vast and full of possibilities," Christopher said with a grin. "Don't worry, we'll figure it out in time," he added and patted her back in a supportive manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It came so easy to me… and here these ancient ruins trip me time and time again… the Azarinth, Demons, Ascended… what can a mere human do?" Iana asked, seeming lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weavy just pointed a clawed finger at Ilea. "She is human too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Barely," Iana said and looked up. "But I suppose you're right. We will figure it out. Just need more time… Ilea, we will have to reach level two hundred soon. To extend our lives."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You want to extend your life just to study runes?" Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course. What other reason is there?" Iana asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's not get into this discussion right now," Ilea said. "Come on, let's go before the suns rise."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I didn't sleep," Iana said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll accelerate quickly again, you'll be out for the duration of the flight," Ilea said and patted her shoulder. "A higher level might help with that too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"True… Christopher, we will join a few combat lessons. Killing monsters will become a part of our routine. Our bodies are not prepared for the power of these runes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Did I just create a monster?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I see. I'll follow your lead," Christopher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Two monsters.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eyn chuckled. "They finally understand. Lady Ilea has saved my master and set him free. Now it is our turn."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Look what you did," Weavy whispered to her in an accusing tone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, take some credit, mind demon, I'm not the monster here," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, but you are. Look at me, how could anyone think I'm a monster?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea did and could very much see the resemblance. She did however not comment on it, unsure if he was developing sarcasm. Either way it seemed he was mocking her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Demon," she whispered, monster hunter rushing through the room as she froze everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She proceeded to pick up her companions and waved at the others. "Have a good time. Eyn, don't forget that you're human. Go and play with some peers sometime. And don't kill or eat them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was already out in the forest when the two enchanters could move again, her wings carrying her through the tunnels in seconds. "Ready?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes," Iana said and relaxed in her ashen cocoon, closing her eyes as she yawned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christopher nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good, then off we go," Ilea said and sped through the forest, emerging a few minutes later as she charged her wings. &lt;em&gt;Good night.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shock of near instant acceleration to whatever speed her wings could manage knocked the two out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Dark Magic Resistance reaches lvl 19'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;That was a nice change of pace. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Back to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;the boring old &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;training then, &lt;/em&gt;she thought, wondering how long it would take for Baralia to strike back. She hoped to get in a few days of training at the very least.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">502472</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 15:20:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 463 Quest</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/501612</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 463 Quest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale blinked a few times before he burst out laughing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's so funny?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He shook his head as he calmed down. "It's just… to attempt fighting a Basilisk, without a plan or preparation, nor a team. For the sheer sake of an achievement for one's next class evolutions. It sounds ridiculous to me and yet when you said it with a straight face, I just accepted it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale lifted the bottle again but decided against it, putting it away instead after he glanced at her with a questioning look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Theoretically, people like you should exist, should be out there. Hunting and fighting, improving so much that they are hardly recognizable as humans anymore. I just never thought I would actually meet someone like that. Now the most dangerous thing I've met is not an elf anymore but someone I call a friend," he said and sat back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Life is full of surprises, isn't it?" Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That it is. As to your question, I haven't heard of a Basilisk. Not since your caravan encountered it several years ago. I suggest you check the guild to see if they have anything to offer," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is it open at this time?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's always open," Dale confirmed. "You're not the only one who sleeps very little. I for example just don't exactly have a choice," he said and got up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're going too?" she asked and followed the man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To Alistair, yes. I will report your success and the potential issue. I know you hate these technicalities," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're a treasure, Dale. Really," Ilea said to him took a deep breath of fresh air, only a tiny bit sullied by the smells of the city. Riverwatch luckily did have a sewer. &lt;em&gt;The marvels of magic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And you are a monstrous killing machine that I am fortunate to call an ally," he said and sighed. "When did you say the slaves should arrive?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A few days. It's hard to say exactly how long they need. My flying speed keeps improving," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Way to make me envious of your power," he said and smiled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, a few weeks of dungeon training with me by your side and you'll be the strongest in town. You say the word," she suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale crossed his arms. "Thank you. I mean it. I would rather do it the old fashioned way, lest I turn into a creature of ash too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you calling me a monster?" she asked, her limbs fanning out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man wasn't fazed in the least. "Keep your intimidation tactics to people that don't know you. Good luck on your hunt, and stay safe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll do my best," she said, tapping his shoulder before she vanished into the night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The guild hadn't changed much since she had visited. A few repairs were visible but only thanks to her sphere, otherwise well done. To her surprise, the guild hall was packed. Dozens of people drinking and feasting together, just as many waiting in line to get quests or get rewards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It felt nostalgic, even though she had barely participated in this type of life. These were the adventurers of Elos, slaying monsters and taking care of the various problems that come with a life near the bottom of the food chain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oy, healer! Ya lookin for a strong team!?" a very loud patron called out to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Warrior – lvl 68]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Adventurers of Elos indeed, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and joined one of the lines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Didn't ya hear me?" the man called out again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Leave her be, don't wanna insult the orders, they're a nasty bunch," his friend said, a rogue of a similar level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Miss, I want to apologize for the behavior of my fellow adventurers. My name is Asher," someone else walked up to her and introduced himself. He looked straight out of a romance novel, long blond hair and a charming smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Mage – lvl 102]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hello Asher, what is it that you want?" Ilea asked as the line moved forward, the man dancing around her to avoid bumping into the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It has come to everyone's attention that you are a healer. Your kind is rare within these halls. I was wondering if perhaps you were looking to join a team?" he asked, getting straight to the point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea liked that he didn't try to manipulate her at first. He simply greeted her and asked. "How surprising, you actually have manners." she said. "Are you from Riverwatch, Asher?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The name amused her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not everyone here grows up in a gutter," he said and winked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it would have had more of an effect on her if she hadn't met Elves and powerful Shadows, a few of them rivaling the sexiest men on Earth in looks. Or perhaps it was all the blood and guts, all the death she had seen, that let her ignore his attempt at charming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can see that. As much as I'm intrigued, I believe I'm looking for different jobs than you," she said, arriving at the front of the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Welcome. Your badge please," the attendant said, a rather petite woman in her twenties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What kind of jobs are you looking to do? We can adjust. If we had a healer in our team," Asher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're…," the attendant said when Ilea handed in her silver badge, identifying her as a level fifty healer. "Would you like an updated version? You are far beyond silver," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Mage – lvl 110]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wondered how high the woman could identify. &lt;em&gt;Does she think I'm one fifty? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Two hundred?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure, whatever is the equivalent of this," she said and summoned her Shadow badge, placing it on the counter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asher opened and closed his mouth before taking a step back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman nodded and checked the badge. "This is real. Let me see if we have any emerald badges. Ah… as you are a Shadow, I'm not sure how many jobs you did for the adventurer guild. If you didn't reach a certain quota, the badge will cost you one gold piece and thirty silver. Is that okay?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why do I need an updated version then?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It may provide entry to certain dungeons, cities, inns and other establishments. Granted, your Shadow badge opens most of those doors but not all of them. Do you wish to have it?" the woman asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure, why not," Ilea said and summoned the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than a few people were looking her way by now, the conversations having died down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asher chuckled. "Apologies for wasting your time, Miss Shadow," he said and bowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea smiled. "Don't worry about it. I appreciate the way you asked, compared to the dolt over there," she said and nodded towards the man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What did ya say!?" he said and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't!" his friend called out but it was too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I said that you lack manners," Ilea said to the low level warrior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asher took a few steps back, trying to get out of the way. A wise choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't give a fuck what shit order you're a part of. Shadow or noh-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A slap sent the man sprawling on the floor, a few teeth missing and blood dripping from his mouth. He was knocked out cold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Apologies," Ilea said when the attendant returned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, no worries. It's not the first time he has ended up in a similar situation. I will put the cleaning cost on his tab," she said and handed over the new healer badge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looked the same other than the metal it was made of. A dark green that didn't reflect much light. She paid and made the thing vanish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Anything else I can do for you?" the woman asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm looking for information on a certain creature," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea soared through the skies, trying to identify the landscape. Sadly there had been no new information on a Basilisk in the area. The attendant could however pin point the area where Ilea's caravan had encountered the creature last on a map.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She would have perhaps found it anyway but the process was much faster this way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few skeletons showed that she had found the right place. &lt;em&gt;Nazarks, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and kicked a skull away. &lt;em&gt;Not decayed, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;chewed off.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The ciiiiircle of liiiife," she sang to herself and strolled towards the cavern entrance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few creatures moved by in the nearby forest, doubtlessly aware of her. It seemed they deemed her too dangerous to approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lucky for them, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought and found parts of the caravan still sitting untouched within the cavern. Ripped apart wood, wagons, spoiled goods, weapons and destroyed armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the Nazark corpses had little remaining on their bones but it did look like only the brave had come in here to feed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed bizarre to her, that after all this time, this cave remained mostly untouched. &lt;em&gt;Why would it be any different? It's not like a city was struck by a natural disaster and had to be cleaned up.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She grabbed a sword that had been missed or deemed cheap enough to be left behind, twirling it in her hand as she looked for any traces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tracks were old. No traces of magic either, nor a massive winged creature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea spread her own wings and flew through the cavern, speeding up as her senses didn't pick up a single thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She chose the largest rift she could find and entered. The tunnels were large, dozens of ways leading away from the main one, naturally formed or created by the denizens of Karth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She stayed in the main tunnel, the walls moving farther away by the minute. Bones and a general absence of living creatures gave the area an eerie atmosphere. &lt;em&gt;Not quite as eerie as &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;the presence of &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;rot &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Specters.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea found herself in darkness but kept flying, speeding up as time went on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hiss resounded in front of her, making her stop in her flight. Her skills were ready, the sound expected this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'You have heard a mighty being's cry, you resist the effect'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not quite the same as last time, &lt;/em&gt;she thought with a smirk and moved in the darkness. The buildup of mana was graspable, permeating the air as the spell manifested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She turned and faced the creature, unable to see it, nor close enough to perceive it in her sphere. &lt;em&gt;Something &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;is wrong.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spell manifested, a wave of air moving her way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She saw it come within her sphere and rushed backwards, blinking to the side twice as the powerful magic rushed by.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is this?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The whole cavern rumbled when the spell impacted the opposite wall a moment later. Quite a powerful attack. &lt;em&gt;But I avoided it so easily.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea rushed at the creature, reaching it moments later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Large wings and a head that reminded her of a dragon and snake mix. A wide maw with crooked teeth as wide as her head. Scales lined its body like armor, its eyes looking right at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Basilisk – lvl ????]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Found you!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then she was there, ashen limbs smashing into the monster's head, most glancing off but four finding purchase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It lashed out, the attack avoided with a quick twirl to the side as more limbs smashed into it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea closed the distance, her fist slamming into its skull with a full load of her destructive spells. She watched as it opened its maw, releasing a lightly charged Heart of Cinder into its throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Basilisk veered back and started charging another spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She stopped, floating in midair as she closed her eyes. &lt;em&gt;This is all wrong. It veered back. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Trakorov &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;barely moved. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;I remember it too, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;the ice mage &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;injured it as well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its spell was charged and released, another wave of air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time she trusted Azarinth Fighting, feeling the attack coming and letting it wash over her. It barely scratched her armor, the wind moving to each side as if she split it in half.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Illusion? &lt;/em&gt;She sent the thought towards the being. A question. One she did not expect an answer to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet, she received one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L ea ve&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Broken sounds spoken with an inhuman voice that transcended the material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She felt her very soul shake. &lt;em&gt;Not &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;very reassuring. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maybe I should listen to the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ancient creature.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You killed half of that caravan, I'm not leaving," she said, quickly realizing that it wasn't exactly the reason she was here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea hadn't known many of the adventurers that died on that day, nor had she cared much back then, let alone now. No, she was driven by something different than justice or even revenge. Merely curiosity and a potential achievement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was it enough to challenge such a being? Perhaps not, but curiosity would find it difficult to kill Ilea, just as everything else did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She rushed the creature once more but found nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It had vanished entirely, as if it had teleported away. Only traces of its magic remained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Only one way to go, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and continued down the tunnel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few more wind magic spells disrupted her journey but the Basilisk itself didn't approach anymore. The charge time for its attacks lessened and the power itself increased with each spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tunnel led into another cavern, this time in a bowl like shape, a few crystals growing from the ceiling providing enough light for her to see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hmm, not good, I think?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea reached the center and with it the remains of the largest egg she had ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Baby Basilisk, no wonder she was so pissed back then. That healer guy was right.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She remembered the druid had sensed something, telling them to flee from the cavern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is this worth something? &lt;/em&gt;she wondered and broke off pieces of the shell, storing them in her necklace. The egg was already broken, so she dismantled it with her ash and took it with her. Not everyday do you come across a four mark creature's hatched egg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Now I feel like a scavenger, &lt;/em&gt;she thought, wondering if the residents of Hallowfort would look for discarded egg shells themselves. She wouldn't say no to Trakorov shell armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A definite exit to the cavern revealed itself when she looked up, a large circular shaft expanding up into the unknown. &lt;em&gt;I wonder if it's still here, or if that thing I saw before was just a remnant of its power. A dormant spell to protect its spawn.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her wings moved and she was taken up, soon back in near complete darkness. A few cracks and tunnel entrances showed up within her sphere from time to time, testament to the intricate underground network that was home to native creatures unknown and dangerous. Many had likely never seen the light of day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A nightmare to most and yet exciting to Ilea, finding a fascinated joy in exploring the unknown. Something perhaps intricate to any human, muffled by fear and the need to survive. Or perhaps she truly was a deviant, her interests andjoys so far removed from human, she could hardly be defined as such anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question did not have an answer, not one she would accept, even if an all knowing being deemed her worthy of the knowledge. Despite her changes, her power and the experiences she went through and would continue to live out, she knew that she was human. And she would remain such forever, no matter to what twisted forms her body, her magic, and her mind evolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flight was long, considering the speed she was traveling at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When she emerged out into the open, the air had thinned, the moons seemed closer, shining bright. Cliffs and boulders grew around her in towering shape and size. The way oceans made her feel small and insignificant, the mountain of Karth came quite close itself, formed over millions of years through shifts deep below the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plateau she found herself on was located far above the clouds dotting the sky below, only faint colors visible of what amounted to forests, lakes and plains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bones littered the area, flesh and organs still clinging to some. Creatures larger than most living things Ilea had ever seen or fought. The sheer logistics of bringing these creatures up here seemed ridiculous to her but when she considered the Basilisk's size, impossibilities turned feasible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gaping abyss behind her led to where its spawn had hatched. She didn't know why the being had laid it deep underground instead of up here, above the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea remembered that the skies above belonged to beings far above humanity. Those were the words of the librarian she had consulted back in Riverwatch, when she had known nothing of the world. Now, while she silently moved through the graveyard of bones, she felt like she had learned precious little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Already she could see the green scales in the distance, moving with tremendous ripples of muscle. The creature lay surrounded by stone, its eyes closed, unaware of the ant within its domain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was not the Basilisk she had seen. In many ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looked smaller, less vicious. And still, its sheer presence shined bright within her sphere, despite being outside its influence. Like flames whose heat could be felt before one's eyes could find it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify worked from this distance, either because the being was immensely powerful, its aura inhibited or because its sheer size demanded it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Basilisk Hatchling – lvl ????]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is probably the best chance I'll ever get,&lt;/em&gt; she thought, wondering if she would really kill a baby, for the chance of a better class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hiss came as the answer to her moral dilemma. It flowed over the mountain like a wave crashed into the seaside cliffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'You have heard the challenge of a Basilisk. You resist its effects'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea found the creature hovering in the night sky, its shape unmistakable and its power unquestioned. She wondered if there were a few Trakorovs and Fae in the area to recruit in her endeavor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this time, she was alone.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">501612</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 15:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 462 Mark of Trust</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/500305</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 462 Mark of Trust&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea watched as the slaves were led to another open section of the camp. One not littered with corpses and blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She waited until all of them had arrived. There were more than the group she had talked to before. Most of them were women. None of them were mages or warriors. There were smiths, leather workers, farmers and many other professions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea already had their attention. "Okay. I'll make it quick. I killed your master. You are free now. If you want to, Riverwatch will take you in. You will get a life, a job and a right to decide on your own fate. That is one of your choices and the one I suggest you take. The other one is to take what you can from this camp and leave, to wherever you want to go."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Murmurs went around the group after a moment of silence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea looked at them all. Some were scared and crying, others happy and crying. A few were cursing at her, others were cheering. &lt;em&gt;Alistair, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;I &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;commend &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;you &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;for dealing with this.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Grab what you can anyway. Gold, clothes, weapons and gear. The way to Riverwatch will take a few days," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A surprising number of them got to work immediately, grabbing their friends and going through the camp, looking for clothes or even looting the corpses she had left behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vowed," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They all rushed to her and stopped in formation. "Make a line. I will remove your implants."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of them complained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five minutes later, they were all free of their burden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do most slaves have something like that?" Ilea asked Steve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Too expensive, &lt;/em&gt;he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I see. Now, all of you. From now on you are free. I suggest you go to Riverwatch too. You can work as guards, adventurers, soldiers. Whatever you want. Your abilities will be greatly appreciated."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They looked at her, not quite understanding the words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Always a master, &lt;/em&gt;Steve wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not anymore," Ilea said and took off the ring, crushing it in her hand before she dropped the remains onto the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Think of it like this. You are now your own masters. You can decide," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why not you? You are strong.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Because I don't hold slaves. Not even if you lot want it. If you want a last task then protect everyone while you lead them to Riverwatch. As soon as you are there report to Dale Langston. If you simply cannot comprehend having no master, he is a good man at least and he will put you to work. Otherwise, decide on your own," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of them bowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Steve, do you know the way to Riverwatch? And do you think you can protect everyone while you go there?" she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Steve knows the way. Very little danger. Drakes, wolves and soldiers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good. Then I will leave it to you to escort everyone there. Those who want of course. Everyone who wants to leave is free to do so," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Great, means I don't have to fucking escort everyone for days.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She went back to the tent, the one man still crying over Luis' body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cursed demon," he whispered, not looking at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are free to bury him and to go back to Baralia. And you are free to seek revenge. He was a man who believed himself to be worth more than others. Someone who owned people, caged and chained them," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man turned his head her way. "He loved us. And I loved him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea left him to mourn. &lt;em&gt;That'&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;s why &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;fighting humans &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;just &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;isn't &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;for &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;me, &lt;/em&gt;she thought. &lt;em&gt;At least &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;now he can &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;be &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;miserable &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;as a free man.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She chuckled at the thought and shook her head. "This sucks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Death is never pleasant, ashen savior," a woman said. She bowed when Ilea turned her way. "You have set us free. My whole life have I waited. Prepared. I imagined so many ways. To break free, to escape. And I never did. I never had the courage."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You have your whole life in front of you," Ilea said, unsure of what else to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you," the woman said and looked up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea noticed dozens of people listening, looking at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What is your name?" a man asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can call me Lilith," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The camp raided, provisions and wagons prepared, the convoy set out. Protected by the Vowed who would lead everyone to Riverwatch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only nine people chose to leave on their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea hoped they would make it. Their chances weren't good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She checked the surroundings from the air, quickly finding a few fleeing warriors and mages as well as the monsters that would soon prey on them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hundreds of peoples' lives. Entirely changed by little old me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She turned around and checked on the convoy, torches lighting their way. &lt;em&gt;On the right track. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Good.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next stop was the Azarinth temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iana and Christopher had moved down into the cellar, studying the well and the walls. No new bluemoon grass had sprouted but the glow was unmistakable. The roots were still there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh my fuck!" Christopher exclaimed when he turned and saw Ilea standing there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, sorry," she said with a knowing smirk. Blink was entirely silent. "How's it going?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well! Splendid… thank you for taking us here. It is most interesting!" he exclaimed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And frustratingly useless to us," Iana grumbled. "How is your mission going?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Done. Well… I killed a Baralia noble's son. How high do you think the chances are of them retreating and forgetting about this?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Zero percent," Iana said with a monotone voice. "Christopher, check the fourth layer on this one. Any clue what it means?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea sighed. "Ah man. Okay, you seem to be busied for a while. I will brief Alistair and Dale. Ah, he's going to love having a murder commando under his control."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;He's going to hate it, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and couldn't stop herself from smiling, just a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She checked her notifications on her way to Riverwatch, making sure to fly low and through the forest. Ilea ignored all the messages about defeated, no, slaughtered people. She knew that should she get involved in the war directly, thousands more would follow. Thousands who thought their beliefs to be righteous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Sphere reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 15'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Ashen Wings reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 16'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Monster Hunter reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 7'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On the other hand, you could save thousands, &lt;/em&gt;she argued. Some of the warriors had chosen not to fight but if she went into their lands, attacked their homes, it may be different. Uprooting so many people and bringing them into an existing city or a newly built settlement required tremendous resources, otherwise more suffering would surely follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the fires of war already raging in Baralia, it was easy to justify the funding of operations to extract former slaves. Her network so far was sadly not wide enough to provide large scale support. The Sentinels would hopefully fill in that gap in a few decades or even years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She assumed the empire and any other country involved were after not just gold and land but the people too. Employing former slaves seemed like a sure way to boost one's economy. Especially if those slaves were skilled and experienced workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea decided to keep her involvement low for now. The operations launched in Riverwatch were in part funded by her and Claire, making her feel somewhat responsible. She didn't know what kind of fate a freed slave would have if she attacked and slaughtered their masters. The ones extracted and brought to Riverwatch however, those she could employ and feed. Or people she trusted would fill that role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She landed in the city, the cover of night masking her approach. Once more she was glad her wings were near black and not bright lightning like Trian's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sentinel Huntress and her sphere quickly led her to Dale's guard station, picking up traces of him in the surroundings. A few blinks brought her in front of his office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sat on his desk, working through the night with a straight back and strained eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wondered when he had last seen his family. She knocked and watched him sigh and relax back into his chair before he straightened again. &lt;em&gt;Captain, &lt;/em&gt;she thought with a smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Come in," his words were muffled through the thick wooden door, simple in design but sturdy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She opened it and stepped inside, closing the door behind herself with an ashen limb as she took in the gloomy atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His office had remained the same, a testament to simplicity and efficiency. An officer's dream. The only source of light was an oil lamp placed slightly behind his table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You look overworked," she said and formed an ashen chair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sighed. "And you look like an uninvited dangerous Shadow, ignoring boundaries such as walls without a hint of remorse." He leaned back again, crossing his arms. Despite the hour, he managed a slight smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The perks of power. And teleportation," she said and sat down. "I'm afraid I'm bringing more work."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As is tradition," Dale said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Warrior – lvl 149]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had leveled again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you aware of the request sent to Ravenhall?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He quirked up an eyebrow. "The one sent today? Yes, the officers were consulted. You came so quickly?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;He's not even surprised anymore, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea though. She was a little bit disappointed. &lt;em&gt;Could show him some other shit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"About Baralia stopping attempts at slave extraction from the southwest part of their territory," she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale opened a drawer and grabbed a few sheets of paper. "Let me guess, you already went and took care of it? Did you consult Alistair at least?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I did, both of those things, here comes the new work bit," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man started laughing, grabbing a pen before he calmed down. "Okay, shoot. What did you get us this time?" he sounded genuinely excited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea explained her earlier encounter briefly, happy to find the man showing a reaction this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Vowed… and you killed an actual Harken… to think they sent one of the sons because of this," he shook his head and sighed. "Wouldn't you assume that a war on your doorstep is more of a concern than a few hundred escaped slaves?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't know them. Maybe Riverwatch just seems like an easier target than the Empire," she suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Possibly. Well, it was inevitable. You scared them away but if their lands don't get attacked, we will have another strike to prepare for. They may not hide in the forests anymore," Dale said. "I will report this to Alistair immediately."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How come the Harkens aren't involved in the war yet? I thought the empire was sweeping Baralia, aided even by the other surrounding kingdoms," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't have the full picture. The Empire seems more focused on rebuilding and securing their own lands right now. Powerful high level teams have entered Baralia but it's a large country. I doubt this conflict will be over anytime soon," the captain explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I would have expected more," Ilea said with a sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It took them a year to break the siege of Virilya. I believe a majority of that time was spent on internal politics but if they had the power for a swift strike against Baralia, they would have done so much earlier," Dale said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When do you expect a strike? If they don't get held up by Empire forces?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Difficult to say. A small scale attack could happen in a few days already. But Ilea, you don't have to stay because of your attack. Alistair asked for assistance in taking out the enemy, not to help defend the city. We are prepared," he said and looked at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You don't believe me? Or do you just think us that weak?" he asked. "I'm not insulted… just curious."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I know little about how to defend a city. Ravenhall, with the Shadow's Hand was overwhelmed and decimated by a couple thousand summoned demons. I doubt Riverwatch could hold against something similar. There are… things out there…," she didn't continue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale smiled knowingly. "I know. I have seen some of them too, despite my comparatively low level, Ilea. Most will stay away from the noise and smells of a town, let alone a large city like Riverwatch. We're talking about Baralia, humans. Not wild beasts. We have an idea about their troops. If Lord Harken doesn't mobilize his whole army to attack us, we will hold."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What if he does?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale tapped the table a few times as he thought. "Then perhaps our new ally would be inclined to help. I'm sure a few Shadows would tip thebattle in our favor."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You seem to know exactly how strong they are," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I said we have an idea. Of course we don't know enough. One rarely does. It seems unlikely that they would move enough troops to challenge our city. For what? Freed slaves?" he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For a murdered son," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man didn't counter that argument.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In any case. It may take a while for you lot to call for help. Which is why I visited you first. I have a skill with which I can mark someone. I can find them. Plus they can release it to call for me. Thought you should have one."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Me? You place too much trust in me. There are far more powerful and capable people in this city. Alistair being one of them," Dale said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Whether that may be true or not, I don't call them friends. This mark isn't meant as a gesture from Ravenhall for Riverwatch. It's meant as a gesture from me to you. If someone kidnaps your family or if you face an enemy too powerful to overcome, call for me. If your city is under attack and you need assistance, call for me. I will be there. Perhaps not immediately but I will come, that I promise to you," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think of you as a friend too, Ilea. I just think you may be overdoing it. I helped you out when we found you near the city but that hardly qualifies for you to be at my beck and call," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I trust your judgment. Obviously don't call for me if it isn't necessary. I know you would do the same for me. Give me your hand," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man complied and soon sported a runic mark on the back of his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you know how to use it?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale nodded. "Incredible. How much power you used just for that. As if it was nothing. I could see the mana that flowed into it's creation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't forget that I took out a camp of slavers in less time than it took me to get there. A group your city deemed difficult enough to warrant help from Ravenhall," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fair enough," he said and smiled. "You're really something. What's your current level anyway?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Three forty eight, and I should get a third class if I get to three fifty. According to an ancient Fae," Ilea explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dale nodded. "Sounds about right. Don't lose yourself up there, in your level of power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I try not to," she said and smiled. "Talking to you always helped with that, you know?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thanks," she added. "And not just for helping me that one time. Thanks for showing me the ropes, giving me gear when I had none and for seeing me as a human. Even now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He opened a drawer and got out a fancy looking bottle and two glasses. "It just shows me what we're capable of. And it's good to know not everyone in your leagues is a noble born twat."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea chuckled and watched him pour, taking her glass right after.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought you didn't drink on duty," she teased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's a first time for everything, isn't there?" he said and looked at the mark on his hand. "Plus, I can call a Shadow now, might just be safe to have a drink now and then." He turned his hand a few times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Maybe you're right. So, just call me if anything comes up," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will. Are you staying in Riverwatch for a while? I would assume we ripped you out of an important schedule. Or were you about to leave on an adventure again? To the west this time? Or eastward?" he seemed genuinely interested, taking a sip of his drink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wondered how close to Whiskey it actually was. She preferred other beverages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just for a little while. Hopefully not even a day. Say, have there been any news on a Basilisk on the road to Salia lately?" she asked and leaned forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You don't honestly think of…? Ilea, as a friend, and your elder, I strongly advise against this plan of yours. We are talking a legendary creature… one rarely even seen, never without casualties," he said. "It's a four mark, isn't it? You're not even a three mark yet!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Humans start at zero," she said and shrugged. "What do you think a Basilisk gets born at? Three hundred? Eight? Maybe a thousand?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It doesn't matter… there's a reason creatures like that are at the top of the food chain. Traps won't help you with this, neither will careful planning, tools and weapons. Something like that is a force of nature," the man said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I didn't exactly have a plan in mind. But I have to see. Last time we fought it seemed… beatable? And I wasn't even level one hundred. None of us were," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And still, you lost dozens of people. Take it as a grace of fate, if you will. It won't happen again. Can you not wait until you've reached ample strength? With your progress it can't be too far off until you yourself are a natural disaster."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea frowned. "But then it might be too late for an achievement!"&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">500305</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 13:39:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 461 Infiltration</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/499400</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 461 Infiltration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Luis Harken, hmm? Charming man," Ilea said as she read through the notes on the man. A level one sixty two mage and the leader of this rag tag group of government funded bandits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You think it will work?" she asked, having outlined the rough plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He shrugged. The epitome of confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A shrug is enough for me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dress or roughed up leather armor?" she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Armor. More believable.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Probably," she murmured and let her ashen armor flow to her back. She casually slashed open her arm and rubbed some of the blood onto her face. A few rough rounds through her hair with both hands left it disheveled enough. "How do I look?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rugged, &lt;/em&gt;the man wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Beautiful enough to peak interest?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea squinted her eyes. "Are you just saying that because you think I'm your master?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Smart man.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them casually strolled into the camp. At the sight of the slave she had come to call Steve, the guards nearly ignored her completely. Two men a little above level one hundred tried hard not to look at Steve, clasping their weapons a little more tightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He gestured her to continue and stepped back into the forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The camp was quite vast, trees felled to provide space for tents, some luxurious while most were quite simple. Moonlight shined from above, few clouds obscuring it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good evening, gentlemen," Ilea said with fake apprehension, glancing around frantically to give off the notion of a carp inside a wasp nest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Vowed brought you here… who are you?" one of them asked, now quite a bit more hostile than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;God you are stupid. The other guy is at least respecting my level. The Vowed… of course.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was separated from my team. I'd like to talk to whoever is in charge here," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man laughed and glanced at his companion. "I'm in charge as far as I'm concerned. You want to stay the night? Have food and water? Maybe we can work something out. Not the ugliest I've ever had."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea took in his scent, the sweat and lack of hygiene, his aura, the feel of his magic, as dull as it was. She would find this man and she would personally rip off his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We shouldn't… what if he finds out. You know what happened to those scouts," the other guard said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That seemed to put a real damper on the dead man's ambitions. He wrung with himself but finally his fear won out over his desires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What makes such a high level healer travel alone through here? With which order are you?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I would like to discuss such matters with whoever is in charge. As to your earlier comments, I hope you will fulfill my request. You know what will happen if a Corinth Order member suddenly vanishes," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He turned to her and got close. "A lone healer… and you still think your order will protect you. Here? In the middle of nowhere? How will they find me, I wonder?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They will interrogate your friend over there. Or the silent one who brought me here. He seemed more wise than you are," Ilea said, enjoying the twisting veins on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Invoking the Corinth order's name brought her some joy. She couldn't agree more with the man. Nobody would come for a lone healer caught in a war camp of a bunch of slavers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Follow me. No crap or you will be thrown to the slaves," he said, walking ahead through the camp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea could see the grin on his face thanks to her sphere. He believed her fate set in stone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I'm going to expand your world by so many dimensions, little warrior man.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Warrior – lvl 112]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her sphere gave her an idea of the equipment of the people here. This wasn't a rogue team trying to get a few slaves back. This was a war camp, perhaps one of many. Why they were here instead of their own country was another question entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is that lord really that petty? Just forget about those slaves. Get your forces behind the walls and defend against Lys.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When she was let into the largest and most unnecessarily decorated tent, the question of pettiness answered itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four Vowed ones occupied the large room, one in each corner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sprawled out in what looked like a couch lay a man wearing gold laced pants and no shirt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked bored as he turned to her and the guard that had brought her here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With him were nine women in a varied state of undress. And three men. They littered the floor as if they were furniture or pets. A few of them took note of Ilea but tried hard not to glance her way. The man had dark green eyes, toned muscles and wavy hair. A short beard gave his face a pleasant form as he rested on one hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who is she?" he asked in a bored tone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sir, she came looking for help. She claims to be part of the Corinth order, separated from her team," the guard helpfully informed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A frightened and lost cub has come to my tent. Tell me, my dear. What are the principles taught to the Corinth order?" he asked in the same monotone voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fuck&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You got me. I'm not part of an order. The rest is true," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The guard next to her grinned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh? So you lied to us? Now that… that doesn't paint a very bright future for you, my dear. Hmm… it has been a while however, that I have feasted on such a rough… animal. And healing powers are so, enticing. You may stay the night. With me," the man said with a slight smile. He didn't sound malicious, perhaps truly believing it to be a courtesy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He stood up slowly and appeared in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Mage – lvl 162]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My name is Luis Harken. I welcome you to my tent," he said and touched her face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea stepped closer, reaching out and stroking his arms. She brushed her still armored chest against his and found his hand, her fingers brushing the thing she was looking for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She got close to his ear, noting that his heart rate had increased, his manhood pushing through his pants against her thigh. "Now, my dear. Promise not to scream."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ash spread out behind her and into the man's mouth as she snapped off his finger and with it the signet ring. Four more limbs immobilized the guard that had brought her here as she took a step back, both men caught in her ash, the missing finger already healed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shiny," she said and looked at her outstretched hand, the golden ring topped off with a red signet. "Vowed, take a step forward."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four men in the corners of the tent simultaneously took a step forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea was happy none of the slaves had spoken a word. She could tell that a few of them weren't exactly present, their minds within a fog of ecstasy. Those that weren't were very distressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Interesting. All that is needed is this ring. Steve was right, what a surprise," she mused to herself and looked at her captives. Their mouths were still filled with ash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't worry, I'm here to free slaves, not kill them," she said and crouched down in front of Luis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"See, you're quite attractive. I might have considered your proposal if you didn't hold humans like cattle."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He made a muffled noise as his body caught fire, a spell forming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea's hand lashed out. The slap extinguished the flames entirely, the man nearly going unconscious. Her healing brought him back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Now, now, now. Listen to me, Luis. I want you to realize in what position you're in," she said as her ashen armor extended around her. The grip of her ashen limbs strengthened on both of the men. She noted that his erection didn't wane. Quite the contrary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ew, now I feel dirty.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your life is in my hands, do you understand that?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man nodded, fear in his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Now, I want you to answer everything I ask and do as I say. Or I will kill you. It's as simple as that," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He nodded frantically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You won't scream if I take out the ash?" she waited for the nod and then freed his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man coughed, helped along by her healing. "You won't get away with this, woman. My father-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another slap made him shut up. A few of his teeth had broken, as well as his jaw. Ilea healed it quickly as her ash kept his screaming to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Listen here you little shit. I really don't want to torture you, you're just so fucking weak I nearly kill you with a slap. Your threats aren't very convincing with that thing poking through your pants."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My sexual interests matter not. You dared lay a hand on a Harken. You life is forfeit. Unless… perhaps we can find an arrangement," he suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea sighed. "Okay. First tell me what this ring can do. I can feel several uses."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It shows the enchantments placed within the Vowed and lets you charge them," the man explained. He remained quite calm after his small literal outburst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Confident that he has the upper hand. Even bound and horny. This man hasn't lost a single time in his life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You, get every Vowed here to this tent," she said, pointing at one of them. "You, tell the guards outside that I'm the new master. Nobody is to be let in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both men vanished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don't get used to it. You will have to give away this toy. It is the ethical thing to do.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I can at least be evil for a little while, &lt;/em&gt;she thought with a smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you really here to retake the slaves freed and taken from your lands?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man looked at her as if it was the stupidest question to ask. "Of course. My father doesn't take lightly on thievery. These lines of slaves have been held for generations. Fed and trained by us. Given purpose. A light response would not stand."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Really? Even though your country is at war with several nations?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The king will prevail. And Wynehold will stand. It has been that way for centuries. The empire is weakened, wounded. It will bleed out in our lands, as will any other that dare to attack," Luis explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is he delusional? Or does he know something I don't. Claire seemed sure the war was at an end. Just a matter of time until the kingdom is conquered or destroyed, its parts split between the vultures.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why are you so sure of victory?" Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My father believes the priests of the order. I personally trust more in our military might. You must understand that the siege of Virilya was merely a play. A distraction for those who wanted war, bored of the status quo. The true power of Baralia remains within our cities, none of which will be taken," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Bored. What the fuck," Ilea said and sat down on an ashen chair. "There is so much in this world you could discover, so many creatures to find or fight, so much land, ruins and dungeons to explore. To stave off boredom… you start a war?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course," the man said. "What is more glorious than war?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question was serious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If everyone in that country thinks this way, this war may really go on for a little longer than the empire or Claire thinks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Okay. Here's the deal. I only kill that guard because he is a disgusting fucker and insulted me personally. I take all your slaves and you fuck off back to your country and never come back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man looked at her before he burst out laughing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You cannot be serious… oh… you are!" He laughed even louder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea waited for him to calm down. "So you're telling me there is no way you will retreat or stop this little play here?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our people were stolen. It. Will. Not. Stand," he said, glaring at her with unfounded confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People aren't property," Ilea whispered, making the man laugh again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are weak. The order of the world is si-" he couldn't finish the sentence for a lack of head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The guard started struggling against the restraints, one of the ashen limbs piercing his skull a moment later. His limp body slumped to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea sighed and looked around the tent. There were better options, she knew as much. Luis didn't seem like he was outright evil. He grew up in a system that promoted inequality, taught him that it was the way of life. And yet he restricted and endangered the lives of every slave in this camp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She chose the easy way out and killed him. Ilea wasn't a saint and she didn't judge herself as one. The man held slaves. He wouldn't be missed. Baralia wouldn't be missed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Vowed one appeared next to her in a crouch, bowing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're all here?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve appeared a moment later. He nodded, looking at the corpses and the ring on her finger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can I disable the enchantments?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I see. Well. I will remove them later. The rest of you. I want you to call a rally with everyone present in the camp. Only those who are not slaves. Or slaves forced to work for Baralia, like you were before," she said. "Right outside this tent, I suppose. There's plenty of space."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two men nodded and vanished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She spread a light mist of ash and healed all the slaves in the tent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few of them shivered or yelped when the healing suddenly flowed through them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are safe now," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Y… you killed him… what have you done?" one of the men said, carefully moving closer to Luis' corpse. He touched it, tears flowing from his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others didn't seem inclined to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You will have a choice later. To come with me to Riverwatch, get a new life there as free men and women, or to go your own way. I suggest the former. The wilderness isn't quite as forgiving," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She kept her ashen armor on now, her bone set right below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you," one of the women whispered. Not loud enough for the others to hear but for Ilea it was crystal clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea waited in silence for the next fifteen minutes, ash lazily moving around her form as she meditated. For a few minutes she had contemplated her decisions here. Luis had not budged and neither would she. It was inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She opened her eyes when one of the Vowed appeared in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Mage – lvl 184]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Spread out and protect the slaves. Kill anybody that tries to take them, harm them or use them as hostages," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man vanished again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wondered how the others understood the command. Perhaps it was part of the enchantment in their teeth. Or it was an inherent ability they shared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Either way, it was time to continue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She grabbed Luis' head and stepped out, ignoring the wails of the slave behind her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over a hundred people had gathered, all soldiers or adventurers, trained, armed and armored. Cooks, bards, administrators, scouts, rogues, and everything else a war camp required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the situation could escalate, she whistled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone froze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hostility and aggression turned to fear and apprehension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you attack me, you die. If you kill or attack the slaves. You die," she said and threw down the head of Luis. "If you continue to intervene here. You die."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Return to Baralia without causing any problems and then, stay there. Leave and live," she finished with the simple choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People started moving once more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than half immediately attacked, formations of them moving in on her and past those that were yet undecided. A few were cut down by their own, the word traitor thrown around here and there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea just stepped forward, to create some distance between herself and the command tent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone that rushed at her was ripped apart by fast moving ashen limbs. Some of them dodged or blocked a hit but every single one of them died. Not a single one of them was above level two hundred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their magic impacted her ash, her sphere making sure everything found its target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Keep them focused on me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She saw a few of them going for the slaves or fleeing. The former were cut down by the Vowed. The rest she didn't care about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashen spears formed and skewered the mages and rangers who attacked from a distance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It should be obvious by now that their efforts were in vain. And still dozens of them attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea didn't mind. They had made their choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pitiful display. Only a third had fled, the only ones remaining either dying or still frozen, undecided and soiling themselves. A few were crying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How very unpleasant," she said with a sigh. "Why can't we just let each other live?" she asked as a few of her limbs cracked the barrier put up by the last remaining mage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His armor and body were ripped apart in the next moment, blood and guts slowly seeping onto the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She clapped a few times to get the attention of the last four standing people. A cook, warrior and two mages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their heart rate and location of excrement suggested not just fear but terror.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You heard me, lads. Go back to your home and your families. And stay there," she clapped and watched them finally move, running for their lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the son was an indication for the father, they would have another visit on their hands shortly. &lt;em&gt;Think not of what was lost, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and looked at the slaves, shivering in their basic clothes, hope in their eyes as they tried to see her.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">499400</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 12:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 460 Problematic Conflicts</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/498584</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 460 Problematic Conflicts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea landed in Riverwatch without being confronted by a squad of guards or arrows and artillery flying her way. To her disappointment really. If she could enter this easily, others could too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Then again, I can't truly expect Ravenhall's level of defense. They neither have the capability nor a recent mass genocide by demons to remind them of the necessity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wore her leather armor and casual clothes, her ashen armor receding to her back, just below her neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A passing guard squad supplied her with directions towards the main governmental buildings. A quick show of her Shadow badge convinced them that she isn't a dangerous vagabond traveling their streets by night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea tried to use her Huntress skill as much as possible, focusing on Alistair as her target. A few more skills would allow her to mark more people, something she definitely wanted. It had been difficult to level the skill during combat, meaning opportunities like this were very much welcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few stores were open still and the occasional worker or adventurer passed her in the streets but the difference between day and night was striking in this city. Compared to Ravenhall where many, especially in the inner two circles or Viscera, went about their business no matter what time of day. Some stores were even closed while the suns were out, knowing business would be better when the higher level people shopped at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mostly inns and pubs were still active. The suns had set but it likely wasn't past midnight quite yet. As spring rolled in, the nights would grow shorter too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her skill informed her of a trace of mana. Instinctively, she knew it was her target. Alistair. &lt;em&gt;Don't remember him ever using a skill &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;in front of me. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Just his aura was enough? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Or &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;can I &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;just feel &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;the mana of everyone I've ever met &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;with &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;this?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She focused on the Ascended and his magic, not picking up a single thing in her surroundings. A comforting thought. To be able to know at the very least, if her enemy walked amongst humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea hoped her assumption was correct and the being heavily disliked these mana starved areas, being of another species and all. One that might have started at a higher level too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She found Alistair in the city hall, where she had met him before. The same office even.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She mused on how easy it would be to assassinate the man as one of his guards checked her badge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The request went out earlier today. How come you are already here?" the woman asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea spread her wings behind herself and flapped them once, a gust of wind moving away in both directions of the corridor. The sound of a violently shutting window cemented her argument.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lilith," the other guard murmured, eyes wide open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It's spreading far and wide. Maybe for once the name actually helps, &lt;/em&gt;she thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman knocked on the door, entering upon confirmation. "A Shadow is here to see you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alistair appeared close to the door and opened it wide. "Ilea. It is marvelous to see you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man had bags under his eyes, moving a hand through his disheveled hair as he looked at her. "Well, let her in. I know her."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The guards nodded and stood aside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good to see you too, Alistair. I take it you haven't been as well as when I saw you last?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She formed an ashen chair and watched him teleport to his own, slumping down as the doors to the room closed, an enchantment's effect activating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It has been… turbulent. Are you here just by chance or because of our request for assistance?" he asked, unsure but hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Claire sent me, I'm here to help," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sighed and got a bottle from one of his drawers, pouring a glass and glancing at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm fine, thanks," she said and instead summoned a bottle of ale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am… relieved that you are here. And I won't be wasting your time with idle talk," he downed his glass in a single motion and continued without pause. "The contract with Ravenhall was a success. Many higher ups in Riverwatch welcomed the security it should provide. Doubts of course were present too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"More came up when operations to save ex slaves from Baralia to incorporate into our city were launched. Quite successfully if I may say so myself. The financial and logistical support from your side was an immense help of course. Many ex slaves have already been employed by shops, smithies, and even the guard."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea took a sip. "What's the problem then? Angering Baralia? I thought everyone is pretty much working together to destroy them at this point."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Exactly. Which means everyone wants a piece of their land and the riches included within. However the doubts and complaints were of a less materialistic nature. Some few individuals simply do not see the worth of slaves and the fact that we set them free. Sadly, their influence and other capabilities far outweigh the impact of such arrogant thinking."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cut to the chase, governor. I plan to leave again tomorrow," Ilea said and downed her ale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man blinked and nodded. "Of course. Apologies… where were we… yes, the operations. You see, Nipha has made offers and requests lately. Their interest in Riverwatch and the western cities has been known for long but the crises in the past years has made them more bold."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It seems they haven't intervened in the passing of a rather large group of slavers and lords from Baralia, trying to reclaim the slaves we took from them. They are blocking roads, rile up monsters and outright attack caravans and soldiers, heavily reducing our effectiveness."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We could intervene but the resources we spent on this already make it difficult for me to convince all parties. It is paramount that I keep this city and its most important leaders unified. Nipha and potentially other players are ready to use any opportunity they can get."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea crossed her arms and slumped in her chair. "Why the fuck do they care? Isn't Baralia under attack? Why come here and get some slaves back?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The lords and ladies of Baralia are loyal only to themselves. Pillaging rescue operations in a foreign forest suits them more than rallying their troops in their king's defense," Alistair said. "It is an easy target and they do hate to be wronged. I hear that all slaves of an owner are punished if a single one escapes or is taken. Now that isn't possible because we take everyone from estates and farms. The only way to punish them thus, is to find them and take them back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are they really that bored? With all the things you could do in your life? You hunt down escaped slaves to punish them," she said and shook her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To them those people are property. They grew up learning that and believing that such is the way of life. Even now, I doubt many citizens of Baralia truly know in what kind of danger they are. Now they are here, to get back what belongs to them. In their minds, they are righteous," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That doesn't make it better. Just sad too," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man shrugged and poured himself another drink. "War always is."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Humans," Ilea said and rolled her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We do have a certain charm," Alistair said. "Now I wouldn't have asked if it wasn't a precarious situation. For any other Shadow I would have offered twice the normal rate. For you however, I have something else in mind. If you finish the job, it may be possible to finally convince the others."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What are you talking about?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You will see. It is suffice to say that the worth of the reward will vastly exceed the normal rate. I owe much to you, Ilea. And so does Riverwatch. And I will do my utmost for us to be kept in your good graces. Riverwatch will stand with you and Ravenhall and it pains me that already we are forced to ask for your help," he said and stood up, bowing to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't bow. Wow, I'm really not cut out for this. Sure, I will help you. Just get as many slaves out of there as you can. I'd prefer if they worked in stores owned by me," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course. I have a squad of highly specialized adventurers prepared to come out with you, as soon as you are ready," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What are their levels?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Close to two hundred but their abilities are quite extraordinary," Alistair said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I would rather work alone, wouldn't want any of them getting killed. My tracking spell needs a few levels too. How hard do you think it would be to find them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are many. They occupy the area right outside Nipha borders," he said and took out a map, showing her the location. "It will be simple to find them. However it wont be easy to avoid open battle without covert experts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why would I avoid open battle?" Ilea asked and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will leave it to you then. Do not overextend yourself," he said and lifted the glass to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wasn't sure if she could trust the man fully. He was a governor after all and as everyone with power, they were playing their little games. She was just a piece on his board as she was a piece on Claire's board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps more a wildcard than anything else, making them adapt policies through sheer brute force and wealth. Claire owed her but more importantly, she was a dear friend. The same thing could not be said about Alistair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The owing part, yes. But she didn't trust him quite yet. Alice had used her and there was a high chance that he would try to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe everything he said was true but Ilea wouldn't just slaughter a bunch of people on the word of one man. She would ask them herself and find out why they were here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Alistair had been honest, that would benefit their future relationship. She hoped the man took her for what she was and not someone to manipulate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Glad I'm not a fucking &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;governor, &lt;/em&gt;she thought as she landed twenty minutes of flying later. A river flowing nearby let her orient herself. The area Alistair had marked was quite extensive, suggesting either a very mobile force or large numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Making people understand that slaves are just as much human beings deserving the same rights as everyone else seems exhaustive.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sentinel Huntress and her sphere picked up every movement, scent and living being around her as she strolled through the forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea spotted a few wolves that promptly sprinted away upon sensing her. One nimble bear like creature climbed up a tree as if its life depended on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is it the aura? &lt;/em&gt;Ilea wondered. She turned it off. &lt;em&gt;Deviant of Humanity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another pack of wolves avoided her but didn't outright run for their lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She found tracks and magic residue, following the confusing trail until she glimpsed dull torchlight in the distance. Still hundreds of meters away but with her eyes it could have just as well been next to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I have special eyes, don't I?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She giggled to herself, noticing movement within her sphere. &lt;em&gt;Oh? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Already found? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maybe &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;he was right &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;and I should have &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;taken &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;that covert squad with me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Huntress reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 4'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Niceee," she said out loud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person stalking her stayed at a safe distance, shrouded in something that obscured them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eve my dear, you would be disappointed, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and vanished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her hands rushed out and grabbed, finding purchase in thin air before she felt an attack coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Useless.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blade scraped against her armor, a poisoned throwing knife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Stop it or I will snap you like a twig," she whispered and put Monster Hunter into the mix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her captive calmed, the air shifting before a man in dark brown robes appeared, his face covered by a steel mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Rogue – lvl 191]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea removed the mask which revealed a man in his thirties, various scars showing on his clean shaven face. He was bald too and didn't have a tongue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Great. The silent assassins. How fucking original," she said and rolled her eyes. "Are you a slave?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man didn't reply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm… what's that?" she said as her healing mana examined his body. Her sphere helped too. "Interesting. What do they do? The things in your teeth?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes opened wide and he shook his head slowly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What? Tell me or I'll just rip them out, your choice," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man made a noise but talking proved difficult without one of the relevant organs. The injury seemed too far back to be healed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you want to gesture?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Okay, good. Don't do anything stupid," she said and grappled him with several ashen limbs, letting go of his arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man made two fists and then opened them quickly, moving his hands away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Explosion?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Same happens if I remove them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He nodded again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How powerful are we talking?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you trust me?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you want to be free?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't reply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're with Baralia, right?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man didn't deny.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ah what the hell, if he dies I'll have taken out one of their assassins.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She filled his mouth with ash and hardened it to keep it open. "Now this is going to hurt, my dear. I suggest you think of something pleasant."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Didn't think I'd become a dentist too, life leads you on interesting paths, &lt;/em&gt;she thought as her healing mana flowed into him, two ashen limbs wrapped around the relevant teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"On three, one, two-" she ripped the teeth out with blinding speed, the explosions muffled by ash, unable to penetrate the encased space. Ilea was sure her Blast Resistance had helped tremendously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Catching an explosion within a closed off space. Pretty ridiculous if you ask me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wounds were already healed, new teeth grown to replace the old ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hah, now you're free. Bet you didn't expect that when you woke up today. Now I want some information or I will have to kill you," she said, watching the man grasp at his jaw with both hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes were wide open as he looked at her and the ash holding him in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sound had been muffled enough not to reach the distant light but Ilea thought it possible that someone could show up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked back and once more touched his jaw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She felt he was in great distress but not because of her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Scared your master will kill you because the implants are gone?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He focused on her, tears forming in his eyes as he nodded. He made a pained noise. A request perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Look. As far as I see, you have two options here," she flowed healing magic into the man. "One, you go back to your master, who surely trained and groomed you since you were a wee child. They would likely kill or punish you for taking out the implants, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked around frantically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Option two. You cooperate with me, I kill your master and set you free, as well as any other slave that is in that camp," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man locked eyes with her as his breathing slowed down. The turmoil was clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't have all night. Do you want to live or do you want to die?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He closed his eyes, tears flowing down his cheeks before he nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What, die?" she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Live. Good choice. I would have chosen that too. It's fun. Living. And now you're free. As soon as you told me what I want to know."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He gestured to his mouth and the obvious lack of tongue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tell in a figurative sense. You can write I assume?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Great! Fantastic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It soon became clear that the extent of the enemy forces had been underestimated. Not just by Ilea but by Alistair as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The camp ahead was just the long reaching arm of one Lord Harken, the noble in charge of Wynehold, which was the southwestern most large city in Baralia. They came to retake the slaves stolen from their lands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Seems like Alistair didn't lie. So much for not getting massively involved in this war. Eh, we're freeing slaves, aren't we?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She sat with the freed man, his resolve broken as he wrote down the answers to all her questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As if he's just fulfilling an order.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How old were you when your training started?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked up and showed four fingers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Four years old. Do you even understand the concept of freedom?" Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't reply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No master. Nobody to take orders from. You decide on your own," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He listened but it looked like he didn't hear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man wrote something and pointed at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Master&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ah fuck. That's exactly what I didn't want to happen, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought and sighed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will figure that out later. For now, we'll need a plan to free all the slaves in that camp and disrupt these operations. Can you sketch me a layout and tell me how many people there are, if they're slaves or not and how powerful they are?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea stopped him for a moment and looked into his eyes. "What's your name by the way?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pale man just shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course you don't have one. I'm Lilith. Nice to meet you," she said. He might still escape or betray her, in which case she preferred him use that name instead of her real one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He mouthed the word and continued the sketch.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">498584</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 15:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 459 Request</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/497117</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 459 Request&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The testing with Iana and Christopher wasn't quite as successful as on the previous day. Something definitely worked but other than chunks and pieces of Ilea, nothing else was teleported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea's lessons in the afternoon went well on the other hand, nearly all students participating in the torturous endeavor. She wondered why Lorelai watched her with such an intense glare. Ilea decided it had to be just a difficult day. Or she overcame her fear and pain by channeling her anger at Ilea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her bow training didn't amount to a level but she did receive one for her Sage of Torment skill, bringing it to level three.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea went to meet with Claire afterwards, finding the woman watching Cless draw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Kyrian again, flying in mid air with a large number of blades floating around him, all aimed at a creature shrouded in a mist of colors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're back, how was your day?" Claire stated, not taking her eyes from the canvas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The girl was utterly consumed, not reacting in the slightest to the newcomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Classes went well. Training too. Did she draw me earlier? I got a level in Divination Resistance."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She did. Several times. I am not sure if what you're doing is the best idea, Ilea. I've seen it before but the still painting of dozens of spells flying at your unprotected body made me worry a little," Claire said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is Kyrian fighting a mist monster or what is that?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It means Cless can't see it, whatever it may be. It happened with you too from time to time. Some creatures have a higher resistance to divination magic," the woman explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I see. Let me know if you find out anything about his location. As to your question, it's perfectly safe. I doubt anybody in this city can kill me at this point," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I didn't say it was unsafe. I said it might not be a good idea. Everyone who uses their magic against you will feel inadequate. I can't have half the city's adventurers quit because you broke their self confidence," Claire explained and finally looked at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea followed her to the table, enchantments activating that separated Cless from their conversation. Not that the girl would listen right now anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"With all due respect," Ilea started and formed an ashen chair as she sat down. It warmed up immediately. "If anything, I'm providing them with easy skill levels. If someone quits because they can't injure a powerful Shadow, they are not adventurers in the first place. Plus, there are a few Shadows present now too. It might help to see that their spells are just as ineffective."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire sighed and summoned a document. "I hope you're right. I know you don't care much but every adventurer is needed, for a variety of jobs. The economy and growth of this city would be impacted if a lot of them quit suddenly."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most come back for more. I believe you are overthinking this," Ilea said and nodded to the piece of paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Maybe. I didn't mean to have you stop by the way. I just thought to tell you," she said and turned the document around. "I received this a few hours ago. From the team manning the communication unit provided by Iana and Christopher. A request for assistance," Claire said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Riverwatch?" Ilea asked. It was the only place outfitted with such a device outside of Ravenhall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire nodded. "Yes. I assume we will get further information in the coming days from a courier. Anybody that could make the trip in less time would be too valuable to send."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Want me to go check it out?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought about asking, yes. A job for the Shadows would take a little more information and who knows who would take it. Our alliance is new and you already know Alistair. However, I know you are busy. Both with your classes and personal training," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm. You are right with both. People know me now though. I can take a few days off if necessary, they will be back. The students might welcome a bit more time to breathe too. You will receive the information from Riverwatch anyway. If it's too big for me or if it takes too long, I'll leave it to a Shadow team," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire closed her eyes and visibly relaxed. "Thank you. I really really appreciate this, Ilea. And I apologize that I'm bothering you with this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't worry. There are a few people in Riverwatch I'd like to survive. And I know the situation isn't exactly stable with the war and everything. Plus, there are some things I wanted to get done in the area. Guess I'll just move that a little forward in my schedule," she said. "Should I just go talk to Alistair?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I told you everything I know. The device isn't very specific. Yet," Claire said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will go immediately then. No dancing lesson today, I suppose," Ilea said and got up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I suppose not. I will be here for your next one. Trian and the arena will be informed that you won't be participating tomorrow. Don't get yourself killed out there. And please, don't start any wars," the administrator said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll try not to," Ilea replied and vanished out of the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With my charged flight speed, it shouldn't take more than a few hours to get there, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and made a stop at the Sentinel headquarters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iana and Christopher were still working. &lt;em&gt;Might be good for them too. Another perspective.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good evening you two," she greeted them with a wave, having been let in to their sanctuary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey Ilea. Didn't expect you back until tomorrow? Didn't you plan to explore dungeons?" Iana asked. She scratched her head, still holding a pen in her hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christopher didn't even get up from his desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I did. A request from Claire and through extension Riverwatch has come up however. I will fly there right now and thought you two should come with me," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What… Riverwatch?" Iana said and looked around. "It takes months to get there… I don't have my things ready and we can't stop our research for so long!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It does seem like a long trip. Even though you fly quite quickly," Christopher said as he got involved as well. "Why do you want us there anyway?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea crossed her arms. "Calm down you two. It shouldn't take more than a few hours. My wings aren't the same anymore. Hmm, I do hope you survive that speed. How does your Vitality look?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iana was murmuring something to herself before she spoke up. "Ilea, focus. Why this trip? Why now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Because back in the Azarinth temple, where I got my class, there was a device that teleported me down into the basement. That and a fountain that made the water inside it have healing powers. I want you two to have a look. Plus, if Weavy is around, you can talk to him about demonic runes. Both might be helpful," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I wonder if Maro is already back too. He probably fucked out of the north as fast as possible.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The demon you mentioned. That would be quite helpful. Iana, I think we should go," Christopher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes but a few hours? How fast exactly are you?" Iana asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Quite," Ilea said. "You have food, clothes and whatever else you need in your storage ring?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I do, but-" Iana said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea nodded and clapped. "Then we are ready to go. Come on, grab what you need for your research as well as a bunch of weapons and armor."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Will we have to fight?" Christopher said, frantically glancing at the two of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't plan on it but who the fuck knows what's waiting out there. Might as well be prepared," Ilea said. "If you need anything, we can quickly check some of the shops."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, no. We are quite prepared. My father made sure of that," Iana said as a set of dark blue steel armor appeared on her body, the enchantress' look changing to that of a fearsome warrior. Various enchantments glowed on the gear. A rapier was fastened to her belt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The armor was obviously fitted and made just for her, reminding of Ilea's own bone armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You look good in that," Ilea said and nodded to the weapon. "Are you trained?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The girl winked, only her eyes visible. "I can hold my own. Not against a Shadow but enchanters have their own tricks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't have tricks," Christopher said with a sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you mean? What about the trap enchantments you made and the explosives? You finished the implosion device too! Just activate and throw them," Iana said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah yes… I suppose I could do that. I will get them, give me a few minutes," he said and walked to one of the many storage units built into the walls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Check C18, I made something for you. Just in case," Iana said with a giggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have you been getting a little closer than just work acquaintances? Hmm? &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought and glared at the girl with a smile on her face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She didn't look her way, instead focused on the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;He may be a little old for her but if anyone is looking for someone more mature than their age, it's Iana.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh wow… this is… quite useful!" the man exclaimed and looked through the pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will get dressed immediately!" he said and started changing where he stood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not very modest, are we?" Ilea asked, not loud enough for him to hear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iana's face turned a little red, her eyes still focused on the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was done a few minutes later, joining them again with a smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea had to admit that his face was easy on the eyes. Perhaps not the most striking appearance but it might not be fair to compare him to level two hundred mages and warriors, enough money, time and power on their hands to get all they could out of their appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to when she had found him, in Arthur Redleaf's &lt;em&gt;employ, &lt;/em&gt;the man now positively glowed. He looked a few decades younger too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His gear consisted of belts and pockets, strapped onto an intricate light weight armor with bits of steel and leather. Masterful work but what else was to be expected from Balduur and Iana. The most striking part was that all the pockets, straps and belts were part of the clothes. They didn't have to be fastened individually. Otherwise they might have very well left on the next morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think with this I can distract a few monsters. Or set up some barriers at least," he said, gingerly opening and closing some of the compartments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good. Ready then?" Ilea asked. She wasn't in a hurry because of the request itself but perhaps there was a chance that she could be back for her morning session after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two looked at each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess so," Iana said. "You will carry us?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, I will," Ilea said as her ashen armor formed, limbs moving out to grab the two. "I don't want you to die so I'll have to hold on pretty tightly. My healing should offset any damage you would take but I will have an eye on the both of you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Going off your estimation, we would pass out and die after less than a minute of flight," Christopher said as he looked at the ashen limbs, nodding to one of them as if it was a living creature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will test," Ilea said. "If you can't take it, I'll go alone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea's normal flight speed without charged wings was already quite taxing on the two. She was sure they would pass out after a few minutes without her healing and the ashen cocoons she had formed around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The test with charged wings was successful too, both of her passengers passing out after a while, their vitals however stable thanks to her continued healing. &lt;em&gt;Delivering &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;two &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;enchanters &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Riverwatch, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;now &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;where &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;was that &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;large fucking mountain?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just under three hours later, the dark winged healer reached the intended destination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The suns hadn't gone down quite yet and visibility was good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea spotted the town from a high distance, just a speck to her enhanced eyes but it was unmistakable, sitting next to the mountain Karth and the river flowing past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The town was neither on fire nor besieged as far as she could tell. Enough for her to swerve away and towards the Azarinth temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea slowed down considerably, going low and into the forest to avoid any interested eyes. Her sphere, blink and third tier wings made the dangerous journey quite simple. Not that trees would stand against her flying form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be moot however, if she avoided tracks on the ground but left behind dozens of felled trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She did spot a few of them on the way, some likely not downed more than a few months ago but that didn't change her opinion. The temple was close enough and they soon reached it without interruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Here we are," she said and checked the area. There were tracks and she saw magic residue. Nothing that would suggest humans or other bipedal creatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea laid both of her travel companions onto the grass and pushed a little more healing into them than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both shot up immediately, eyes wide open as they reoriented themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What! What happened? Where are we!?" Iana said out loud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How long have we been out?" Christopher asked as he cupped his face with both hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A little over three hours, I think," Ilea said. "We are near Riverwatch. Far enough away not to attract any attention. And this," she gestured behind them. "Is an Azarinth temple. Past its glory."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is where you got your class," Iana said, already over the experience. Likely due to the constant healing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Three hours?" Christopher said as he scrambled to find a booklet in one of his pockets. "That is… incredible… truly. If people can move at that speed, a teleportation device becomes obsolete in the first place… storage devices would solve the wind resistance issue and the logistics of transferring large amounts of goods," he murmured to himself as he took some notes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The world is bigger than the human plains, Christopher. And I doubt many will be able to fly this fast, nor do I want to become a delivery girl," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course. I am simply looking at the possibilities. Well, the enchantments you wanted to show us, they are here?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes. Follow me," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Marvelous… it's healing isn't it?" Christopher asked and looked to Iana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She nodded, moving her hand over the inscriptions, barely visible without any perception skills. "It invades whoever gets too close, thus activating the enchantment without a previous charge. Ilea, do you happen to have a skill to steal mana from someone?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Part of one skill does that, yeah," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But nobody mentioned gaining a drain resistance I assume? It's a healing skill," Iana correctly assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea just nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can you recreate it?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not sure yet. The chance is low however, because neither of us can channel the type of mana necessary. The principles however, might be useful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Perfect. The second thing is in the room this teleportation thing leads you to. A fountain that produces healing water," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will look at it as soon as we're done here," Iana said, focused on the runes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How long do you think you will need?" Ilea asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The enchantress looked up. "As long as we can."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea nodded. "I don't think there should be anything too dangerous around. For your level at least. If something does show up, just teleport below using the enchantment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You won't stay?" Christopher asked, glancing around the dark temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have other plans. I would leave a mark but I'm out currently. I'm sure you'll be safe. I will sweep the area to check if anything is around but I survived here for weeks on end, below level one hundred," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's alright. We aren't defenseless, Ilea," the enchantress said, giving her a thumbs up with an armored hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You don't look defenseless. But if a Specter or Praetorian showed up, you wouldn't stand a chance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good. I will check in on you again. You have food and water as well as provisions?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iana nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Okay. If I'm not back in three days, assume I'm dead. Go back to Ravenhall and continue your work," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What exactly are you planning?" Iana asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I hope you aren't getting in too much danger," Christopher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your funding will be guaranteed anyway, don't worry," Ilea said. "I plan to meet an old acquaintance and help out an independent city with an unspecified problem. Just don't want you two to be stranded in case something finally manages to put me down… though it is more and more unlikely."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will figure it out, don't worry about us. I welcome the opportunity to be in the wild, studying ancient runes without my overprotective father looking over me," Iana said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christopher gulped. "I had hoped it was finally over."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't worry, we don't plan to face Taleen. And if it becomes too dangerous, we will leave," Iana said, patting his back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well, knock yourselves out. Ah, if any Bluemoon Grass has grown in the meantime, harvest but don't eat it. It hurts and there's a high chance it can kill you. Well, maybe not you at this level but I would still be careful. Stay safe and I'll see you later," Ilea said and waved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You too. Have fun on your adventure," Iana said, beaming with joy in her eyes. The dangerous looking armor gave the farewell an odd feel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Have… fun," Christopher said, shaking his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea chuckled at the sight and vanished, appearing on top of her temple. A single ashen limb moved out and marked a few new discoveries on her small map next to the compass rose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It felt a little weird, to stand here now, where she had started in this weird and fantastical world. &lt;em&gt;If the wolves or drakes had gotten me, it would have ended &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;somewhere &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;here, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;in the woods. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;But it didn't.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her wings spread as an armor made of ash covered her. The fear and uncertainty that vividly came to her mind as memories of her first months came back to her were no more. All was replaced by confidence in her magic and abilities. The only feeling she shared with her past self that had struggled to survive in this temple, was excitement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;f only she &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;had known&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;that in a year or two, she would be &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;flying through the skies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">497117</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 12:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 458 Reputation</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/496357</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 458 Reputation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea watched the resolve and caution in the adventurer melt away in the face of money. &lt;em&gt;It's just too powerful a weapon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She still had four hundred and twenty four pieces of gold with her. A small price to pay for calming her conscience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea didn't care as much for Karheim. In part because the undead just seemed much less dangerous to her than the Specters did but mostly because she just didn't know anybody there. Checking in quickly would be enough. Worst came to worst, she was sure most would escape anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Specter on the other hand would just rip people apart. &lt;em&gt;No wonder we hide behind walls. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Even &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;low level Elves would have difficulties &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;with &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;those fuckers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a good thing after all that not every species living in this plane of existence had similar ambitions as humanity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Questions… I want you to answer a few questions if possible," Sophia said after she had regained her focus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will choose to answer but shoot," Ilea said. There was little reason not to share some knowledge with the mage. The lack of sharing in this world was a major factor why humanity struggled to gain more of a foothold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your name is Lilith, isn't it? You are the healer from Ravenhall?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Didn't you ask that before? Hmm, well I guess I didn't confirm it. Yes. That is a name I use. Started kind of as a joke but I suppose it stuck. It would be useful if I didn't share my actual name all the time," Ilea said and shrugged. She was just not cut out to be a cautious politician or rogue. If her honesty and carelessness became a problem, she would deal with it the way she dealt with most problems. On the fly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman nodded excitedly. "Your level is really at three forty?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I won't confirm nor deny. But I have passed the three hundred threshold."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is huuge! Wow… you must be one of what? A thousand? A hundred?" Sophia said and giggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tell me, why did you choose us? Was it because we were a low level team? Or because of one of our classes?" the woman asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea tilted her head to the side. "I just happened upon you. Been looking for the Caverns of Rot and you knew where it was."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But you could have just asked for directions!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You still think this is some evil plot?" Ilea said and sighed. "You offered me food. And I thought it would be fun to join a normal adventuring team for a change. I've mostly been solo and I doubt a Shadow team is the usual experience."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So you are a Shadow too. Yes… okay. Okay, I will risk it. I accept. Do you need to carve it into my chest or something?" the mage asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What, no. I just push mana into you," Ilea said. &lt;em&gt;Calling it rape. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;That's such bullshit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, I see. Well, I'm ready," the woman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why is she blushing? &lt;/em&gt;Ilea asked herself as she set the mark. &lt;em&gt;Could it be?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She smiled but didn't comment on it. Sophia was obviously dealing with last night's experience. &lt;em&gt;Maybe some other time, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought and stepped away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The adventurer looked at the mark on the back of her hand and smiled. "Did I just sign over my soul?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, my dear. You didn't. If things here go south, call for me. It should be an instinctual thing," she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"See you around," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"See you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flight back took a little longer, Ilea making a beeline for Karheim. The small village seemed entirely the same, people drinking in the inn's common room, some entirely passed out and others sleeping in the rooms above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No incident then. Good.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her breakfast consumed, she strolled to the arena, finding even more people than on the day before. Any arguments as to who would be permitted to participate were silenced as soon as she was there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone clad in ash and two question marks above their head were a little more convincing than the meek handler.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He apologized for the delay, despite her reassurance that everything was alright.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea was just glad someone else managed the screening, payment and reservations. Today they had an even larger hall. One obviously used for a little more destructive testing and training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She spotted a few people in entirely black gear, their levels in the two hundreds. Not people she remembered but according to their body language and the looks they gave her, they at least knew about her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Welcome all. I'm sure you are informed already. Start whenever you want to. Jerry will evaluate your participation and you will be paid accordingly. His word is gospel and if you start shit with him or argue too much you won't receive anything at all. If you go further, I will personally fly you up above the clouds and then drop you. Understood?" she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three Shadows nodded immediately. Everyone who had participated previously did too. Some few looked around with a confused expression, others even chuckling at the declaration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea didn't know if it was pride or just a darker sense of humor. What she knew was that if they came back again tomorrow, they would nod just like the others. &lt;em&gt;Yes, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;learn &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;grow, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;my &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;resistance providers!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She needed six more levels for another third tier point. Blood would soon reach the end of the second tier but she still needed Void. Veteran was close as well. Which left Monster Hunter. Four points plus one for emergencies. Which already left her with one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I should probably spend them all before advancing. Ten seems like a good number for a potential achievement.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the Shadows vanished and appeared closer to her before anyone had started to whirl spells at her. He wore light armor, intricate carvings covering large sections of it in a language unknown to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Mage – lvl 226]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I would like to start, if you would allow?" she said in a gravely voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A woman? Interesting. Didn't look like one.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure. If you think your spells too powerful, step forward," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other Shadows as well as a few of the others came closer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first woman was the highest level person present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She demonstrated her magic on the ground, a chunk of stone vanishing in an instant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the people present recoiled and started murmuring amongst themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Void. You, my dear. Are very welcome," Ilea said with a wide grin. She walked close to the woman who remained motionless. "I hope you don't have plans for the coming weeks. My friend there will pay you handsomely for your continued participation," she whispered the second part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman ever so slightly turned towards her. "I am sure we will find an agreement."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good. Very nice to meet you. Don't go for the head and we are golden," she said and looked to the next person in line. Another Shadow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wore light armor too, mostly treated hides. Very little metal. A hood covered her head and a scarf most of her face. Dark orange eyes stood out from the otherwise dark aesthetics of the level two fifteen mage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman lifted a hand and black smoke formed above. It looked similar to Ilea's ash but much less dense and defined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was quite literally just smoke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Interesting. That would be a new one," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is what I had hoped," the woman said and giggled, the joy not reaching her eyes. A crossbow appeared in her hands, the heavy tool easily moved by the woman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will use this too, for the price of the bolts," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Jerry, can you handle that?" Ilea asked and nodded towards the man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course," he replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good. What do you have?" Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Poison, explosive, fire, lightning, paralyzing and a few more that I will not declare," the Shadow said and winked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Perfect. Use everything but explosive. Ah and… feel free to throw in some of those mystery bolts. Would be interesting to see," Ilea suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm… I just might do that. Oh… before we continue, I usually use my smoke to choke and disorient my prey. The attacks are less direct," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even better. I have Oxygen Repository, so feel free to make me gasp for air," Ilea said and winked back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oooh, I like this," the woman whispered to herself and leaned in. "Do you perhaps have a spot free in your team?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A new Shadow? Or she wants to switch. &lt;/em&gt;"Not at the moment. But I will let you know when something comes up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea nodded to the last Shadow. A level two hundred and four warrior. He was tall, over two meters. His gear had to weighas much or more than the man below. A large sword was strapped to his back, the form reminding her of a katana but its size was closer to a greatsword. Two meters or more in length as well and currently sheathed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His armor was made of black steel, dents and scratches telling a story of their own. Four varied horns adorned his helmet, only two sockets showing his eyes behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others were all below two hundred and none of their skills were anything new to her. She suspected that the majority of them simply overestimated their own abilities or they didn't believe the stories from those who had participated in the course already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it was the Shadow's turn, he looked to the waiting group and spoke. "Cover your ears."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then focused on Ilea, took a deep breath and shouted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She felt the power reverberate through the hall, washing over her as if it was a wall of stone that hit her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sound magic… that's good. I'm pretty low there. And something else, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and tried to place it. &lt;em&gt;Ah, yes. I can even tell he's not particularly good at it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mind magic too. Interesting combination. I suspect you confuse your enemies and cleave them apart with that thing there?" she assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few of the people present had gone to their knees, some even bleeding from their ears. The Shadows didn't react.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You noticed it. As expected from someone with your reputation," he said, surely sporting a smile below his helmet. The magic he exuded meddled with her sphere, if only a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can you focus it more? I don't want people to get hurt," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you stand farther away, yes. I will use another angle. Someone can put up a wall of stone or ice. That should do it," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Earth mages," Ilea said and looked at a few she knew to be practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of them nodded and raised a wall in mere moments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"May I ask something?" the Shadow said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course," Ilea replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I sense the presence of your mind. The only time I felt something similar was when I met a powerful mind magic wielding creature ten years past. A part of the attack was even thrown back at me," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm… that is a little secret of my own. Maybe you'll find out more if you continue to join," Ilea said and winked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Resistance, &lt;/em&gt;she sent the thought to him and smiled when she saw his eyes widen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You…," he stammered but focused again quickly. A laugh resounded as he walked to his spot. "I expected much and it still wasn't enough."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait until you see her just stand there," one of them said, shaking his head as he avoided looking directly at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As if that would protect you, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought with a grin. "Well, that settles it. Shadows, please start with low power attacks. We will find an effective system."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;____________________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lorelai frowned when she reached the large table, eyeing the corpse laid out on top of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sidney had asked for someone to show what they had learned about anatomy in the previous week. On a real body. With a dagger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What is it?" the teacher asked. "I can give you a sword or axe if you prefer it. Just don't make a mess."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's not it," she said and looked at the body again. The hips, modest chest, the skin color and most importantly the muscle. &lt;em&gt;Beheaded.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry to ask but… where did you get that body?" she whispered to the teacher next to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman leaned closer and smiled. "That is classified. If you don't want to do it, I will ask someone else."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lorelai gulped. &lt;em&gt;No, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;no it can't be. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Or can it?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She took the dagger and glanced at the waiting class. Everyone attentive. Sidney had made sure of that since the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"First, the heart," she said and touched the cold skin with a hand. "Protected by the rib cage, there are a few places where a stab can reach it. If you can get under the arm," she said and pushed away the arm. She made a double take, squeezing the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It's like fucking steel, &lt;/em&gt;she noted and stabbed the dagger into the corpse's side. Or she tried to at least.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A little more effort and an awkward glance at the others was followed by the activation of a few skills. The blade only penetrated a few centimeters into the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sidney stepped over and grabbed her hand, ramming the blade inside. "Better?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lorelai only nodded dejectedly. "If you can manage to hit this spot, it can be deadly. However an injured or destroyed heart doesn't always lead to death. As you all have seen with Ilea."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We didn't actually see her lose her heart," one of the students said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She could probably lose her bloody head and live," Celeste said and chuckled, leading to a few laughs coming from the group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lorelai looked down at the body, her eyes moving to the neck as her eyes widened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's enough for now, I'll take it from here," Sidney said and patter her back. "Don't," she whispered in her ear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman nodded and stepped back to her seat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You look pale," Luke said. "Must be scary to stab a body."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Leave her alone," Nathan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's just like cutting meat, stab, stab, stab. I don't see the problem," Celeste said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It's her. She can regenerate her head.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her response to the realization was a giggle that turned into a full blown laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lorelai, please. If you can't control your laughter, calm down outside," Sidney said and continued the lesson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four hours passed in the blink of an eye. Ilea learned that choking inside smoke is worse than simply choking due to a lack of air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Void magic was still void magic but she could once more put into perspective just how insanely powerful that monster's magic really was. The Shadow was close to Maria's level of power. Ilea at least assumed as much. It was difficult to gauge with all the new power she had gotten since last training with the woman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything deactivated brought the Shadow close to what Maria did to her back then. And it was immensely helpful. Sadly, there weren't any competent blood mages involved but with Trian, Orthan and now the Specters, it was just a matter of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warrior mostly focused on sound magic, the mind aspect not quite powerful enough to raise her level, even with Avatar of Ash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rest of the group delivered however, close to a hundred and twenty people participating again today. Many were below level one hundred however but their contribution accumulated to quite a few skill levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She enjoyed some lunch while she waited for Iana and Christopher to adjust the enchantments again. Orthan was occupied with the corruption, quite a few books and tools now occupying his small work space within the Core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea checked through the notifications while she let them work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Oxygen Repository reaches lvl 3'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Oxygen Repository reaches lvl 4'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Crystal Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 4'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Crystal Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 5'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Dark Magic Resistance reaches lvl 18'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Divination Magic Resistance reaches lvl 2'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'One third tier General skill point awarded'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Earth Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 7'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Lightning Magic Resistance reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 2'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Mist Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 12'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sound Magic Resistance reaches lvl 5'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Sound Magic Resistance reaches lvl 8'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Void Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 12'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Void Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 13'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Water Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 7'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Water Resistance reaches 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 8'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'You have learned the General skill: Smoke Magic Resistance – lvl 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smoke Magic Resistance – lvl 1&lt;br/&gt;Usually the result of fire magic, this school focused on smoke itself. Wielded by a master, it can be just as deadly and destructive, if not more so. Knowing you, you probably just set fire inside a closed off cave and enjoyed the choking sensation. Slut.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' Smoke Magic Resistance reaches lvl 2'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' Smoke Magic Resistance reaches lvl 3'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;My subconscious thinks I really enjoy being choked. Might just be worth a try, maybe I AM into it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third tier point was welcome too. She quickly looked over the options and found she hadn't spent her twenty stat points yet either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They went straight into Intelligence. &lt;em&gt;I won't reach &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;a thousand Wisdom &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;until &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;three fifty anyway. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Might as well &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;make my &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;magic hit just a little harder.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea chose to finally advance her Wind Resistance with the new third tier point she had gotten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Wind Resistance reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 1'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wind Resistance – 3rd lvl 1&lt;br/&gt;The ever elusive magic of Wind can cut from any side. You have learned that it might've been a good idea to become a Void mage. This skill helps you resist the power of wind a little more.&lt;br/&gt;2nd stage: The mana flow inside of you has acclimated itself to the air around you, making you more aerodynamic.&lt;br/&gt;3rd stage: As you adjust to the flows of powerful wind magic and natural torrents, you find yourself often capable of using some of the power. Perhaps to propel yourself forward or stop abruptly. Wind mages might think you one of their own.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A nice potential surprise for the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Griffin, &lt;/em&gt;she thought with a smile.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">496357</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 15:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 457 Worthy Adversaries</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/495458</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 457 Worthy Adversaries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea was sure an hour or two had passed already. She would have to leave soon to join her resistance training. The only reason she even considered it was because the date was set. If she was too late or didn't show up, tomorrow there would be fewer people. Fewer potential skills and levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Specters however, would remain down here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wondered if they could kill her. If she remained motionless or trapped. Their destructive power, swords and magic against her regeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her body would regenerate as long as she had mana and the creatures continued to provide it. &lt;em&gt;Stick a &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;sword into my brain, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;maybe two. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Then I can't regenerate &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Secure the head &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;and just keep &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;going until &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;I have no more mana. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;If that isn't possible, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;you can't kill me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She went through the steps she herself would employ if her opponent had the same abilities as herself. Avoiding magic was a large part of potential success. Or magic as overwhelming as the Ascended had possessed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Teleporting me away might be an option too. I doubt meddling with my mind is an option, considering Sentinel Reconstruction and my resistance to that magic type. Another option would be to trap me indefinitely. Bind or seal me away.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She didn't like that thought at all. If she went out, she would want to go out and not be trapped for a thousand years. &lt;em&gt;Hmm… &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;well &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;with meditation &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;it might not even be that bad.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The attacks kept coming and by now she had a good idea about their speed, range and magic. Even if they manipulated their blades with the help of blood magic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her Heart of Cinder had been charging for a while now. Longer even than in the core of the Descent. She chose one of the Specters at random and blinked in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She dodged the blades and punched, all her limbs smashing into the creature. She ignored the blades cutting into her back and the blood magic ripping through her body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reversed healing mana flowed into the one Specter as her attacks kept going, culminating in the release of the stored energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blast sent back the blades still stuck in her body, burning through the skin and muscle of the Specter she had chosen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others moved in again as she smashed down one last time, fire surging from hundreds of thin orange red veins where Storm of Cinders had accumulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A ding resounded in her mind and she blinked out, just as three blades got close to her once more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three more blinks brought her out of the cavern and another five farther up through the dungeon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea stopped and turned around, crossing her arms as she steadied her breathing. Her mana was at half, despite the constant blood magic attacks. It would regenerate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If they follow, I'll have to kill them all.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She waited. A minute. Two. Five.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When twenty minutes had passed, her focus finally changed and she let out the air she was holding in her lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They wouldn't come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Defending their cave. Or they're the boss of the dungeon. Seems pretty ridiculous considering how weak the Abominations were before.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She checked the kill message and frowned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'You have defeated [Specter of Rot – lvl 621]'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Holy fuck they're strong for that level.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea slowly flew backwards through the tunnels, once more following the traces of ice and earth magic. She could clearly feel the mark moving farther and farther away. It remained stationary and quickly waned in intensity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;They're as tough as Praetorians with their shields but have faster regeneration. Plus their movements are multiple times as quick. What a find… what a night!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She flew back with the occasional twirl and bob, giggling through the dark tunnels like the madwoman some thought she was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Turns out the dungeons here are very much dangerous and interesting. If you just dig deep enough.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rest of her notifications didn't let down either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'The Azarinth Sentinel reaches lvl 347 – Five stat points awarded'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'The Azarinth Sentinel reaches lvl 348 – Five stat points awarded'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Kin of Ash reaches lvl 347 – Five stat points awarded'&lt;br/&gt;'ding' 'Kin of Ash reaches lvl 348 – Five stat points awarded'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ah fuck, can't kill another one or I'll reach three fifty.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wondered if she shouldn't just get it over with already. On the other hand, she could gain a few more achievements beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her skill advancements from the dangerous battle didn't let down either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Absolute Destruction reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 23'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Blink reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 21'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Sphere reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 14'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Core reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 24'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Azarinth Fighting reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 27'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Azarinth Perception reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 13'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Armor of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 29'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' '&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aspect&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; of Ash reaches &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'True Ash Creation reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 24'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Heart of Cinder reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 17'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Storm of Cinders reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 17'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Ash and Ember Unity reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 22'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Ashen Wings reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 15'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Eyes of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 8'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Avatar of Ash reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 21'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' '&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keeper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; of Ash reaches &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Deviant of Humanity reaches &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;lvl 2'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Meditation reaches 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl 4'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Monster Hunter reaches 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl 5'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Monster Hunter reaches 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Veteran reaches 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl 18'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Blood Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl 17'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Blood Magic Resistance reaches 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lvl 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Bone Magic Resistance reaches &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;lvl 5'&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Bone Magic Resistance reaches &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;lvl &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'You have learned the General skill: Rot Resistance – &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;lvl 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rot Resistance – lvl 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;W&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ith your regeneration and healing, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;it &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;was unlikely &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;that &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;such a resistance &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;would ever manifest. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;However you have found &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a powerful source of unnatural rot. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perhaps fueled by a curse &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;or magic. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Congratulations on yet another&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; painful &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;horrific &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;experience.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hmm… maybe just a few more exciting nights with my new Specter friends. I have a source now for levels, class skill levels and resistances.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea wondered if it even made sense to explore the other dungeons on her map. &lt;em&gt;For training purposes, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;I'll &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;have to. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Especially the ones close by.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wasn't just about her own resistances but about her students as well. They were progressing fast, even after a couple of days. She saw little reason for it to slow down considerably any time soon. Some combat experiences would help them get the right classes. Perhaps something a little less support oriented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She herself had only one true healing skill and it was easily enough to take care of herself and everyone around her. A full support healer with a second class to reinforce such effects could maybe heal half a town's worth of people in instants but that wasn't exactly needed most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question was also apparent of how to actually get someone to the required level. &lt;em&gt;Questions over questions. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Can't say I'm not living an exciting life &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;at least, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and grinned, her wings retracting as she reached the upper part of the dungeon and with it the exit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The suns weren't out yet but her flight would take some time as well. Not hours anymore, thanks to her third tier wings but enough to endanger her extended breakfast. Definitely her second breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ah, forgot about one small thing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia turned in her bed. The benefit of joining an otherwise male party was usually getting her own room. It wasn't always possible but the last two years were good on her purse and her team respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sean sometimes got a room on his own too, the other two didn't care much. Edgar needed very little sleep and Colt was often found passed out in the common room. Most inn keepers either couldn't physically move him or didn't care to risk it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tonight, she would have preferred some company. Even with the annoying comments from the brute. She had been liberal with her drink but her Poison Resistance was just as high as that of her team members. Contrary to Colt, she wasn't about to spend her last coin to keep herself inebriated. &lt;em&gt;Maybe I should have.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep had come but only for an hour or two. Not quite enough for her. A nightmare had woken her up. A healer reaching out her hand, their face suddenly turning into an Abomination before she was swallowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It had been a while since an experience had shaken her this much. &lt;em&gt;Half a year maybe? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;were&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;wolf, &lt;/em&gt;she thought and shuddered. It would take some time for her to recover fully. &lt;em&gt;It's &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;weird &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;really… &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;this was much worse &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;objectively &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;and yet, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;I seem to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;be able to handle it much better. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maybe I'm imagining things. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Or &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;I'&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ve &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;grown more &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;resistant to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She noticed her thoughts focusing back on the Abominations, their squeals. The ripped apart adventurers in that small cavern. Ilea getting slashed apart, coloring the ground and walls, the wet sound of bone hitting flesh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She sat up and rubbed her eyes. &lt;em&gt;What a fucking nightmare.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wasn't worth some levels. Not in a thousand years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A knock on her window made her yelp out and teleport to the opposite wall. Her heart rate accelerated but her breathing calmed. Ice formed around her as she prepared her spells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The faint light of dawn shined into the room, barely illuminating a floating form outside her window. Blue eyes and black wings. A glowing smile and a wave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She rubbed her eyes and relaxed. &lt;em&gt;I'm still dreaming.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hello Sophia," a voice said, the presence now closer to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No need to be afraid. Come on, it's me. Ilea. Open your eyes," the voice said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something warm and relaxing entered her body and she yelped a little at the sudden sensation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She opened her eyes and saw that the healer was here. Here in her room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Out," she found herself saying, her voice steady and her eyes focused on the woman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea nodded and vanished, appearing once more outside the window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What the fuck is this supposed to be?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She shook her head and walked to the window. &lt;em&gt;Let's get this over with before &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;she &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;decides &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;slaughter &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;this whole &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;fucking town.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The window slid open and she leaned out into the cool morning air. "What do you want?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Apologies for invading your room. You seemed scared and highly distressed. I thought I could help out," the woman said, showing genuine concern on her face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;And she's a good actress too, &lt;/em&gt;Sophia thought. &lt;em&gt;What an absolute monster.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're not human, are you?" she found herself asking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What? No of course I am!" Ilea replied, hovering outside a window with ashen wings on her back. Wisps of the element licked the air around her like an omen of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia rubbed her temple and sighed. "Don't just go around pushing your mana into people. It's borderline rape."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her eyes opened wide and she hovered back a meter or two. "I… I'm sorry… I didn't."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She waved her off. "Don't, it's fine. You meant well. At least I think you did. Forget what I said. I don't want people to die or go insane because you ask them for healing consent. What kind of world would that be?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One where you can sue doctors for treating you?" Ilea said, more to herself really.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sue? Whatever… what did you want? Why has the personification of pain and death come to my window?" Sophia sighed. She was tired and noticed it too. &lt;em&gt;You're taking risks &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;that you shouldn't. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Calm down. Choose your words carefully. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;You know what she is. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don't &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;offend her.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea laughed and floated a little closer again. "I thought I'd be seen as someone who brings life and recovery. Not pain and death. I suppose both are true."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Keep it fucking down you twats!" someone shouted out of an open window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman hovered closer. "Should we continue inside?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure," Sophia said and closed the window, finding Ilea sitting on a chair made of ash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll keep it short. You are obviously in dire need of sleep," the woman said. A statement of fact, neither insult nor taunt. "I found something in that cavern you saw at the end. Well you heard it too. The Specters of Rot," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia opened her eyes wide. "There's more than one? It's unusual for anything below triple mark to paralyze me for that long."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well, they are triple mark. Around level six hundred actually," Ilea said and scratched her chin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Six hundred? Wow… your identify skill is that high?" Sophia asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah no, It's just at level twelve. I killed one of them. Six twenty. They regenerate and use blood magic as well as bone swords. Quite dangerous. Some of the most powerful creatures in the six hundreds I've fought," the healer said, nodding as if to confirm her own assumption. "The Wyverns might be close… if they had regeneration… maybe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I…," Sophia started and stumbled backwards. "I need to… sit down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her bed was still miles away but she felt something form behind and under her, catching her stumbling form before she found herself in a chair. A black one, made of ash. It warmed up as she sat there. &lt;em&gt;Comfortable, &lt;/em&gt;she thought as it shaped itself around her bum and back. &lt;em&gt;No, focus.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You, killed? Killed one of them? Six hundred? Alone? What?" she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes. I have quite a few skills that make me a good match for them. Regeneration and high defense as well as Blood Magic Resistance in the second tier. Perception helps too of course, otherwise it would be difficult to keep up with the teleporting creatures. Especially in complete darkness," she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Okay," Sophia managed to say. The words were still processing in her mind. "How does this relate to me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Did she just come to gloat? Or is her game still ongoing… oh gods… she's still playing with us, just another form of torture.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, yes. Of course. Sorry, lost track again. Well, I waited for a while and they didn't follow but I would say this little village is fucked if one comes up to the surface," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Six hundred? Yes… we would be," Sophia said and gulped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's why… I have a skill to give people a mark, to let them call for me in case of emergency. I thought about the others but you seem just the right mix of apprehensive and smart. Colt would just call me for a laugh or because he'd think it an advance on my part. Edgar hates my guts and wouldn't use it even if his life depended on it and Sean. Well it was between him and you but you seem a little less scared of me," the monster explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You wish… to mark me?" Sophia asked. &lt;em&gt;No… &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;never make a deal with a &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;monster &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;or demon. It never comes out well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes. I tested it with several of my friends and it's safe. I'll know where to find you in case you call for me. Just a precaution. I think if nothing shows up this week, we're in the clear. I'll be back tomorrow night anyway but I just wanted to be sure," she said and continued in a murmur. "I hope that undead didn't break out of that blight cathedral… ah well, might check in quickly before going back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blight cathedral… undead? Wait a minute.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't exactly have a choice here, do I?" Sophia gathered her courage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You do. You just say no. I know it's scary to see someone powerful show up out of nowhere and show interest in you in some way. Trust me, I do. However, even though I know the training was nothing for you, did I actually do anything to put you in harm's way? Did I break my word even once? Was I hostile towards you or is there any reason why you would mistrust me?" Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia calmed herself and again marveled at how comfortable the ashen chair was. She thought back on everything and had to agree. They were never in danger, not really. If she could beat a level six hundred creature, the Abominations were nothing to her. It could be a lie but she had seen her fight the beings. As much as she believed the healer, in the end it did not matter if she killed one or not. She had healed Edgar without asking anything in return.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea had rushed to help that adventurer, saved him even. She had helped them get stronger… in her twisted and horrific way… and she had protected them, even brought them back out after. Despite her interest to go deeper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If she was Lilith, and there was little reason to doubt it at this point, then the songs supported her too. &lt;em&gt;If she didn't &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;pay for them. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Everything just to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;get this mark on her.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She shook her head and sighed. This woman could just force her to accept anyway. And yet she was giving her a choice here. Her words rang true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I accept. Under some conditions," Sophia said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea smiled. "Oho… how daring of you," she said and leaned forward in her own ashen chair. "What do you want?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gold!" Sophia blurted out. &lt;em&gt;Ah, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;that's so stupid. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ask for gold? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;She &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;doesn't even &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;carry &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;a &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;pouch or &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;backpack.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure, how does five pieces sound? That would be equivalent to quite a few jobs at your level. For a full team that is," Ilea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What?! Five! Is she nuts?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia watched in disbelief as five pieces of gold appeared out of nowhere and floated towards her on a small circular ashen tablet. &lt;em&gt;A storage item, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;of course! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;did I not think of that? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Because &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;she doesn't dress &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;like a noble, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;doesn't talk like them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Anything else? I don't want to be annoying but I should leave soon," the healer said and looked out into the morning sky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;That's it, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;the sunlight &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;will hurt her! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;S&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;he's a &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;witch after all. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Or something more sinister. &lt;/em&gt;Every argument the more cautious side of her came up with was dulled and dismissed by the golden shine in her hands. This would cover her expenses for a year if she was conservative in her spending. &lt;em&gt;Or I could buy new equipment.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">495458</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 16:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azarinth Healer - Chapter 456 Blood</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/493975</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chapter 456 Blood&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia couldn't stop herself anymore. She stepped to the side of the exit and puked. Whatever remained in her stomach came back out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, do that somewhere else," the nearby guard said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Leave it, I don't want to explain a corpse to the guard," Sean said and handed a coin to the man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fucking rookies, at least prepare before going in," he muttered to himself and resumed his post in silence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prepare? For that? &lt;/em&gt;Sophia thought and turned around, wiping her mouth as the surroundings grew colder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sean was already there, placating her with a gesture. "Calm down. He doesn't know. Nobody could know."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be so satisfying, to show that guard who was unprepared, powerless, weak. Sean was right. Jeopardizing themselves and their entry to this dungeon wasn't worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you alright?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm very far from alright, Sean," Sophia said and sighed, looking at her hands as she opened and closed them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell was that?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man just shook his head. He hadn't been speechless many times, usually eager to offer some words of support. "Come on, let's have ourselves a drink."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good idea," Colt said as he joined them. "You think she'll come back tomorrow?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are kidding, right?" Sophia said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What? Got more levels from this than the last year of adventuring," the warrior said. "It was pretty fucked up, I'll admit that much."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fucked up?" Sophia said. "I never want to see anything like those Abominations ever again. And that last part? I thought I was getting eaten… from the inside."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warrior gulped. "It was crazy. And her healing just took care of it… Sean, I tell you, we really have to get us one of those healers. We could do what she said, lay traps and hunt creatures like that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have fought with healers… she's not exactly a normal representation. I haven't ever met one who just stood there and took direct hits from level three hundred creatures," Sean said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why are we talking here, come on. Let's go," Sophia said and walked towards the inn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Agreed," Colt said and followed. "Did you see her wings? I want some of those."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good luck with that. With your weight, you'd need ten times that size," Sophia said and winked his way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll show you something else ten times that size," the warrior said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That doesn't make any sense, Colt," Sean said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edgar sighed and shook his head. "What a night."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_________________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'You have heard the challenge of a Specter of Rot – You resist its effect'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea received the same message as earlier. She had dropped the group off near the exit of the dungeon, the flight quite simple with her Sentinel Huntress and sphere picking up where they had used their magic on the way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reward had come when she used the same skills to get back into the deep cavern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ding' 'Sentinel Huntress reaches 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; lvl 3'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could feel it again, the blight damaging her from the inside. &lt;em&gt;Not bligh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;t, &lt;/em&gt;she thought. It was less strong of an effect than the power she had experienced in the Karheim dungeon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enough to kill the others.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her healing luckily canceled it out but fighting creatures while focusing on them wasn't in the cards. Not if she wanted to guarantee their survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sooo, Specter of Rot… let's see if this place manages to pose a challenge after all," Ilea said as she hovered farther into the vast cavern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The place was pitch black and silent. Nothing suggested the presence of a being other than herself. If only it hadn't been for that screech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you had been quiet, I might have left you alone… to rot in this god forsaken hole in the ground.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea didn't know where the creature had come from, it might as well have been birthed out of the void itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two swords made of bone slashed out, the weight, power and quality enough to cut through her ash and deep into her skin. According to Azarinth Fighting that was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea didn't quite know enough yet to let the creature close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was flying, like her. Wings made of skin and bone. Two dead eyes set into a malformed skull. The creature was three meters in height, deadly talons on both hands and legs at the end of lean but muscular limbs. The swords were just over two meters long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Specter of Rot – lvl ???]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Way to make it interesting, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought with a smile, all her skills ready to answer whatever questions the being might ask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Specter did not have a mouth however, power emanating form its form as magic was released.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dancing? Oh, how did you know I just took some lessons?" she asked and twirled through the air as the being rushed her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;__________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I tell you, she just stood there. Level three hundred. She's at least that high," Colt repeated himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of five was listening to him near the bar, the innkeeper apparently quite interested too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What skills did she use?" one of them asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you think this is a good idea?" Edgar asked Sean, the two of them sitting with Sophia at their usual table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She didn't tell us to keep it to ourselves," Sean said. "Besides. Everything he said so far is in the song."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We shouldn't share anything else. About the healers she wants to train… and about how she helped us out." Sophia said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She nearly got us killed," Edgar said but waved her off before she could retort. "I know she helped. And I get it. She's just a little off. Well a little lot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't think we were ever in any danger. Not from anything besides herself," Sophia said. &lt;em&gt;They still don't get &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;what k&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ind of a monster that woman was. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Talking &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;about Abominations &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;instead of her. Just because she's wearing a human body.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Doesn't matter. I agree with you that we shouldn't talk too much. Sean?" Edgar said and glanced at the man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ranger rolled his eyes and stood up. "Okay, alright. Colt!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ash!" the warrior said and spread his arms. "That's all lads… keep away from the dark, or she will snatch you away."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of them laughed, others talked amongst themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sounds like that song. Lilith, was it?" a nearby patron said before changing the subject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colt brought four mugs to the table and sat down with a satisfied sigh. "There you go lads. Something to fill back up the water we lost by shitting ourselves. Or puking." he added and winked to Sophia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And we survived another day," Sean said and grabbed his mug. "To Lilith."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To my crush," Colt said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edgar touched their mugs without a word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To the monster of Ravenhall," Sophia said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sean laughed. "To get that title, with the Shadow's Hand being located there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you think she's actually different form them? Or is she just a high level Shadow?" Colt asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We never asked if she is one in the first place," Sean said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia signaled to them that they had company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The barkeeper had switched with someone else and was approaching their table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sean, right?" he said and nodded to the man. "Couldn't help but overhear your story. Mind if I join in?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Take a seat, Hudson. It has been an exciting night," Sean said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia glanced at the man. She had seen him before and was pretty sure he owned the whole place. He wasn't very tall but made up for it in sheer density. Hudson nearly reached Colt's levels of muscle. He sported a short gray beard and hair of the same color bound in a bun, visible scars on both his face and arms telling of his time of adventuring or military, wrinkles added into the mix giving him a grizzled look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Warrior – lvl 82]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not an overwhelming threat, &lt;/em&gt;Sophia thought. His influence in the area could be a problem, which is why Sean allowed him to sit down with them. After what they've been through, she was sure he wouldn't easily welcome a stranger to join in conversation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you know?" Sean asked, getting straight to the point as he leaned in. He talked in a hushed tone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hudson leaned back, the chair groaning under his weight. "I heard the songs. More than that, I talked to someone who met her. Nearly a year ago."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Songs? There's more than one?" Edgar asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia was interested too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yep. Pretty much the same thing however. One goes into more detail on why she is such a bloody good thing for Ravenhall and its people. Sounds to me like she has a cult following. Mind magic is an option," the barkeeper said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia rolled her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You disagree, lass?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Bards need money too. You pay them and they write a song," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well… you ain't wrong. Songs are one thing but the man I talked to… he swore he had met her. The Shadow wielding ash. Apparently she paid people to attack her. To train resistances, people said. Just that the magic did very little to injure her at all. And if it did, she was healed back up in mere instants," Hudson explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why I thought it was her. It sounded the same to me when the big guy over here talked about it. But three hundred? I've never heard of someone that high," he said and shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sean nodded. "I think she has to be there. At least that. With what she showed. They're out there, you know? They have to be. People at that level. Higher even."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nobles hiding in their estates and castles," Edgar said and took a sip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hiding won't bring you to those levels. You can torture and kill slaves and captured pray all you want," Sophia said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Aye. That one… she enjoyed it. Not a shred of fear in her. You saw it too," Colt said and looked at Sean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ranger nodded absentmindedly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you think she found down there? You think she really went after it?" Colt asked and glanced at each of them in turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She did," Sophia stated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hudson was wise enough not to ask too many questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you think she will make it?" Edgar asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia turned her attention to the mug in front of her, lifting it towards her mouth. "I don't fear for her. I fear for whatever stands in her way."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea felt the magic condense, choosing not to blink this time as it manifested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rupture went through her, her blood exploding in a flurry of heat and movement. Half her chest was ripped out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She let it reform as she drifted backwards. &lt;em&gt;Having a hard time, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;are we?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The creature had to focus on her for quite some time to manifest its spell. It changed up the pattern, where it attacked and how fast it manipulated her blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of that mattered in the end as Ilea didn't exactly want to dodge the attacks. Granted, she didn't know exactly when they came but she was getting better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, she hadn't retaliated in any way, simply observing the creature as it attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Specter varied between a flurry of bladed attacks and blood magic in various forms. Projectiles, ruptures within her body, enhancement for its swords, and vine like blood shooting out from the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea only avoided the last variant, not about to get trapped if she had anything to say about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here we go again, &lt;/em&gt;she thought when the creature vanished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It appeared in a mist like state behind her, blades slashing through her armor and skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could see it vanish within her sphere, forming again and continuing its attack. The being attacked four to five times per second, putting her blink to shame. She only avoided the thrusting attacks, just in case she would end up impaled and thus trapped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea didn't know yet if the swords would give her bone magic resistance levels but it was worth a shot. It was difficult enough to avoid them entirely already. She was glad they didn't cleave through her limbs as easily as the Ascended had taken her apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Alright, let's see how durable you are, shall we?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She twirled backwards, a blade slashing through the air below. Ilea sped up and used her wings to maneuver her around its moving blades. She took the hit from the blood sphere that surged out, burning a layer off of her armor right before her fist landed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Absolute Destruction and Storm of Cinders rushed into the being as she pulled back, taking two slashes that drew blood. The thick red liquid flowed down and ignited, energy expanding as her wounds ripped open. And closed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Didn't die yet. That's good, &lt;/em&gt;she thought with a smile. &lt;em&gt;But you'll have to try harder than that, my friend.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She watched it vanish and turned to where she felt the newly available mark. Promptly using it against the creature seemed like a good way to further work on the skill. Ilea could feel its effect weaken as the seconds went by, another surge of magic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Talk?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She sent the thought towards the being floating in the dark but nothing answered her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It teleported in and out of her sphere's range with its continuous attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Quite convenient. Knowing where that thing is at all times.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea continued to fight the creature, her body cut and ripped apart in the process, the woman getting more and more aggressive in her approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She found that her punches and skills had less of an effect as she had expected. Something was wrong. This one was regenerating too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Perfect&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea could even see the creature now, the embers burning within its body and on its skin lit it up like a torch. The effects waned quickly but she reapplied them just as fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added other skills to the mix, burning it with Heart of Cinder and finally whistling at it with Monster Hunter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The creature stopped in its tracks and forced its magic into her blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No reaction? Guess my level just isn't high enough, &lt;/em&gt;Ilea thought with a smile, the echo of her whistle reaching her a moment later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She dodged another two blades that slashed her way and to her surprise found the weapons doubling suddenly. Blood magic made her shoulder explode an instant later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ah yes, the increased range. Maybe I shouldn't have infused it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were five of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea struggled to completely avoid all their attacks, finding their coordination striking. The constant blood magic posed more of a problem too, now that the more physical attacks didn't stop during the casting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her third tier healing was working extra shifts as whole sections of her were ripped out and splattered onto her ash or the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashen wings maneuvered her up and into open space, allowing her enough wiggle room to avoid most of the enemy strikes. Finding openings proved difficult however and she wasn't focusing on a more suicidal tactic quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea's limbs spread out from her back, interconnected with her wings, the tendrils lashed out and struck the beings, three at a time. All five when they were close enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The magic slamming into her was both there to level her resistance but just as much to recover mana, allowing her to keep up with the creatures even after nearly ten minutes of constant battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was sure by now that these things were either close to level seven or eight hundred or they had some form or regeneration. &lt;em&gt;Or &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;mana intrusion resistance. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Doesn't feel that- &lt;/em&gt;her thoughts were interrupted by a blade nearly slashing through her throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea kept her head as the tissue reconnected. &lt;em&gt;The mana goes in. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;They just heal the damage. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Quite &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;tough.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wondered if they were on the Vampire's level but thought it too risky to go all out, sacrificing her movement, dodging and defense over pure attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart of Cinder charged to higher levels for now and she didn't hold anything else back either. At this point the playing had turned into serious training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The danger wasn't anywhere close to the Ascended but she wondered if the Specters could actually take her down if they just managed to capture her with their blood vines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It helped that they apparently had to connect to the ground, ceiling or walls. If she stayed mostly in the middle of the cavern's space, she should be mostly safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This would be quite a bit more brutal in a small corridor.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood vines were moving closer from above, Ilea finally letting go of the stored heat. A spherical wave of fire and energy expanded, momentarily illuminating the space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dead eyes stared back, their skin nearly as pale as the swords of bone they held.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her released Heart of Cinder burned through the blood magic and parts of their bodies with ease. Not close to the power she had used against the steel barriers of the Ascended but nothing to take lightly either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ilea watched within her sphere as the burnt skin healed, missing parts reforming and the scorched sections shed away. Not a hint of fear or pain, just a single focus, a single goal. To cut down the unknown intruder in their midst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She blinked back to avoid a thrust attack, jolting her head backwards as a chunk of her face exploded outwards and reformed. As long as her brain didn't go, she wouldn't be taken out of the action. Her third tier prevented her from dying but even a fraction of a second could mean being pinned down and potentially reduced to a continuously regenerating soon to be corpse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She took a deep breath and focused on the fight. &lt;em&gt;The chance of them taking me down &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;is &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;low. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Now, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;let's see &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;if the same is &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;true the other way around.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">493975</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/syndication/16946</link><description>Latest updates of (Azarinth Healer)</description></rss>