<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Deeper Darker</title><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 93: Double Indemnity</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/502898</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tethari Asteroid&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Onla reached the relative safety of the overhang in front of the Ollo base before Horne. He had been ahead of her but had double-backed to give the lagging VendX troops some cover. That's what self-medicating with hormones did to you — made you emotional.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Horne, get in here," she shouted into the comms, but in a controlled and professional manner. "You're going to get yourself killed, you half-witted moron."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Incoming! We've got more incoming." He was flying above the running troopers, being buffeted by the wind but using the updraft to remain aloft longer than he would have been normally able. His suit's deflectors were set to max as he intercepted huge bolts of light that were slamming into the ground and bursting the remains of ships around them. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Onla's HUD showed the composition, construction and energy potential of the light-torpedoes. They were far in excess of anything the Central Authority could produce. And far more than what Horne's suit could block.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He didn't try to block them. Instead, he carefully positioned his shields and an angle that took them away from the panicked troopers. Light was still light. And Horne was still a moron, but he wasn't stupid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I can see that!" An edge crept into her voice, even though her hormones were at the minimum level. "Don't tell me what I already know, you jackass."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Troopers ran past her into the area around the main entrance, a huge vertical door that had been raised about a metre and left stuck there. None of them wanted to go in and face the base's security system, but no one wanted to be out there either.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm seeing over a hundred people out here," said Horne, his voice fading in and out over the comms. "Also several hundred more still inside the ships, hoping they can wait it out. Don't think that's a good idea. How are we going to get them—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a massive explosion as one of the VendX transport ships took a direct hit from a sizzling white beam of solid light. The ship, the people near it and the ground under it, all erupted into a cloud of flame and dirt, the newly created air molecules helping the flames to burn brightly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Horne went tumbling through the air, crashing into the ground only to suddenly spring back into the air as though he had just executed some perfectly timed acrobatic trick.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Never mind," he said. "Problem solved."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ziff, have you heard from the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tranquillity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;?" she asked the suit's AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm afraid there's no response," it said with unflustered politeness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Confirm Central Authority fleet status. Are they still in one piece?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a slight pause. "All Central Authority ships showing full hull integrity."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Are they coming?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"All ships are stationary."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Why can't you talk to them?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Signals above three hundred megahertz threshold are unable to get through."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They're being jammed?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Not by any technology we are currently aware of."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was always difficult to get machines to think for themselves in new situations. If they, or any of the devices on the network, had encountered an event previously there was no problem. But the first time something cropped up, it was a nightmare to get a machine to join the dots. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Find another way to get in contact with them. If you can get a reading on hull integrity, you can find a way to speak to them."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I understand."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Onla peered outside of the alcove. The Antecessor ships that were tiny dots near the wormhole were now slightly bigger dots. Pretty soon they wouldn't be dots at all. And then they would find out who was piloting the damn things. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Horne, we have to get inside."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm not getting any response from &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tranquillity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;," said Horne, his voice both excited and strained — jacked up on naturally occurring hormones at unnatural levels. He was going all out to protect these worthless VendX workers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They're being jammed. They'll send help when they can. Now get back in here."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Will do. Soon as I—" Horne's reply was distorted by static, the roar of the winds and the rapid disintegration of the asteroid's surface under light-torpedo bombardment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The CA commtech was designed to operate and deliver a clear signal under any conditions. Under water, during solar storms, through solid rock kilometres-thick. But there was something interfering, something the equipment hadn't been designed to anticipate, because no one knew it existed until now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"ZF-989, can you remotely boot up Guardian Horne's onboard AI?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm afraid not,m Guardian. Access codes have been reset by Guardian Horne. I can try to guess his password. Psych-eval strongly suggests it will be a lewd combination of words and numbers. I estimate I can break the code in between three and thirty-six hours, standard."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Horne! Stop self-medicating and fall back. We don't know who's flying those ships. If it's Antecessors, you won't be able to save anyone if you deplete your suit's defences on these useless plebs. Let them die. Stop being so bloody emotional!"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Okay, okay, no need to get your space suit's integrated underwear in a twist. I'm coming back."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Onla let out an exasperated breath and turned around to find herself facing hundreds of VendX employees, fully-armed, crowded into the alcove, all staring at her. It was then she realised her comms were still switched to enforced public announcement mode.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What are you looking at?" she snapped at them. "You can't wait out here. Go inside."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;None of them moved. It was understandable they would be reluctant to walk into an Ollo facility without the correct clearance, but it wasn't like they had a choice. What was in there might kill them, but what was happening out here definitely would.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ziff, lay down warning fire, ground-level."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A  rapid burst of laserfire issued from Onla's suit, striking the ground in front of the VendX employees. They quickly backed up but were still uneasy about entering the site under the partially raised blast door.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Around them, the asteroid continued to be bombarded but the intensity seemed to have decreased.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Multiple ships are attacking the unknown Antecessor ships," reported ZF-989. "Multiple ships have now been destroyed."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Central Authority ships?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"All Central Authority ships have been destroyed."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;So much for the cavalry. The firepower of those Antecessor vessels was incredible, able to pierce the shields of the most advanced ships in existence with barely any effort. The base would pose little problem for them once they arrived at the asteroid. Their only chance was to go deep inside, barricade themselves in and then wait for reinforcements to arrive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Where did they come from?" said Horne as he landed next to Onla after falling,  running and sliding to a halt. "Antecessor ships actually flying around blowing things up. This is crazy. What now? Fire up the Ollo defence grid and blow them out of the sky? Revenge, right? That's the play."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Calm down, Horne. You're being too emotional. Drain your lymphatics and take deep breaths."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm not being emotional."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Emotional and overexcited."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No. This is the way I always am. Take it or leave it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'd like to leave it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Tough luck, you'll have to take it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Excuse me, I'm Chief Office Ghent of the VendX Priority Fleet," said a stern voice that came from one of the troopers who were huddled inside the alcove. "We've made a quick check and we three are the ranking officers. We suggest a temporary alliance until this matter is resolved."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;His battlesuit was the fanciest of the survivors, adding credibility to his claim. The two people with him were a little less ostentatious in their attachments, but all three had a high-level of weaponry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Didn't you hear what I said?" snapped Onla. "This is a compulsory buyout. We give the orders, you follow them. Do as you're told or have your contracts terminated, permanently. Lead your people inside the base, Ghent."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was another explosion but not so loud. There wasn't much left to blow up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They don't appear to be targeting the base," said Ghent. "We can wait out here for now."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Go inside," said Onla. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I respectfully decline to follow—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Three quick shots struck the VendX officers, one each in the head. Horne's sleeve gun hissed and let out a little smoke before retracting. He'd just executed three high-ranking VendX employees.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Numerous members of the VendX fleet activated their weapons. The inside of Onla's visor sprang into multi-sectioned life as targeting screens showed each hostile action and primed weapons on her suit to take them out. The activity along her arms and shoulders was enough to give her would-be assailants enough reason for second thoughts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Okay, maybe I'm being a little emotional," said Horne. "They started it, though."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Guardian Horne has committed an act of unprovoked aggression," said ZF-989. "Would you like to file a report?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Unprovoked?" said Horne. "Are your sensors even working?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I apologise, Guardian. My programming requires me to bring this matter to my operator's attention. No judgement is implied."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No, no report," said Onla. "Classify it as Control Protocol, level three." It was standard Central Authority practice to remove the leadership of any commandeered group. Once there was no other authority figure to turn to, people became much more compliant. Although, executing them was only meant to be used as a last resort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Level three is only valid in the case of food riots and civil unrest," said the AI. It wasn't wrong.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm classifying this as a special case. Reasoning to be laid out at a later date when we aren't being bombed to shit."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Reclassification noted. Reminder set."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And send VendX a letter of complaint for poor training of their salesforce, and demand an apology." In these sorts of situations, it was best to go on the offensive. As it was with most situations. "Put me on public announcement mode." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You are already in public announcement mode."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Of course I am. Remind me to speak to you about that." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Reminder set."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She turned to the gathered, somewhat nervous survivors of the VendX Priority Fleet. "VendX employees, as I have already clearly stated, you are now sub-contractors for the Central Authority. Breach of contract will be dealt with swiftly and with no option for appeal. This is a category six emergency, and we only have five categories, understand? You do exactly what I tell you or we will classify you as an enemy combatant and eliminate you. We are the Central Authority and VendX has signed up to our charter. We own you until further notice." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They weren't responding very well, as the biomedical telemetry ZF-989 was showing her clearly indicated. Mass readings were imprecise at best but when the crowd all felt the same way, the graphs shot up exponentially, so subtle interpretations weren't necessary. It wasn't like they were treated any better than this by VendX, but then VendX rarely executed its own people in public. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Aren't you just going to use us as meat shields," said a hesitant voice. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;ZF-989 pinpointed the speaker and offered her the option to take him out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No, we don't need you to be meat shields. Antecessor tech will vaporise you and keep going. We do need you to not get in our way, so follow orders or be eliminated from the situation. We also provide full medical and dental benefits while you are conscripted to us."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The crowd seemed to settle down. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a bright flash and the asteroid surface was painted a brilliant white.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The wormhole is opening," said ZF-989.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Reinforcements already?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Onla pivoted to look up at the starry sky. The Antecessor ships were still on her HUD, but now there was a fleet of ships behind them, and they didn't have Antecessor profiles. Although, they were just as recognisable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Seneca Corps has been identified," said the AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oh shit," said Horne.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Get inside," shouted Onla. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;No one hesitated this time. If there was one truth in the universe, it was that the Corps didn't give a damn who got caught in the middle of one of their fights. They saw every battle as us against them, and everyone who wasn't in the Corps counted as them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Even though the blast door was only partially raised, it was wide enough to allow several dozen people through at a time. On the other side was a long tunnel that led to the main base. The VendX troops flooded the tunnel as they raced to get away before the Corps unleashed their ridiculously overpowered weapons that would probably cause more damage than the Antecessors ever would.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The ground was shaking already.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Onla reached the base control room and tried to get some kind of response from the Ollo network. Everything looked turned off and depowered. The doors at the far end refused to open despite the VendX troops doing their best to prise them apart.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Receiving no response," said ZF-989.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Is it dead?" If the network was down that would at least mean it couldn't target them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No. It is being suppressed. Source unknown."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Someone's controlling it?" This was an unexpected turn of events. People had been known to destroy one of Ramon Ollo's devices, but no one had ever managed to hijack one.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hello everyone," said a voice in everyone's comms. "I'm Hollet 3.2."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The people crowded in the control room stared blankly at their companions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You're the Central Authority, right? I'm here with Guardian Tezla. Well, she's around here somewhere. Look, it's not really safe up there. Why don't you come down here? Not that it's safe here, either, but, you know, safety in numbers."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The doors on the far side opened. It was clearly a trap. Onla would have hesitated if she didn't have hundreds of meat shields to help out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Everyone, go through," she shouted. "It's our only chance."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They ran into the gaping entrance to the Antecessor site.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">502898</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 92: Hostile Takeover</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/501939</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tethari Asteroid&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Two metal tubes stood erect on the surface of the asteroid, their bottom thirds buried in the hard rock as though it was soft mud, unbending against the howling wind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There wasn't supposed to be any wind on the barren, atmosphereless surface and also no howling. The asteroid was changing into something new, something never seen before. Not by humanity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Panels slid aside on each tube and two Guardians stepped out, their suits protecting them from the misplaced elements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Full analysis," said Guardian Onla. "Here to the base." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We already have a full analysis taken from the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tranquillity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;'s sensors," said her onboard AI. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I don't recall asking," said Onla. "Full analysis, ZF-989."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Please call me Ziff."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," said Onla. "If I have to ask a third time, it won't look very good on your record, ZF-989."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Analysis is complete. Displaying results now." The inside of Onla's visor lit up with numbers and spectral graph readouts. "I followed your orders the first time, Guardian. Concurrent advisory suggestions are provided as an extra benefit to be used at your discretion. No time was wasted as I am able to multitask."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The only thing worse than being saddled with a fastidious AI — which was all of them — was getting saddled with one of the smug ones. She knew they weren't programmed with personalities, yet they somehow always managed to develop the most objectionable ones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Windy," said Horne, flapping his arms as though he was preparing to take-off. "Have to be careful we don't get blown away."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The readings told her very little. There was an atmosphere but no indication of where it had come from. The air wasn't breathable but would be in around twenty hours from now. The temperature was increasing steadily.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Wind speed was gusting up to 60 km/h. Her suit kept her rooted to the ground. Horne was running back and forth in front of her, leaping into the air and seeing how long he could remain airborne. The low gravity enabled him to stay aloft for several seconds before crashing back down several metres away.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ping Guardian Tezla's location," said Onla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No response," said the AI. "Ollo base is shielded below ground level. No life signs on the surface."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"None from up here, either," said Horne as he soared past for the third time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Could you take this more seriously? We're here to do a job."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm doing my job," said Horne. "Weee, I'm flying."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Your suit has rocket propulsion," said Onla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yeah, but this is flying like a bird, all-natural, tech-free, no organics. Once the air stabilises, I might try it without the suit, naked. Hey, do you think not being able to blink counts as a malfunction in a new body? My vision's okay but my eyeballs feel a bit dried out."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Horne was a good Guardian. His record spoke for itself, full of successful missions and few repercussions. But as a colleague, he was deeply irritating. He insisted on activating the hormone secretions in his body and leaving them on beyond what was physiologically necessary, which could make his behaviour somewhat erratic. He claimed it made him feel more human. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We might as well enter the site," said Onla. "We won't get any more information from up here."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Do you want to get together after this is dealt with?" said Horne.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," said Onla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I have eye-drops somewhere, if you find the intensity of my gaze uncomfortable."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ops-1 is sending me updated orders," said ZF- 989.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Why weren't they sent directly to me?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You were busy. I thought it would be easier for you to focus on one thing at a time."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She could see she would have to take corrective measures against her suit-bound partner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What are the orders?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"A VendX repair team has been allowed access to the planet for emergency work. We are to check for any drones or satellites they might try to send to the asteroid."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What the—" Onla looked over the report scrolling across her visor. "They let them through?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Is there a problem?" asked the AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Get me Ops-1."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Sent. No immediate response. Perhaps I can assist you," said ZF-989. "Is there a problem?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Is there a problem? Command has just let through a VendX strike force."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You are postulating an attack on Enaya?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"How do they even let you out of the factory with this many bugs in your system?" Onla shook her head. "Is there no QA at all?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I was not built in a factory," said the offended AI. "And my internal systems are bug-free. My last screening showed a—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"VendX is headed here," said Horne, jumping fifteen metres to land next to Onla. "They'll send a drop-ship over here once they're masked behind the planet."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"There is no current evidence suggesting they will overstep their clearly delineated boundaries. Such a breach would be highly prejudicial to future relations between the Central Authority and VendX Galactic. Probability of such an action is less than five percent. Still no response from the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tranquillity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Great," said Onla. "Send an urgent communique to all Central Authority vessels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;telling them to prepare for one or more ships in their vicinity to fake an accidental explosion that will target their engines, weapons and communications array." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Probability of such an action is—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I hope you're multitasking while you're wasting my time with your babbling."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The AI stopped talking. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Weapons online?" said Horne.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes," said Onla. "See if we can make it to the base before the 'surprise' attack. Haven't heard much from your AI. Why isn't it annoying you with poor advice."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Turned it off," said Horne. "Never use them. Voice in your head telling to do things you know are wrong — I find it a little creepy, to be honest. Hey, what's your take on pubic hair — yay or nay?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ships detected," said ZF-989. "Approaching on an oblique vector. Verification is being blocked."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Onla looked up at the endlessly starry sky. Her visor display turned into a grid, highlighting the dots that were the approaching ships. Twelve of them with flight paths disguised to seem like they were just passing. Very convincing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;These sorts of 'accidental' incursions were standard practice for a company of VendX's size — smaller companies would try to sneak in undetected, bigger ones would obtain clearance. The VendX-sized ones thought they could get away with it because usually they did. Central Authority drone ships accepted their excuses at face value and apologies were documented and filed. Fines were imposed. It was hard to program an AI to see the difference between an honest mistake and a cunning deception. That was why they employed the Guardians.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Cannons deploy, safety off, arm with anti-armour rounds."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Her suit vibrated as sections unlocked and weapon turrets emerged.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Request for live fire sent," said ZF-989.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Field override," said Onla. She doubted they would hear back from the command ship anytime soon. "Cause of override: mission objective interference. Confirm."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Confirmed. Would you like to hail the approaching ships?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes. Open fire."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Send a hail or open fire?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Both. Multitask."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;VGV Executive Order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Planet Enaya - orbit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord stood beside the captain as the reports from the drop-ships came in live. The bank of operators down on the floor were coordinating the attack and the main screen showed their positions as they closed in on the asteroid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We are under fire," screamed a shaky voice. "Sensors identify two Central Authority sources, outputting fifteen hundred megatons of damage each. Taking evasive action. Recommend we abort. Please advise." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was undoubtedly Guardians, at least two of them. They weren't on the CA ships, they were already on the asteroid, and they weren't waiting for an explanation. Guardians rarely did. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Not a welcome deviation from the Chairman's itinerary but not a completely unforeseen one.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord leaned forward and spoked in the mic on the captain's left armrest. "Negative. Do not abort. Broadcast preloaded message delta." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What do you think we've been doing?" snapped the mission leader. "We've tried beta and gamma also. They're ignoring us."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The screen showed the ships weaving through the hail of missiles directed at them. They were doing well, only minor damage so far. But it would be a lot more than that if they tried to land. The Guardians were letting their displeasure be known.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;No surprise there. Guardians didn't care for corporations asking for help, genuine or not. They saw it as a waste of resources on entities that had plenty of their own resources to spare. They also liked to pick and mix from any wreckage, as was their right under salvage laws.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Request permission to return fire. We could claim a misfire."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Request denied," said Daccord. That would only lead to an escalation and a terrible mess. There was only one way out of this. "Mission leader, I want you to cease evasive manoeuvres and take the hit."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What? You want us to sacrifice a ship?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I want you to sacrifice all of them. Take damage and then crash land on the asteroid. The ships can take it and you have the latest anti-crash protection installed. Testing indicates at least seventy percent of you will be fine, and you'll be on the rock through no fault of your own."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was a solid plan. If the Guardian's shot their ships down, it would be their fault VendX Galactic was on Ollo property. He could definitely work with that in a court of arbitration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a long pause before the mission leader responded. "Hazard pay authorised?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Half-pay," said Daccord. "For survivors, only."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We're going in."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tethari Asteroid&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This is ridiculous," said Horne. "How do they keep dodging our missiles? Did we buy these things from VendX?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;That would explain it but Horne was just venting his frustration. The suits were built by the Central Authority, the missiles were generated from stored energy by the turrets. The VendX ships just had better defensive tech. As long as they remained far enough away to be able to calculate trajectory, they would be able to—&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was an explosion, followed by another and another. The ships were being hit. For a moment, Onla felt a pang of satisfaction, but it was quickly quelled as the ships changed course and came crashing down. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Clever. A deliberate ploy to justify landing on the asteroid. Well, they wouldn't be able to dodge if the ships were on the ground.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Target crash site," ordered Onla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Central Authority regulations require me to inform you—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Do it while firing. On low volume."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Looks like they're offering to surrender," said Horne.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It's a trap," said Onla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Probability of survivor's needing medical assistance is high. Seventy-eight percent and rising."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What's the overall percentage for Guardian overrules being correct?" said Onla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Thirty-eight percent."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And what's the overall percentage of AI suggestions being correct?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a slight pause. "Twelve percent."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Keep firing."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The VendX ships had crash-landed in a cluster, creating a crater filled with smoking hulls. They had all managed to remain mostly intact, apart from some wings and external housing. Troops were pouring out, straight into a hail of laserfire. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The CA suits were built to destroy entire planet defences. They converted light into lethal energy blasts, adapting form to fit the target. Anything from tiny pellets spread over a wide area to torpedoes that could take out a battleship. A few VendX repairmen wouldn't pose a problem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A blinding flash of light caught Onla by surprise. She turned her head and her visor instantly darkened. Above her, the swirling eye of the wormhole was opening. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What is it?" said Horne. "I thought it'd been shut down."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It was," said Onla. "It's a forced opening. Maybe Seneca? Or one of the mega…" Her voice trailed off as she saw the first ships to emerge. Even at this distance she recognised their distinct profiles. Antecessor ships had a very unique look to them, although this was the first time she'd seen one actually moving.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Are those Antecessor ships?" said Horne, awe in his voice. "Who's flying them?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Points of light glittered around the newly arrived ships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Shut up and run," said Onla. She was already moving. "ZF-989, open a channel, public, enforced. VendX Galactic, I am issuing a compulsory buyout order. You now are all temporary employees of the Central Authority, provision of the… Ziff, what's the treaty?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The Deathbed Treaty. Treaty 19, section—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes, yes, I'm issuing Deathbed. No negotiations, no opt-out. Look it up in your own time. Get to the base and leave behind the injured. Move."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figures ran, bouncing across the wreckage. Horne went soaring over her head.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The first light torpedoes hit the asteroid just as she reached the base. It was the same technology as the lasers in her suit, except the Central Authority had only managed to get them to work at a six percent efficiency. She doubted the originators of the tech would suffer from the same limitations. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">501939</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 11:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 91: Disarmed</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/499854</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;VGV Executive Order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord tapped the screen with the tip of his thumb and scanned the summary on the datapad to make sure he had everything in order. He had made a short list of key events for quick reference. The Chairman's plan had to be implemented in the correct sequence to guarantee success. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;As expected of the Chairman, he was able to combine these elements in his head, switching them around until he arranged them in the precise progression that would yield the desired outcome. Even with the blueprint for success in front of him, Daccord found it hard to see the natural leaps in logic that would force the Central Authority and the Enayan government to authorise the VendX fleet to enter the restricted area where the Tethari asteroid was located.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He had to let his mind idle and allow the rational part of his brain to withdraw. He had to think like a customer. He had to let himself want to believe. Then it became obvious. It was the only path they would take. Take willingly. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;And the Chairman could see it all without technological assistance and with the additional and voluntary handicap of being blind. He refused to have his sight fixed until the person responsible for causing his injury was caught and suitably punished.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;That task now fell to Daccord, and if he failed to accomplish it, the person suffering Ubik U Ubik's rightful penance would be him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The Central Authority have hailed us, Mr Secretary," said the Captain. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord looked up at the man in the command seat. He looked a little pale, a little clammy around the face, but otherwise in reasonably good shape. His right arm was in a sling, bound to his torso by metal cables that prevented any kind of movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes," said Daccord. "As expected, they are using standard protocol." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;You could count on the Central Authority to act as expected in any given situation, no matter how strained. They followed guidelines and took matters one step at a time. They acted calm and restrained at all times, which made them very open to external management procedures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"How many other ships are on the perimeter?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"One hundred and forty-seven," said one of the ensigns. "Eighty from rival corporations, Twenty-six content providers, twelve independent salvage teams, three observation platforms and the rest are private contractors with crews of three or less."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It sounded about right for an unprecedented event like this. Opportunists and observers for other parties. No one knew what to expect — most likely nothing — but they wanted to make sure they didn't miss out on something big. An Antecessor site left unguarded could provide a bauble or two for someone passing by who 'unknowingly' stumbled across an invisible perimeter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The only problem was the Central Authority and their ships. They followed rules and were slow to act, but when they did, it was usually without mercy or remorse.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The Priority Fleet?" said Daccord, checking his datapad one more time. This had to be done right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ready to join us."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Captain? Are you ready?" &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I…" He didn't look ready for anything other than a return to the M-Aid machine. They'd had to pull him out a little early, but most of the work on his arm had been completed. He was in the recuperation phase and his contractually agreed period of leave from active duty due to traumatic loss of blood, tissue or bone had elapsed. "I am ready."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The man looked green and unsteady, but he was sitting in a fully supportive sustain-harness with all systems set to cognisance delta-3, the lowest level of brain activity that still enabled speech. They needed him to be able to hold a conversation. He had to do it personally. The Chairman's plan didn't allow for anyone to take his place. The ship would keep him conscious and alert, even if his organs failed and his central nervous system collapsed. The hypodermic needles inserted into his back fed him drugs to soothe and stimulate him in automated sequence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Captain, please," said Daccord, giving him a sympathetic nod to continue. "You may begin with stage one of the action."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The captain gave a slight nod back, careful not to lose control of his recently un-braced neck, and turned his chair with a tap of his finger on the armrest. The chair swivelled to face the large screen at the front of the bridge. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This is Captain Maharash of the VendX Galactic Vessel &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Executive Order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;. Responding to a distress call from the Enayan General Assembly."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The screen flickered from the centre in seven different colours, a pebble dropped in a pond, radiating outwards; the call sign of the Central Authority. No Guardians — that helped. They didn't bother with visual identification when Guardians weren't available — they were faceless computers — but they did require anyone they hailed to show their faces. And if you told them your ship was suffering some sort of technical malfunction preventing you from doing so, they would gladly send a drone to punch its way through your hull with a camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This is Central Authority Vessel &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tranquillity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;," said a soft, sexless voice. "We have monitored no communications between the planet Enaya and VendX Galactic. This region is currently under lockdown, by order of the Central Authority, Treaty 7, section 3.  Full terms and conditions of the treaty are available as an attachment with this communication and also as a downloadable file from the Central Authority hub."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We are aware of the lockdown order," said the Captain. "The distress call was automated and sent encrypted via the VendX internal network."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Currently, we are experiencing technical difficulties with the Tethari asteroid and won't be allowing access to this area for the immediate future. Please remain behind the Ruben-Sadar line to avoid being destroyed by Central Authority artillery, as sanctioned by Treaty 19, Sections 4, 6, 9 and 12. We apologise for the inconvenience."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Captain's eyes flicked to look at Daccord. He knew what was at stake. A lot more than his arm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We aren't here about the asteroid," said Maharash. "This is a humanitarian emergency regarding the Enayans, not the Ollo Dynasty. Please contact the Enayan government for confirmation."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Please wait."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The screen went dark and Captain Maharash let out a long, jagged breath. The needles in his back pumped up and down like tiny pistons and the lights on the harness lit up as they corrected for the deficiencies in his body, boosting his immune system and secreting synthetic cell tissue repair hormones into him. The cost for his medical maintenance was already far beyond what the man's health coverage allowed for. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord checked the datapad which was relaying the Captain's readings in real-time. The important thing was to make sure he survived. For now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Continue with stage two when the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tranquillity &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;reconnects."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes," said the Captain without turning his chair.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The screen radiated colour again. "&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Executive Order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;, this is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tranquillity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;. We have connected General Assembly Acting Chief Officer Toaku to the call."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A face appeared, filling the screen with sombre intensity. The face of a military man, that much was obvious from his bearing, his scars and his stiff collar with military markings. He looked haggard and worn out. A man struggling with problems on a global scale, with no time for pointless conference calls. Daccord checked the datapad. It was the man the Chairman had told him to expect. Of course.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This is Colonel… Chief Office Toaku. We can not accommodate any kind of—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ki…" said the Captain, recognition flooding his weakened voice. "Is that you?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The eyes of the man on the screen narrowed. "Tareq?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They knew each other. From long ago, they had met as junior officer and up-and-coming salesman. The Captain of one of VendX's flagships had to start somewhere, and he had to be pretty good at it to climb the ranks so spectacularly. What was even more spectacular was the  Chairman's awareness of an unremarkable meeting that occurred decades ago.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes, old friend." Toaku's feature softened. "It has been a while. How much easier things were then, eh?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Nostalgia, familiarity, relief — susceptibility was already trending up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Please continue with the confirmation-denial decision," cut in the Central Authority. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The man on the screen, Toaku, grimaced, then pressed on. "We can confirm VendX equipment installed at thirty-six thousand sites across the globe have suffered catastrophic failure. We need those vending machines operational but we can not currently open any landing sites. Unfortunately, we will have to—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord hit a tab on the datapad screen. The needle just below the Captain's right shoulder injected an oily liquid and Captain Maharash let out a stifled yell. He arched his back, careful not to slam his back into the seat. Even in great pain, he remembered he was sporting a harness full of sharp points. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What is it?" said Toaku, leaning into the screen with concern. "What happened to your arm?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The move back revealed more of the Captain's injury. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Nothing, nothing. I am recovering."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Get it seen to, man. VendX have the best healthcare equipment in the galaxy, that's what you always told me, isn't it?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"For a price, yes. Sadly, I've used up my quota for the month. Don't be alarmed, I am in no immediate danger." He hissed air out of his mouth. "What's important is that I'm here, as I said I would be. You remember how I told you it was called the mythic package for a reason? That's why I'm here, Ki. With the whole Priority Fleet. We're going to get those machines up and running, even if we have to airdrop our mechanics from orbit."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was a bravura performance. You could take the man out of the sales team, but… &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You came here, in that condition, because…" Toaku was choking up. "It was my arm, last time…"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord wasn't aware of what Toaku was referring to. It wasn't in the records. But the Chairman knew. As he always did.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"That's right," said the Captain. "You pulled me out with only one arm. I can at least do the same for you."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Shared hardship, mutual obligation, parallel empathy. Susceptibility would be off the charts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Current Central Authority directive states that no vessel may—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Damn you," shouted Toaku. "Can't you see how desperate this situation is? Mass panic, half the planet evacuated, our supply chain with neighbouring planets cut. This is all because of you. You allowed those Seneca…" His lips twitched in an attempt to curtail the vitriol trying to get out. "And then you stopped anyone from coming to our aid. Food and water are already running short. Snacks and reasonably priced beverages could save the lives of millions. Let them through!"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Please wait. Consultation in progress." The screen went dark again, Toaku dismissed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord found himself holding his breath. Everything had gone according to plan, but the Central Authority still had the ability to do as they pleased. They had lots of rules to follow but that also meant there was always another path they could take, justified by another series of treaties. At least they weren't dealing with a Guardian. Then there would be no way to tell which way the CA would jump.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The screen flickered back to life. "Passage to Enaya has been authorised."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Thank you," said Captain Maharash, a sigh of relief slipping out of him, although it could just as well be a response to the heavy drug intake he was currently experiencing. "We will begin our approach."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Sending coordinates," said Toaku's voice. "It will be good to see you again, Tareq."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And you. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Executive Order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt; out."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Good work, Captain," said Daccord. "Continue to stage three. I will inform the Chairman."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Wait, I…" The captain's chair swivelled back around. "What am I supposed to say to Ki… Toaku?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It doesn't matter. We aren't going to the planet. Keep an eye on the Central Authority ships. They shouldn't suspect our true purpose here, but if they try to intercept, inform me immediately. And Captain, try to get some rest. The support harness is yours to abuse until this action is over."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Daccord swiped the screen and sent control of the harness to the captain's chair. He left the bridge and took the elevator up to the hospitality blister. He once again had to suffer through the security inspections to make sure he wasn't an assassin, as usual, and then he proceeded to the Chairman's darkened suite. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There were to be no electronically communicated reports between them. Nothing written down or sent digitally. Everything had to be done face to face. Even when it was carried out in the shadows. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They granted permission," said the Chairman's gruff voice from the darkness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes, sir. As you said, they could not refuse our act of professional devotion or our contractual obligation."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Of course they couldn't." There was a smile on the Chairman's face. Unseen but carried in his voice. "The Central Authority worship the legally binding signature. Their respect for their own laws is their greatest weakness." The rumble of laughter filled the far end of the room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Captain Maharash has been the captain of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Executive Order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt; for three years," said Daccord. "He turned out to be the ideal person to win their trust. His injury played its part, as I'm sure you knew it would. A stroke of genius. "&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Are you trying to flatter me, Daccord?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No, sir. I don't believe it is necessary. I am, as always, astonished by your foresight. Nearly four million vending machines collecting personal information on Enaya and its inhabitants, but nowhere in our databanks is there a mention of a shared moment of trauma between our captain and the interim leader of the Enaya Grand Assembly."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No?" said the Chairman. "How very remiss of someone. You have to know what you're looking for, Daccord. Then it's much easier to find."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes, sir." A valuable lesson, but a secret data collection method short of being useful. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The government on Enaya is on the verge of collapse," said the Chairman. "They won't pose a problem. But there is still much to do. And much that can be mishandled." The threat was hard to miss. "Have the Priority Fleet started moving."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes, sir. They are in formation and ready to move with us."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Have the tail-end remain behind the Ruben-Sadar line. Six ships."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Our supply ships? Won't we need them?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Not once we blow them up, no."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A safety measure to take care of the CA ships and the rest of the competition. And all for the low low price of six ships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">499854</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 90: Team Building</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/498933</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Tethari.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Antecessor Facility &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik could tell he had lost the room. It was his showman's instinct letting him know it was time to bring out his A material. If you let the crowd turn on you, it would only get harder and harder to win them back. Especially when you had a tough crowd like this one — no eyes, no ears, not even noses. All the wonderful smells he could produce would do him no good here. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But it wasn't too late. If he found a way to wow them with some premium quality moves, they'd jump right back into your pocket.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Everyone calm down." Ubik raised his hands, one towards the pale creatures incandescent with rage ( literally, they were glowing with an inner white light), and the other hand facing Chukka and Tezla, making sure they felt no need to jump in. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Nothing ruined a good set-up like someone trying to help when you had everything under control or were about to very soon, most probably.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You stupid idiot," hissed Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Wait," said Tezla. "I've seen him worm his way out of worse." Which was enough to stop Chukka from telling Ubik what she thought of him. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik was grateful for the Guardian's intervention. Not because he appreciated her faith in him — faith that was entirely misplaced since he had no idea how he was going to get out of this — but rather because he had no interest in hearing Chukka whine and complain. He definitely wouldn't want her giving his eulogy?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She continued to glare at him like this was all his fault. She was the one who had stolen the crystal pod or whatever it was. He would never have broken it if she hadn't been holding it in the first place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik slowly descended the steps. The creatures had yet to convert their anger into violent action. They were hardly paying Ubik any attention at all, in fact. They were too busy forming a loose cordon around the larval organism that had emerged from inside the shattered crystal, which was now lying in a puddle of its own making on the floor below. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It looked smaller than it had a moment ago.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights from all around the cavernous chamber held steady; bright and revealing. Everything looked so much clearer fully illuminated, and so much worse. Nowhere to hide and nowhere to run without being seen. Hardly the ideal staging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This isn't as bad as it looks," said Ubik, tilting his words up at the walls. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;That was where the eyes and ears were. The other crystal pods embedded in the walls of the chamber held some kind of unified intelligence. They thought as one, commanded the pale creatures as one. All he had to do was convince them everything was okay and then the rest would fall into place. Easy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik jumped down the last few steps, landed in a crouch and picked up the prematurely freed organism. It was translucent grey, with ridges covering its long, slippery body. He stood up and held it over his head, squeezing it gently so it would slide out of his grasp. It bulged and rippled either side of his hand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lower end hanging limp whipped sharply around his wrist and slithered tongue-like around his bare forearm. Ubik felt multiple tiny needles try to pierce his skin, then ease off, then try again. Then the whole body went slack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It's fine. It's alive." Ubik shook it a little bit to make it look like it was still moving. "Even the colour's coming back. See?" It was turning a darker grey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;None of the creatures attacked him, which was a surprise; a welcome one. This was going better than he'd expected. Something dribbled down his arm but Ubik ignored it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The creatures stepped back. There was something in the way they moved that suggested to Ubik that not only were they not going to attack him, they were thinking about running away.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was then that it occurred to Ubik how strange it was for them to have stood watching their defenceless little responsibility die. They might be of alien origin but, usually, when the thing you're trying to protect falls on the ground, you rush to pick it up. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;That had not happened.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;You could put it down to shock. You could also put it down to fear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik looked up at the thing in his hand. It wasn't moving. It was about the length of his forearm, if it was stretched out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Why aren't they attacking him?" said Chukka. There was a disappointed edge to her voice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I don't know," said Tezla. "I think they expected him to die." She nodded towards the creatures. They were crouching and edging forward now, but leaning back as they did it, the way you might if you were trying to approach something that might explode at any moment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"From this?" said Ubik, lowering his hand. The creatures shuffled backwards. "This isn't as bad as it looks. I've fished out a lot worse from the sewers back home."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka made a disgusted face. She looked over at the Guardian, who winced. These were people unused to living an unrefined life. Ubik really didn't understand how people like them expected to understand the universe without looking in the dark places.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The voice of Chukka's despondent subordinate came wailing from the other side of the chamber. "Get me out of here. The wall's eating me." Which didn't even make sense. Typical VendX exaggeration. Anything to make a sale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hold on," said Ubik. "We'll get to you in a moment." He took a closer look at the thing in his hand. With everyone on pause, now was a great time to figure out what to do next. It was these quiet moments when everyone was too horrified to move that Ubik was able to really shine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was soft and rubbery. It had no appendages or openings. It looked like a snake or an eel. Something that lived underwater. Or perhaps in the depths of space. His eyes lit up. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I know what this is. It's a baby space whale!" He looked up at the walls. "Am I right?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights on the walls dimmed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No?" said Ubik, disappointed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Space whales don't exist," said Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Not finding something doesn't prove its non-existence," said Ubik. "Open your mind, Guardian."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It's an organic," said Tezla, mind resolutely contained inside that bald head of hers. "A big one. Rex confirms it." Her eyes flashed from side to side, seeing sensor readings on her HUD. "It probably can't do anything to you because you're Null Void."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It wasn't a bad guess. Ubik had never actually seen an organic before they were inserted into a person's DNA, but he knew they were smaller than this. A lot smaller. But what if they grew to this size under the right conditions? Conditions humans hadn't been able to replicate, so they put the immature forms into themselves and assumed that was the final product. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;How much more powerful would they become if their organics were as developed as this one? Would that power be controllable?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Isn't it a little big to be an organic?" said Chukka. She kept her eyes on Ubik's wrist. She couldn't take her eyes off it. The look wasn't one of disgust or fear, it was something else. Something more like avarice. What did she think? That she could get him to smuggle it out of here and then she'd claim it off his corpse to offer to her superiors in exchange for a promotion? Wage-slaves were so predictable — always looking to please their masters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It's bigger, but it has the same basic structure," said Tezla. "Rex's readings are conclusive. It was trying to find a way to get inside Ubik's body, but it couldn't. If it got inside an appropriate host, it would be able to assimilate rapidly, far more efficiently than we're capable of. After that… who knows?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"How could something that large get inside a person?" said Chukka. "It would kill them."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You're assuming it needs all of the person," said Tezla. "If it takes over the host body, it might only need rudimentary functions to work."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik held the organic up to his face. The lower end jumped into his mouth. He spat it. The tapered tip shot up his left nostril. Ubik blew it out and then sneezed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I think you're wrong," said Chukka. "It just wants to kill him."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hmm," said Tezla, like she was seconding the motion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I think you're right," said Ubik, holding his arm as far from his face as possible. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Which one of us?" asked Chukka. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Both of you," said Ubik. "I think it wants to find a host and I think it wants to kill me. That's it. That's what we have to do." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Let it kill you?" asked Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No, find it a host."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It's an alien parasite that will overwhelm its host and run rampant with an unknown level of power," said Tezla. "We're not here to speed up the end of humanity."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You're looking at this situation very negatively, Guardian."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You'd like to give the end of humanity a positive spin?" asked Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oobie wouldn't end humanity, would you Oobie." He held up the flaccid organism and it lashed out at him again. "See?" said Ubik, dodging. "Harmless. Mostly."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"He's named it after himself," said Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No. The spelling's completely different."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights on the wall flickered, some message that was near impossible to decipher. Ubik closed one eye. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I think they like my idea."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Can you get us down now?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"One minute, Bashir," said Chukka. "You want to implant that thing inside someone and let it take them over? Who? Who's going to let you do that?" She was more curious than objecting to his idea.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik gave her a long look. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"She has an organic already," said Tezla. "Very weak but her receptors are blocked."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka seemed surprised by the Guardian's declaration, but she didn't deny it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"So do those three."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik looked over at the Seneca women and Chukka's friend stuck in the wall. So not anyone already with an organic. He turned his gaze to the Guardian.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It won't work with a cloned body," she said before he had a chance to say anything.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights flickered. They were getting impatient. Then the lights pulsed rapidly. Ubik couldn't follow them at all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik?" A voice filled the chamber, scattering light across the walls.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"PT?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes. What are you doing? Why aren't the goblins attacking you?" &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Goblins? Them?" Ubik gave the creatures a look. "Why would they attack me? We're practically family."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We have incoming. More goblins. Advanced ones. Those ones are supposed to be a defence against them, but now you've neutralised them I guess we'll have to come up with another way to protect ourselves."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They aren't neutralised, they're just resting. Right, guys?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The goblins didn't move. They could have been made of marble.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What are you holding?" said PT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hm? Nothing." He put his hand behind his back. "I've got a hangnail. By the way, you have a high CQ, don't you? And you don't have an organic or anything, right?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Why do you ask?" said PT, his voice thinning into suspicion. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oh, no reason," said Ubik. "You still in the same place? We'll come to you. I've got something to show you."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Well, you better hurry up. I'm seeing more new arrivals and they're headed down here. They seem to be heavily armed. Central Authority and VendX and a bunch of others."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Finally," said Guardian Tezla. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Have you been stalling all this time?" said Ubik. "That why you've been so agreeable? Waiting for reinforcements? You've got to learn to work with what you've got, Guardian."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Rex, activate a beacon." She paused. "Rex?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oh, don't worry about him," said Ubik. "He's probably busy or something."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What have you done to Rex?" said the Guardian. She sounded as suspicious as PT. If he didn't know better, he'd guess they'd been practising together. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We better get moving." The lights dimmed, the goblins twitched. "Okay. You up in the walls, this is it. The moment you fulfil your destiny. I know they left you here in forever-sleep, forgotten. Your wait is over. I'll be back for the rest of you after I find a good home for Oobie. Be ready."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I think he's working for the enemy," said Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Or they're working for him. Rex. Rex, come online. The scan was clear. Reboot, damn it." Tezla slapped the side of her helmet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik turned to look at the goblins. The name suited them. A deaf, blind army, but they might have their uses. They couldn't hear him but he felt he should say something. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"My Grandma always used to say to me, 'Work hard, play later,' but she would also say, "Play hard, work later.' Then she said, 'Work play, hard later,' which was when I realised she had a corrupt file in her voice matrix. So I deleted that file and now she's a lot less bossy. Okay, that's the commencement speech over. Follow me to victory."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik raised a fist in the way he imagined generals of old would galvanize their troops. The goblins showed no reaction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They can't hear or see you," said Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They don't need to." Ubik tapped the side of his head. "We have a connection. Let's go boys. Or girls." He checked them for any signs of sexual organs. Not even a hint of a bulge anywhere, top or bottom. "Let's go… people."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They aren't people," said Chukka. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Bigot. This way." He took a step up the stairs and looked back. None of the goblins moved to follow him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What about us?" called out Bashir plaintively. "You can't just leave us here."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a loud crash as part of the wall on the far side crumbled and the two Seneca women walked out like it had been a bank of snow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You could have freed yourselves all this time?" said Ubik.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No point being free if you don't have an exit planned," said Weyla, brushing herself off.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The Corps trains you to be patient and find the right moment to act," said Leyla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Does the Corps train you to wait until a man comes along and saves you, too?" asked Ubik as the two women approached through the goblins who remained impassive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Four women now surrounded him. For the first time, he noticed that all four were taller than him. He didn't like it. The strain on his neck was already becoming painful.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"One moment," said Ubik. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He made his way to through the goblins, all of whom were shorter than him, to the wall where Bashir had been entombed alive. He brushed away some loose rock and then tried to break Bashir out but one hand was wrapped in alien rubbery flesh, and the other hand made little impression on the granite-hard surface.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Little help?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Pale hands emerged around him and pulled pieces of rock away from the wall. In a few seconds, Bashir stumbled free. He fell to his knees and then jumped back to his feet, startled by the faceless goblins crowded around him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Calm down, they won't eat you. No mouths. They can strangle you at best. Would take ages with a fat neck like yours. Are you hurt?" There was dried blood on the man's regulation VendX-issue suit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"She… shot me," said Bashir.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The suit stabilised you, didn't it?" said Chukka, sounding annoyed at the accusation. "It was a calculated risk, which saved your life. Don't make me amend your report."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The suit had self-sealed over a hole in the chestplate. These kinds of suits were cheap and basic, but they did have basic life-sustain features in case of injuries. More cost-effective to bring employees back wounded and alive, and then terminate their contract, than to pay out the life-insurance VendX made them subscribe to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Listen," said Ubik in a lowered voice, "there's four of them but two of us, plus my boys. Or whatever. If things get rough and the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;ladies &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;turn on us, it's you and me, bro. I'll take care of Chukka — I know you're contractually obligated not to attack your supervisor — you handle the other three. You with me?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," said Bashir, shaking his head vigorously.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They may all be deaf and blind," said Weyla, "but we're not."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Huh?" said Ubik, turning around sharply. "I was just kidding." He looked back at Bashir and whispered, "Wait for my signal."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Bashir shook his head even more vigorously.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik returned to the stairs and headed up. This time the goblins followed, calmly and in orderly fashion. The four women stepped aside to let them pass. Chukka stared greedily at his alien-encircled arm. Tezla scowled at him while trying to get Rex back online. Weyla and Leyla took turns checking their weapons while making sure one of them had eyes on Ubik at all times.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik smiled to himself. One would be easily distracted, one wouldn't be able to trust her own suit, and two would stay close enough to him to provide him with a convenient shield. He could work with that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">498933</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 89: Lady Eats Tiger</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/496657</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Tethari.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Inner Core.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figaro had been taught to maintain control over his body and mind in extreme conditions. He could recognise his environment, the approximate geography and physical conditions, even when blindfolded and disoriented. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He could calm his breathing and lower his heartbeat in the most strenuous of circumstances, enabling him to isolate his senses and identify the tiniest details in his surroundings. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;His tutors had put him through severe training, more akin to torture, to heighten his ability to read and analyse any terrain using whatever limited form of detection was available to him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Touch, smell, sound, fluctuations in electrical impulses, the tastes of differently proportioned air  — he had extensive schooling in how to make the most of all of his senses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He had no idea where he was right now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Alone in the vast darkness and moving towards something, that was about all he knew for sure. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He wasn't falling and he wasn't flying. His trajectory wasn't downwards, although it was in the direction his feet were pointing. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He was aware of movement, of rushing in a distinct direction, but other than that he was blind and felt nothing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;PT had picked him up and sent him into an opening he had seemingly created in the Intercessors' stronghold. An act that required PT to exert a profound level of influence on a domain under the control of an alien power for thousands of years, or an indication that the Intercessors had yielded their control for reasons of their own.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The force that had enveloped him and pushed him into the opening was now gone, as was any indication that PT's influence was still present.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The force now controlling his movements came from below or beyond or whatever the direction was. Figaro had no way of affecting it. He was at the mercy of whatever was now directing his motion through the darkness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;PT had said there was an area hidden from his sight at the very centre of the asteroid and he assumed that was where he was headed. It was a big assumption considering how many times the asteroid had upended his expectations. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There were many intelligences vying for control here and they were all far more proficient at it than he was. He was well aware of how foolish it was for him to try and play these old masters at their own game, his father included.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But his father was here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figaro had stopped relying on what the sensors in his suit had been telling him, or what those who were vying for mastery of the asteroid wanted him to believe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was one place in the asteroid that PT could not see, and there was no sign of his father anywhere else. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Another trick, another deception? Possibly. Figaro was learning how easy it was to be fooled, and the lessons kept coming.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;One of his earliest memories was the riddle of the Lady and the Tiger. An old fable about a criminal given the chance to earn his freedom by choosing one of two doors. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Behind each door there was either a lady or a tiger. One he would marry and be set free, the other he would be killed and eaten.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;On each door was a sign, one true, one false. A simple logic puzzle to deduce what was behind each door. But that wasn't the lesson of the story. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;If you are given the option of two doors to choose from, know that there are always more than just two doors. They are hiding the others from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;If one option seems much better than the other, know that both options benefit them and neither benefit you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;And if one option is death in the mouth of a tiger, then both doors will contain tigers, no matter what their signs tell you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;How to solve this thought experiment had consumed many hours of discussion with his tutors. But his tutors hadn't taken one thing into account.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Antecessors, the Intercessors, the Central Authority and the Seneca Corps, even his father, they might be able to carefully manoeuvre Figaro into thinking what they wanted. Trick him into choosing the path they wanted him to take — those sorts of manipulations had been familiar to him throughout his life and avoiding them was a fruitless task. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But this was different. This wasn't Figaro having to choose between two options, both of which were planted to produce the same result, neither to his advantage. This was a path chosen by Ubik. And Ubik was immune to the whims of others. No matter how subtle, no matter how coercive. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik would find a way to open both doors. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tigers don't like each other. And if you happen to be wrong and one door does have a lady behind it, then a tiger eating a girl isn't eating you. Either way, new plans would need to be made.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figaro had faith in Ubik. He had faith that no one had prepared for him. You couldn't threaten him, you couldn't extort him, you couldn't bribe him. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;When presented with an option that would give him what he wanted, cost him nothing, protected his interests and punished his opponents, Ubik wouldn't even consider it as one of his top three choices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was no more stark example of this than Ubik creating a way to take over the Intercessor network and then putting PT in charge of it. Ubik simply had better things to do with his time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Now PT had access to everything the Antecessors and Intercessors were fighting over, giving him the ability to see everywhere they could. Something he could never have done on his own, so there was never any reason to prepare a contingency for such an eventuality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;For Ubik, the lady and the tiger were just prospective partner and pet. And you didn't even know which would be which.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Even if the Intercessors had allowed him to be sent here, choosing to let PT assume command of the asteroid, there would definitely be something of interest here. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;And his father had a way of finding his way to the places where interesting things were happening. He was attracted to them just as they were attracted to him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Even as a child, Figaro had recognised that being around his father meant being around the densest element other elements were drawn to. Whether it was powerful people, momentous events, or his mother. They all came to his father, driven to him by some invisible quality of the universe. Just as he was being drawn into the dark interior of the asteroid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But he didn't see himself as having any other choice. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The fate arranged for him was not one he considered palatable. Even if the fate of the quadrant hung on it, Figaro's years of training in duty and sacrifice were not strong enough to make him willingly accept the wisdom of his elders and betters. His education had been too broad and all-encompassing to simply take the word of others on faith, his father included.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It did feel like a failure on his part. He couldn't help the way he'd been conditioned. But the way he had come to terms with it was to prove he had a better way. A thousand people walking the same path made it a clear path, it didn't necessarily make it the right way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figaro had rejected his assigned fate, but he would save his father and defeat the Antecessors. It seemed like the best way to prove his decision was the right one.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Even though he could see nothing, Figaro moved his head as much as the force gripping him would allow. His knowledge of the asteroid, its dimensions and construction, gave him a good idea of how far it was to the asteroid's core. Judging his velocity was difficult without anything to use as reference, but he guessed by the tension within his body that it was at least 2G, possibly more. He estimated it would take two minutes at most before he encountered what was hidden at the dark centre of this rock.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The pull was increasing and the temperature was going up. There had never been a heat signature from this deep inside the asteroid according to the many readings taken by his father's instruments. For all his deliberations about what he might find at the core of the asteroid, he might end up a shrivelled husk before he even got there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The sense of movement ended and his feet touched a solid surface. The darkness continued to be absolute, but there was something obstructing his way forward.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Perhaps he had reached the centre? It didn't feel any different in terms of power. He moved his feet, tapping gently, trying to get an idea of what he was standing on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Smooth. Firm. Curved. Smashed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It shattered under him and he fell. This was proper falling, accompanied by a rush of wind across his body. The air entered his mouth and nose. It was breathable, high oxygen content. He began to feel light-headed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;His body became hotter, from the inside. His eyes felt like they were burning. His entire skeletal structure increased in density. He was losing control of his organic. It was activating at a speed and intensity like never before. He would have burst into a billion tiny pieces if the bracelet on his arm hadn't suddenly inflicted a terrific amount of pain into him, washing the organic back into the cells of his body. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was like being brought to the edge of an explosion and then having it subdued in an instant so that there was nothing left. Dr Yune's device had saved him from certain annihilation. He had helped Figaro throughout his life, taken care of him, and then turned on him. The man had betrayed him and saved him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figaro saw no conflict in the two sides of Dr Yune.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Betrayal was nothing personal. Both he and Mackus had seen it as the more prudent option to take Figaro's birthright away from him. They had their reasons and they may well have been correct. Figaro understood that sometimes betrayal was justified. Even necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It won't work," said Figaro. "You can't make me transform while I am wearing this." He held up his arm in the darkness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It does not wish to," said his father's voice. Was it really his father, though? Figaro couldn't say for certain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Their ability to mimic was excellent. Figaro had been caught by surprise and failed to spot the differences. There weren't many and those that there were, could be considered within abnormal parameters — extreme condition, a unique situation, huge mental stress, a mountain of variables. His father &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;could &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;have reacted the way the Intercessors played him. And Figaro's own issues dealing with the situation were a valid excuse for his mistakes. But they were still excuses. Ubik hadn't been fooled, and he had never met Ramon Ollo.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The wise move was to assume the worst. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Where am I?" Figaro asked.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"At the centre of the asteroid. Or as close as you can get without being destroyed. There are several layers of protection around a microscopic black hole at the very centre. The asteroid was built around it, as a containment vessel. It's a rather elegant design."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It certainly sounded like his father.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Where are you... Father?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You sound uncertain of who I am."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Who are you?" asked Figaro.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I am no longer Ramon Ollo. Why did you come here, Figaro? You cannot save me."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Where is your body?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"On the seventh level. It is nothing more than an empty receptacle now."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Is it alive?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes. Physically."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"But your mind is here?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Part of my mind is here. Other parts are elsewhere. But it no longer belongs to me. Everything I know, have ever known, is now part of the Intercessors. They have only allowed this small part of me to remain in order to communicate with you."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And the Ramon Ollo I encountered above?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"That was also me. A more constrained version. They know me well enough to keep me on a leash."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"But not here?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No. There is no need. Here, we can do very little. The power inside the black hole is not one that can be resisted. You will be kept here until they can find a way to unlock the power within you." He sighed. "It will be my task to make that happen."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I thought they didn't want the power to be released."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Not in the way it was meant to be used by the Antecessors. But if they can extract it whole, they have other uses for it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I can get you out, Father. If I can return you to your body, we can leave this place. I have friends who can take control of the asteroid."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What you're suggesting isn't possible, Figaro. I am dispersed throughout the asteroid now. To remove me would create a void that wouldn't be sustainable. It would destroy us both."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Isn't that preferable to being kept as prisoners?" said Figaro.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," said his father.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figaro paused to think. He had come here to find his father and he had succeeded. He had expected to face obstacles to the rescue but the biggest obstacle was his father himself. He would need to tempt him with something he wanted even more than the knowledge he might gain by being the captive of the Intercessors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What if we replace you with an alternative, to fill the gap. You could retain a place in the asteroid but you would also be free to leave."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a long pause before Ramon Ollo said, "What do you suggest?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Me. I could take your place. Isn't that why they allowed me to come here?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The bracelet on your wrist makes you a worthless substitution. They thought they could break it here, where their power is strongest, but Dr Yune has confounded them." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Figaro could almost hear the smile in his father's voice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What if I replaced you with someone else?" said Figaro. "Someone who has also become part of the asteroid."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"There is someone like that?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;This aspect of his father was not aware of what was happening above. He didn't know that PT had already been inserted into the Intercessor framework.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Of course, PT would not be willing to simply take his father's place. And after all they had experienced together, it would be an ignoble deed to force him to do so. But sometimes betrayal was necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">496657</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 88: Peace Offering</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/495755</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Tethari.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Antecessor Facility &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik quickly took in Chukka's appearance. Alone, dishevelled, clinging tightly to an object she was trying to hide. It was clear the large blue crystal was important to her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What is that? Can I have a look?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka gripped the object tighter, moving it to the side and partly behind her. There was a flash of wild calculation in her eyes. She was going through her options at breakneck speed, searching for the right lie to tell. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik liked her. Whenever she was in a tight spot, giving up was never an option. The only thought in her head was how to turn things to her advantage. She was like a gambler who doubled their bet every time they lost. A reckless and idiotic approach, but hugely rewarding if you managed to pull it off. Ubik would never make that mistake, though. Quadruple the bet or why even bother playing?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Nothing, it's nothing." She was looking past Ubik now, at the Guardian looming behind him, her eyes widening, then narrowing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Where are my manners?" said Ubik. "This is Guardian Tezla of the Central Authority. Major Chukka of the VendX Corporation."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We've met," said Tezla, her face mask hissing as it slid up. "You're still alive. Good. Why are you down here? What happened to the others? Dead?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Most likely," said Chukka, her resentment overflowing. "Thanks to you. Found your target, did you? I'm sure they'll give you a pay rise when you take him back."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We don't get paid," said Tezla. "And only you survived, you say. How fortunate."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You have no idea the horrors I've faced after you abandoned us. Why are you still here? Shouldn't you get him out before someone takes him from you?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm sensing some kind of history here," said Ubik, glancing from one to the other. "Wait, did you both come here looking for me? Is this going to be one of those two women fight over a man things?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," said Chukka and Tezla together.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Well, I don't like to be objectified like that, but go ahead. I'll be the prize. Winner takes all. Maybe take off the suits so you can move around a bit more freely."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka glared at him. Then her eyes looked him up and down. "Why aren't you wearing a suit?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No need," said Ubik, patting down his clothes. "You don't want to get too dependent on tech, like some people." He pointed surreptitiously at the Guardian in her battlesuit. "Addicted to high-grade explosives. Watch out for her when you've got her in a clinch, she'll probably try to blow your head off with one of her little rockets."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We don't have time to fight," said the Guardian, getting tetchy again. "We need to get out of here as quickly as possible." She had been moaning about the importance of getting clear of the asteroid and calling in help ever since PT had sent them off.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"We're here to find these creatures, remember?" said Ubik. "Don't you want to meet the aliens?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm taking you out of here," said Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Same thing," said Ubik pointing past Chukka's shoulder. "The way out's this way too. Down here and up a bit."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," said Chukka sharply. "Not that way. There's no way out that way." She was shaking and her face had paled. "You'll only find death and monsters. You mustn't… you can't..."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A grin of delight appeared on Ubik's face. "Oh, that's good. That's really good. The way your skin changed colour, how do you do that? Some kind of implant? And the shaky voice and everything. Really nice work."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What are you talking about? I'm serious. There are real monsters down there. Not droids."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Good, isn't she?" Ubik said to Tezla. "I bet the higher-ups at VendX have got their eyes on her. Commitment, that's what you have to have to get to the top in the business world. Let's go see these 'monsters' then."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Listen to me, you idiot," snarled Chukka. "You'll die if you go that way. You will be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;devoured&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;." She made a real meal of the last word to make her point. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"These monsters," said Ubik, "they don't have mouths, do they? Hard to devour anyone without a mouth." He chomped his teeth at her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka looked up at Tezla with a mixture of stunned and baffled beautifully painted across her face. "Why are you letting him lead you into the jaws of death?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They don't have jaws, either," said Ubik.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The way out is through there," said Tezla in measured tones. She wasn't very happy about letting Ubik lead, either. "My suit's AI confirms it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Your suit's AI is wrong, then," said Chukka. "Or…" She looked at Ubik. "Or he's done something to it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You think I haven't thought of that?" snapped Tezla. "I've double-checked. It's through there."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You're both going to die. Well, good luck to you. I'm going that way." Chukka pointed past Ubik and Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"So good," said Ubik. "Managed to make it all about who's going where just to deflect from my question about that thing she's got tucked under your arm. Can I have a look now?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What is wrong with you?" said Chukka. "Not everyone's putting on act just because you are."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik pulled a face suggesting he had no idea what point she was trying to make. "I admire the persistence but I've seen people get upset a lot. I mean, I've seen it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt; a lot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;. People get upset around me all the time. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;All &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;the time. Men, women, children. Sometimes even drones, and they don't have the circuits for it. I know what it looks like when somone's panicking for real and when they're trying to deflect. And you're deflecting like crazy." Ubik smiled at her. She was calculating again. "Rex must have run an analysis by now. Anything interesting?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Rex?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Unable to identify. Readings are inconclusive. Material is unknown."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tezla turned her keen gaze onto Chukka. "What is it? No more pretending."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm not pretending," said Chukka, taking a step back. She took a breath. Whatever she'd decided, here it came. "This is the only thing that saved me. I don't want to give it to you because I'll die without it. You have your suit and he has… whatever it is that keeps him alive when he should have died a hundred times already. They… the monsters… they won't attack me while I've got this. They're afraid of damaging it, which means they'll leave me alone while I've got it. It doesn't matter what is — I don't even know, and I don't care. This is the only thing keeping me alive and you can't have it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She gripped the object even tighter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Now that," said Ubik, "I believe."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka's eyes filled with relief for a moment, quickly draining away. "You're still going to take it from me." Her lips tightened into a thin line.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Me?" said Ubik. "No, never. I wouldn't steal your hard-won treasure. Who knows how many people died so you could walk out of here with that thing. It's all yours as far as I'm concerned. Guardian?" He looked up and back at Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Anything found inside this asteroid is the property of Ramon Ollo," said Tezla. "You aren't authorised to remove it or damage it in any way, not as a private individual and not as an employee of VendX Galactic."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oh, yeah," said Ubik. "There is that. Better put it back where you found it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I told you," said Chukka. "This is the only way to protect myself. I'm claiming it as an emergency measure, on humanitarian grounds."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Your presence here is illegitimate," said Tezla. "You do not have the right to claim anything."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You could," said Ubik, "come with us and then relinquish it before we leave. You could."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I could," said Chukka, eyeing Ubik through narrowed eyes, more calculations rapidly being performed. "But are you really sure this is the shortest route to the surface. You do want to get out of here, don't you? You don't plan on going deeper."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Of course," said Tezla. "We will return to the surface and then we will contact the Central Authority vessels on the perimeter to pick us up."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And this is the way?" Chukka still seemed reluctant to go back the way she'd come. Ubik couldn't wait to find out why.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This is the way," he said. "Right, Rex?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This is the way," said Rex in a flat monotone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And what about the monsters?" asked Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Monster is such a negative term," said Ubik. "I'm sure they're quite reasonable once you get to know them."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He set off down the tunnel, confident she would follow. She wasn't lying about the monsters but she would go back. She was relying on her monsters to take care of him and the Guardian. It was the only way she would be able to leave with the object she so desperately clung to. Whatever it was, she was willing to go back into harm's way to make sure no one took it from her. It had to be something good. The monsters wouldn't hurt her while she was holding it, that was what she'd said. The same was not true for Ubik and the Guardian. Not a bad plan. A very Chukka plan. Ubik smiled to himself — not as good as his plan. Once he thought of one, of course.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The end of the tunnel wasn't very far, and then he emerged into a large domed chamber. Instead of the smooth, curving walls in the tunnel, these walls were rough and uneven, covered with bulges and ripples. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;This place hadn't been carved out of the rock by droids. Something more animalistic had dug and clawed this place into existence, but in a deliberate and exacting manner. Sculpted by inhuman hands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was definitely a purpose to it, a very specific purpose. This was a hub, created to amplify some kind of signal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik liked it. He had spent a lot of time underground and knew a safe bolt hole when he saw one. This place wouldn't fall on your head. It was nicely balanced, plenty of room, lots of grips. It was designed to be climbed for access. Access to what?. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Lights flashed around him. They weren't streaks of white like in other parts of the facility, these were dots of colour spread out at random. His eyes followed the pattern as they jumped back and forth, twinkling like stars. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A deep rumble attracted his attention down. At the foot of the steps was a gathering of white, faceless creatures. They had a bizarre appearance, helpless and handicapped. They swarmed together, bumping into one another in their blindness. But Ubik wasn't frightened by them. It was hard to be sure, but he didn't think they were here for him. Their focus seemed to be directed towards Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hello!" said Ubik, seeing no reason not to be friendly. "Nice to meet you. I'm Ubik, this is Guardian Tezla. Chukka, you already know."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The rumble stopped for a moment, leaving a confused silence, and then it returned as a quieter hum. They didn't attack, which was the important thing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They don't have ears," whispered Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Then why are you whispering?" said Ubik. "I wasn't talking to them, anyway." He pointed at the walls where the flashing lights had become much more active. His finger traced the pattern from one light to the next, all the way to the object in Chukka's arms, which pulsed a dull blue.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You came back!" called out a voice from somewhere across the chamber.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes," said Chukka, her tone a little hesitant. "I brought help."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You said everyone was dead," said Tezla, grimly understating the accusation that was implied.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No, I said they probably were," said Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You were going to abandon them," said the Guardian.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I don't think you have the right to lecture anyone on that score," said Chukka. "At least I came back."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was a deft move, making herself appear like the one who wanted to return, rather than the one insisting they didn't.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik," said another voice, this one female and insistent. "Come over here."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Sorry, do I know you?" said Ubik, unable to see the owner of the voice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik, you little shit," said another female voice, "get us out of here."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And then?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"And then we'll get you off this rock."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He knew who it was — the two sisters — but why were they here? It could only be to grab him or Fig.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What about Fig?" he asked.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Him too," said… Weyla?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Well, thanks, but we're not ready to leave," said Ubik. "We're actually settling in very nicely. Might even make the move permanent. Might not look it right now, but this could become the premier vacation spot in this quadrant." He redirected his gaze towards the walls where lights were pulsing wildly. Something was about to happen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik turned his head towards Chukka and the Guardian. "I'm going to go down and have a word with the boys. See if we can't come to an understanding."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka shook her head. "You're insane."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Where is the way out?" demanded Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I can see you're both worried about my welfare, but please don't worry. I'll be fine."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You're a dead man," said Chukka.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Where is the exit," said Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Just one thing," said Ubik. "Can I borrow that?" He reached his hand towards the crystal pod in Chukka's arms. She instinctively pulled back.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'll give it back," said Ubik. "The Guardian will keep you safe until then." He looked at the Guardian, encouraging her to back him up. She shook her head.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," repeated Chukka, wrapping both arms around the crystal and pulling it into her chest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Give it to him," said Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka turned to give the same answer to Tezla. Ubik chose that moment to lunge forwards and grab the crystal. Chukka leaned out of range and tripped over the step behind her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik managed to whip the crystal out of her grip as she stumbled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Thanks, I'll take good care—" and then juggled it as the smooth surface he wasn't expecting slid out of his grasp, smashing on the floor into tiny pieces, an oily liquid wetting his boots and something dark and wriggly slithered down the steps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights around the chamber all lit up at the same time. For the first time, Ubik could see across the entire chamber and the three people embedded into the far wall, only their heads and hands showing. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What did you do?" said Chukka, her voice genuinely panicked as the creatures began climbing the steps towards them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oops," said Ubik.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">495755</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 87: Sending a Message</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/493530</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Tethari.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Antecessor Facility &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka held the weapon steadily pointed at the bulge in the wall. She was threatening a rock, and it was working.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Don't move, don't come any closer." She waved the gun menacingly. The pod she was pointing at glowed a dim blue colour and the creatures amassed around her eased back from their attack postures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They wanted to rip her to pieces, tear her limb from limb, she could feel it, but they daren't.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Her message was getting across. They understood basic intimidation tactics. Blackmail. Extortion. She was building a whole lexicon she could use to make first contact with these aliens. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was interesting seeing how they moved. They responded as a unit, perfectly coordinated. That would be useful. She didn't have to work on them each individually — get one to do her bidding and the rest would follow. Basic grunts. Used to doing as they were told. The ideal audience for her particular set of skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She didn't think the creatures were the ones making the decisions, though. No eyes, no ears, no mouths. They had to be getting information from somewhere. The pod next to her glowed and set off another cascade of coloured lights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The creatures nearest her retreated to give her a little more room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The pods embedded in the walls somehow told the creatures to back off. Some kind of telepathic communication? Maybe vibrations they could sense?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka looked around at the other pods glowing in sympathy with the one kissing her gun's muzzle, at the creatures slowly shuffling to encircle her, at the other three — Weyla, Leyla, Bashir — pinned down under mounds of pale white flesh. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Their weapons were useless against these things. Even the Seneca women had no way to break free. But Chukka had shown her superiority.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Now everyone was waiting for her to make her next move. Everyone had given Chukka their attention and full authority to call the shots. This was executive power, the most potent force in any fight. She liked it. Live or die by your own choices. This was what it meant to be a leader.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Her job right now was to analyse each variable as quickly as possible and find a way to use it to dominate the situation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The strange creatures that had emerged from the ground had stopped in their tracks as soon as she aimed her gun at what, presumably, was some form of living being.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She could see there was something moving inside the translucent pods and it seemed a safe assumption that they were alive. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;That was why the creatures — pale, faceless, violent — weren't currently ripping her to shreds. They didn't want her to kill their precious babies or siblings or masters or whatever they were. That told Chukka a lot about what she was dealing with, and how to manipulate them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A select group chosen to put their own lives at risk in service of these 'eggs'. That told her the eggs were vulnerable and weak. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The creatures looked to her to be newly awoken. Units designed for long periods of hibernation followed by intense periods of violent wakefulness. That fit into what she had seen so far. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;One job, one purpose. Unable to think laterally or to consider alternatives. Protect the eggs at all costs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The more she thought about it, the more human their thinking seemed. Low-level human thinking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;If they thought and felt and feared, then they were the same as the customers Chukka had been trained to deal with. They wanted to keep these things safe, and were willing to sacrifice themselves to do so. They weren't willing to allow a single one of their charges to suffer if they could avoid it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;If they jumped her now, she could destroy one or two at most before she was overpowered. They wouldn't do it. They didn't dare. A terrible negotiating position to be in, as all the textbooks on the subject would tell you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;What she had to do now was find a way to communicate with them. A gun to the head spoke volumes, but she needed to be a little more subtle if she was going to get further than an eternal stalemate. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A stand-off with no end never benefitted the person in control, it only gave everyone else time to improve their situation. She might have the advantage for now, but these things probably didn't sleep or eat or shit. They didn't appear to have any orifices at all. They could wait until she started to get tired and then take her out. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Finding an exit was what she needed to focus on. Out of here with one of these pods in her possession. Empty-handed would be easier, but what good would that do her? No point finding a treasure of unlimited worth just to leave it behind. This was the big one and she had no intention of walking away from it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was even better than the organic tree they'd come across earlier. That would have made her a fortune, but this would make her a player in the big leagues. This opportunity could not be passed up. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Tell them to back off," said Bashir, his voice muffled and shaking. She could just see his eyes through the bodies on top of him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Quiet. I'm handling this." This was no time to allow suggestions. It was never time for that if you wanted to maintain a strong leadership.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Stop thinking about taking one of those things with you," said Weyla, eyes bright red, straining as she rose from the ground, a pile of white bodies covering her. "They won't let you leave with it." She sounded irritated. Not liking the feeling of having her life in someone else's hand. Good. Chukka hadn't given up on extending her influence over the Seneca sisters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They won't let us leave no matter what," said Chukka. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Leyla slowly began to rise, her weapon in her hand. "Get out of here while you can."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The creatures made a rumbling sound that seemed to come from their chests as they slammed both sisters back to the ground. There were dozens of them. More were emerging all the time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka was the only one still standing. She would like to keep it that way. "We need to take one of these things with us." Chukka waved her gun at the pod. "It's our only insurance."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"How?" said Weyla, limbs wrapped around her throat. "They're stuck in the wall. And I don't think they'll like you trying to dig one out."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You have a better idea?" snapped Chukka. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights dimly glowing around them, up the walls and across the chamber, began to pulse, and then strobe in patterns. The creatures around her shifted their body-weight, taking a different stance, as though hunkering down. Chukka stiffened.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Communicating was happening. They were about to make their move and Chukka had yet to come up with a way out of here. The surprise of being attacked and the shock of what they had been attacked by had cost her valuable seconds. She would be forced to react and give up the initiative.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights went out at exactly the same time and the chamber was plunged into darkness save for the light from her suit, showing only the wall. She didn't want to lose her target. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka expected to be attacked. Her finger on the trigger tightened. She didn't want to destroy her only bargaining chip, it would only get her killed. But she had limited options.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a scream.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights from the walls glowed brighter and revealed Bashir standing, propped up by creatures still wrapped around him like a bizarre wedding dress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;His eyes were wild and terrified. His body shook. "Help…" he wheezed. His eyes bulged as his neck was squeezed by several thin white hands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Fast learners. They were using her own methods against her. Dumb. Making assumptions that she would react the same way as them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka moved the gun swiftly and shot Bashir. He buckled and let out a strangled cry before going limp.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights on the wall went crazy, blinking and flashing. Now they understood. Here was the message she wanted to get across to them. They weren't the same. There wasn't going to be an exchange of goods. No refunds. All sales were final.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The creatures let Bashir drop and returned their focus to her, where it belonged. She had their undivided attention now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They began moving closer. Chukka made sure the tip of the gun was pressed against the pod. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Don't test me," she said. They couldn't understand her words, but they knew what she was saying.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Chukka scanned the area for her next move. How to leave with one of these pods?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They kept moving closer, forming a circle around her and up the wall. She couldn't see the Seneca women now but it didn't matter. She had total control of this situation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a scratching, scrabbling noise from somewhere above her. One of them had climbed up high. It was too dark to see what they were up to. Trying to drop a rock on her head? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A skittering, clicking noise filled the air — claws against rock. Dust fell.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A figure moved down the wall, then another. There were several of them crawling down the vertical surface, carrying something between them. It began to glow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They were bringing one of the pods to her, dug out of the wall. The gathered crowd parted as the group of three came down and approached her, carrying the pod reverentially between them. It was green with something swirling inside it. They placed it at her feet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;An offering? A sacrifice to their new god?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;No, that would be too easy. Chukka didn't trust good fortune so readily. They were up to something. Perhaps this was fake, or a bomb. Or they might simply want her to leave the pod she was threatening. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Was there something special about this one in particular? It didn't seem much different to the one they were offering her, other than the colour. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This one," said Chukka, gently tapping the one in the wall with the tip of her gun. Its inner light flared up and something with a tail flashed past the surface. "This one," she shouted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;More lights flashed around the wall in response. The creatures edged closer from the sides and began chipping away with their claws. Chukka kept the gun trained on her target. Slowly the pod came loose. Chukka caught it before it fell.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was smaller than the one they'd tried to give her. That didn't necessarily mean much. Perhaps she could take them both. No, she wouldn't be able to manage. Smaller would be easier. She held it cradled in one arm with the gun pointing down at it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Show me how to get out of here," said Chukka. "Out. Up." She pointed at the roof of the chamber.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The crowd around her parted again, this time creating a path for her. It led towards a wall with a ladder. She wouldn't be able to climb while carrying the pod and her gun. Was this their plan? Attack when she was unable to defend herself. Not a bad idea. She was beginning to see these little imps as worthy competitors. Just not good enough.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Get back. Spread out. Back, back." She waved them away to give her more space. They scattered like frightened vermin. They weren't scared of her, they feared for the safety of the pod she was holding. It was smooth and slippery and easy to drop. Chukka held onto it tight. It was just as precious to her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The ladder was in front of her. Its thick ridges would be tricky to hold onto. Just as she was contemplating how to make some kind of harness, the walls shifted. The rungs of the ladder sank back to create a slope. Steep but with the rungs now forming makeshift steps, she would be able to practically walk up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was too easy, she knew that. They had to be planning something, no way would they allow her to just walk out of here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Come back," she heard Bashir's strained voice. He wasn't dead, which could be a problem if he survived. But he wouldn't survive. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I will," she shouted as she began climbing. "I'll bring help."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She made it to the top and found herself in a dark tunnel. There were bound to be obstacles in her way, but she would overcome them. She was holding the most valuable object in the galaxy and nothing was going to take it from her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Two figures emerged from the dark. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hey, Chukka," said Ubik. "Fancy meeting you here. What you got there?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">493530</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 11:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 86: Divide and Conquer</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/492669</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Tethari.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Core.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two wasn't sure if sending Ubik away was a good idea or not. Being in this situation, his mind part of an alien network he neither understood or felt comfortable in, made it very hard to be sure of anything.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He had expected the sudden introduction of a several millennia's worth of alien culture into his head all at once to have completely broken him, and it did feel like that at first, but at the point where he felt like his mind would collapse in on itself, zenity kicked in. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The calmness he had inherited from his birth on a ship without gravity had enveloped him, and for just a brief moment, he was insulated from the overwhelming deluge of information flowing through him. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He was able to recognise small bits of data that were relevant to his current predicament. The Antecessor method of disseminating information was non-linear and very densely packed, so everything you wanted to know came with everything you didn't, but he pulled himself clear and now he was able to keep his head above water and only dip in and out when he wanted to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was now a picture of the entire asteroid, inside and out, held in his mind. But it was off to the side. A glance every now and again was about all he could withstand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The frightening pale humanoids were the most noticeable element, because they were so numerous and so fast. And so angry. Ubik seemed the perfect answer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik was capable of saving them all, but he was also capable of dooming everyone. At least if he was here, it would be possible to keep an eye on him and be warned early of any disaster he might create. Good in theory, but there was no guarantee that being forewarned would be of any benefit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But Point-Two had decided it would be better to put Ubik's skills to work against the creatures emerging from the centre of the asteroid. The centre that was the only place hidden from his sight. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Information on the creatures, like everything else, was heavily diluted by so much more But he had divined that they were a defence mechanism, built into the asteroid, released when the asteroid's precious cargo became endangered. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It wasn't clear what they released from. There was something at the centre of the asteroid, carefully and thoroughly shielded. Information about it was passed to him in an alien form, ideas and images that made his head feel bloated. Whatever was at the asteroid's core, it produced a massive amount of energy, it was incredibly dense, it contained organic life, and it could act independently of both the Antecessors and the Intercessors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two had tried to probe what was down there but it had caused him intense pain. He didn't want to break something in his brain out of curiosity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;What he did know was that the creatures were considered lethal to other droids. They wouldn't be confronted under any circumstances, and only disaster would follow if they were. How could that not remind him of a certain someone?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You will fail," said the head facing Point-Two. Its features were similar to the creatures, blank and featureless, but now that he had the ability to see things through the Intercessors' own apparatus, he could tell that what he was seeing was a screen, something to hide behind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You don't know that," said Point-Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"There is too much data for you to process. What you have seen is a minuscule amount. Your mind will soon be overwhelmed and the goblins will erase your kind from this asteroid."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Sorry, the goblins?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It is the closest approximation in your visual lexicon," said the Intercessor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Okay. You could be right, but I'm willing to bet our goblin will beat yours."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Intercessor's blank face seemed to twitch. "The one you call Ubik is not enough. You need more than one."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No one needs more than one Ubik," said Point-Two. "You might fear these goblins but there is always a chance they can be beaten."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was strange to be speaking to this projection face to face when they could just as easily be speaking within the asteroid's huge internal network. It had taken him a little time to understand what he had been given access to, but now that he was fully integrated into it, he could reach out to any part of it with his thoughts (almost any part), including the Antecessors (which he had no intention of doing) and to the Intercessor in front of him. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But speaking face to face had the advantage of keeping their conversation private. They weren't the only ones with access to the network.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"There is a small possibility of success," said the Intercessor begrudgingly. Point-two was able to see past the reluctant admission. The Intercessors were the ones who had failed. They had had a mission, to protect and nurture. They had been forced into a position where they now relied on Ubik. He fully understood the reason they felt uncomfortable about it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Any possibility of success is worth pursuing," said Point-Two. "You can improve his chances by aiding us."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Intercessor did not reply. The blank face remained blank.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What's happening?" asked Fig. He had been the most patient out of all of them. His only wish was to save his father, and that had been taken away from him, but he remained calm, waiting for his opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Where Ubik was happy to act without thought, relying on his ability to improvise his way out of any disaster (that he had caused), Fig was the opposite. He waited and observed, learning as much as possible before taking action.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Now that his father's presence was revealed as fake, he was slowly pressing the Intercessor for the truth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two reached out and grabbed Fig, pulling him up and closer. It was almost second-nature now. He wasn't sure how he was doing it, but the gravitational field around him was easily manipulated in this form.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The asteroid is a nest," said Point-Two, using words which weren't particularly accurate but they were the closest he could find. "It was designed to gestate some kind of advanced organic lifeform, but not everyone was happy about the idea."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They are necessary for our protection," said the Intercessor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Protection from what?" asked Fig.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"From you," said the Intercessor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"A lot of your information is wrong," said Point-Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Data cannot be wrong if it is accurate."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Long-term projections can be," said Fig, "if you can't correctly predict future variations in the environment, your accurate data will do you no good. Nothing lives in a vacuum, not even in space. You are using the same methods you used in your previous life in the hope the universe has changed to accommodate them." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Fig's words were concise and precise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Projections are in line with sensor readings," said the Intercessor, unmoved by Fig's analysis. "This has all been foreseen. You are within anticipated parameters. We were expecting you, it was only a matter of time. Once Ubik has been removed, you will no longer have a statistical advantage. Projections will return to within more favourable limits and then the threat you pose will be neutralised." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They expected Ubik to fail. They were counting on it. He was being allowed control, or at least wasn't being fought for it, because so far he was doing exactly what they wanted him to. Sending Ubik to face the goblins was what they wanted and Point-Two had made it easy for them. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two had known that and done it anyway, just as he knew the Guardian was going to attempt to escape the rock with her prize. She wanted Ubik, and she was expecting a rescue party to come get her. She probably thought she could find her way out and then they'd nuke the asteroid from orbit, or whatever it was the Central Authority used to destroy planetoids these days.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Of course, Ubik wouldn't allow that. He wouldn't miss the chance to meet new lifeforms and make them his pets. And having Rex to help him would give him the edge. Point-Two didn't know what changes Ubik had made to the Rex module, but he was sure they wouldn't please the Guardian once she found out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Intercessors and the Guardian both suffered from the same problem — overconfidence in their own abilities. They thought they had a firm grasp on the situation. Point-Two did not have those illusions. He had spent too much time around Ubik to think he had a grasp on anything. He just waited for things to fall apart and then did his best not to get hit by the debris.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What about my father?" asked Fig. Point-Two could tell he had been waiting to ask, being very careful to underplay his concerns. "Where is he?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Intercessor head didn't reply. Fig turned to face Point-Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I haven't found him," said Point-Two. "I've searched the whole asteroid. He isn't in any of the places I have access to. The signal we got from the seventh level isn't there anymore. I think it never was."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What about the places you don't have access to? Could he be there?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"There's only one place. The centre of the asteroid. It's totally dark to me and I don't know how to access it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Fig nodded. "He's probably there."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Intercessor still didn't speak.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Can you send me there?" said Fig.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two took a moment to search for a way down to the darkness. He couldn't see into it but he could see the area around it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The asteroid became denser and more compact the closer to its centre he looked, but the goblins had dug tunnels through the rock to get out. They were gone now, the last of them already emerged and inside the chambers containing the large organics. They were fighting a small group of people who had found their way into the lower levels of the facility. More would be coming and things would only get messier.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I think so," said Point-Two. "It'll be a little cramped, and there's no guarantee your father's down there."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"That's okay. From what I've been able to deduce, it would be too much of a risk to kill me deliberately, and I can avoid most natural disasters." He looked at the Intercessor head, almost daring it to contradict him. There was no response.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Alright," said Point-Two. "I expect Ubik will get us all killed soon anyhow. You might as well go say goodbye to your dad."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Fig smiled ruefully. "I think Ubik will deal with the goblins."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes. I think they'll make him their leader and start a galactic empire," said Point-Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Emperor Ubik," said Fig with a shudder. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The Intercessor head still wasn't saying anything. That probably meant it wanted Fig to go look into the darkness. Usually, you wouldn't want to do what your opponent wanted you to do. Even if you were able to rise to the challenge, your moves became predictable. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Unless, that was, you didn't resist when they thought you would and followed their desire with unexpected enthusiasm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two reached out with his mind and opened another portal, this one on the opposite side of the chamber to the one he'd made for Ubik and the Guardian. Here, in this chamber, his control was strongest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A section below them spiralled open. He moved Fig towards it. Ubik one way and Fig the other, while he stayed in the middle. It would be interesting to see which of them was going to be the busiest. Not him, he hoped.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Fig dropped down. Once the gravity flow caught him, Point-Two let him go. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Now it was just him and the Intercessor. The blank head gave the impression it was happy with the way things were going. Point-Two found it unbearably smug.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Your siblings are coming," said Point-Two. He could feel the Antecessors gathering for a big push. They were above the goblins, clamouring to come down and take the lower levels. Their eagerness spread through the network like humming wires.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They will not come here," said the Intercessor. "They will go to the surface and wait."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Wait for what?" asked Point-Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The hunters."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two looked through the data streams flowing through him for any information on hunters. He found it mixed in with the limited information on the goblins. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Goblins were grown in the dark. They were released to fight off invaders. That was about all there was, apart from a small addendum. They started off small and pale, but perversely strong. But they kept growing and becoming more and more violent. Then they needed to put to sleep, literally or figuratively. They couldn't be put back where they came from, so they were stored in the reflection of their birthplace. The image became clear and distinct as Point-Two focused on it. Inside a wormhole.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two realised what was at the centre of the asteroid and what was producing the gravitational shifts. An infinitely-small wormhole, no bigger than an atom. Anything bigger would be too powerful to control, but even at a microscopic level, it would be able to manipulate large dense masses, vibrating them to produce polarised gravity waves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It wasn't the asteroid that could be moved with an alien engine, it was the portable black hole at its centre that the asteroid was designed to keep in place, like an anchor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"How long before they arrive?" asked Point-Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Soon," said the Intercessor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They would find several ships in their way. That would take care of one problem. Ubik would deal with the goblins and the group they were fighting with. Fig was handling the black hole heart of the asteroid. Which left Point-Two with the smug Intercessor. How would Ubik handle this kind of situation?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Nothing for us to do but wait, then," said Point-Two. "I don't suppose you have any sandwiches lying around?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">492669</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 85: Point of No Return</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/490363</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Tethari.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Core.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik could sense PT panicking. It wasn't because he was good at picking up how people were feeling — that was one of his least developed skills. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;And it wasn't because he had a special bond with PT — although he did like to think of them as good collaborators. And by collaborators, he meant the way he could get PT to collaborate with what he wanted him to do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;No, the real reason he sensed that PT was panicking inside the narrow space he had 'collaborated' PT into entering was the way his feet, which were slightly sticking out of the end, were violently shaking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was the shake of someone not very happy with their position in life. The involuntary shuddering of someone having a hysterical episode. There was also the screaming.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Stay cool and don't panic," Ubik shouted into the crawlspace. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Then the feet stopped shaking. For a moment, Ubik thought he'd made a terrible mistake. He had assumed PT's usually stoic and implacable demeanour would make him the ideal person to undergo what was undoubtedly going to be a horrific and painful experience. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Other people might have a breakdown or lose the will to live, but not PT. There was no doubt in Ubik's mind that PT would grit his teeth and hold on despite the agony, just so he could have the chance of getting revenge on Ubik. His persistence was the key to his usefulness. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik considered pulling PT out to see if he was alright, and then decided it would be better to push him further in, to see if that jump-started something.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The lights flickering and pulsing through the lattice of droid parts began to slow down and move in a more organised fashion. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Organised in the mundane sense. They had been organised before, they just looked chaotic. But now, they followed a much simpler pattern.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He heard Fig's voice, sounding surprised and confused.  Ubik pushed through the lattice, slipping through gaps, no longer concerned about making contact with the structure. There was no need to worry about attracting the Intercessors' attention now.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hey!" he called out, waving to get their attention.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ramon Ollo's head slowly turned around. It moved a lot more stiffly than before. The lights around Ubiks shifted in sync with the head. There was no mistaking it. It was hard to interpret what the lights were saying — the data was moving too fast to be able to read it — but the matching patterns were very, very obvious. The head and the lattice were linked. And they were both moving too slowly to be under the control of the Intercessors or Ramon Ollo. Which left only one other person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What do you want?" said PT. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik smiled. The face was still Ramon's, but the snippy attitude was unmistakably PT's.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You've taken control," said Ubik, grinning. "I knew you could do it." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He had had complete confidence in PT, the ideal candidate. But to do so quickly, to push both the Intercessor intelligence and Ramon Ollo out of the way and assume control, that was even more than Ubik had hoped for. It wasn't often Ubik's projections were exceeded. His projections tended to be quite excessive to begin with.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Taken control of what?" said PT. The face wasn't quite mirroring PT's tone, suggesting some latency issues. He should have shoved PT further into the crawlspace, just as he had thought.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The asteroid," said Ubik gleefully, looking around for any loose connections. "You are the asteroid."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two looked confused. The mirroring was improving, the eyes were already becoming better coordinated. Perhaps there was a machine-learning component to this  tech.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik, get me out of there."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Out of where?" Ubik turned around, ready to go back in and help PT assimilate even further into the mind of the asteroid. "You're already out."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik…" &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was something in the tone of PT's voice that drew Ubik's attention back to the irritated head. And then he was flying through the air, narrowly missing smashing into the structure around him, and heading for the irate face.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But rather than looking annoyed, the head looked astonished. The eyes were wide and the mouth formed an O shape.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik felt much the same. PT had already learned how to control the gravity inside the chamber. Ubik had expected that to take a lot longer, requiring a lot of trial and error to get the fine control required to manage such powerful forces. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But PT's familiarity with gravitational forces of varying intensities had solved the problem instinctively. He was a natural.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik giggled with delight as he was hurled across the chamber. How good was he to set this up so perfectly?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He stopped suddenly, fixed in place in front of Ramon Ollo's nose. Actually, now that he saw it from close up, didn't it resemble PT's nose? Some sort of mental transformation being manifested through the projection?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What was the point of this, Ubik?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"This is our chance," said Ubik, "your big opportunity. You have control. You are the one who can choose what to do?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Like what?" PT's face became twisted with concern.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Whatever you want," said Ubik. "Just do it quickly before you lose control and your brain cells get fried."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;PT's face went from concerned to horrified. "What does that mean? How long have I got?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hard to say. Maybe a long time. Maybe not. It's a lot of information your brain's processing right now. More than an average brain can handle. Don't worry, I'd rate yours as slightly above average."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Then why didn't you put yourself in there?" said PT. "You're the one with all the free space in your head."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Then who would be out here to protect me? You? You don't even know what threats you're facing right now."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What threats am I facing right now?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oh, hard to say. A lot of them are hypothetical. I'm sure the Intercessors and Ramon Ollo will try to kill you long before any of the other variables have a chance to."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;PT cringed with what seemed to be pain. "It's too much. I can see all of it at once. My brain feels like it's going to burst."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You'll be fine," said Ubik. "Just focus on my voice. You'll be too annoyed to worry about all the other stuff."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What the hell kind of plan is that? You want to deliberately piss me off so I focus all my anger on you and block out the infinite amount of data being squeezed into my head?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"See? Working already, isn't it?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;You couldn't argue with results, that's what Grandma always told him. She was right as usual.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It had to be you, PT. This place is built on gravity. Everything here is powered by and controlled by gravity. It's completely different from how we understand the science of gravitational fields, but you use gravity without needing to understand it. You go by instinct and feel. You're the only one here who has a chance of maintaining control over the asteroid and stopping it from breaking apart. I mean, it's only a small chance, but try your best."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You're wrong," said PT. "I'm not the only one. Gravity isn't just powering this place, it's keeping it in check. It's being used to hold back those things I saw. It's a force field used to create a prison, and I can't keep the walls up. They're coming, Ubik."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was that. Ubik had expected the asteroid to house some secrets, but he had only considered the Antecessors and the technology they had already shown. These creatures PT had mentioned didn't make any sense. Since when did Antecessors employ organic beings?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Then again, organics, the augments found on most Ant sites, weren't they organic in origin? Their purpose, which no one had ever been able to determine, had to involve these creatures in some way. They would be interesting to study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You should try to direct them over here," said Ubik. "We can make friends with them. It'll be fun."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What fun?" said PT. "They're going to kill us."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik clicked his tongue and shook his head. "Don't judge them just because they're a bit worked up at the moment."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm not," said PT. "I'm judging them on the single screaming thought in all of their heads to kill everything that's in their path."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Oh," said Ubik. "No chance you're mistaking their intentions? Sometimes people are all mad but really they haven't eaten in a while and they have low blood sugar. Maybe they'll feel better after a snack?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They don't have mouths," said PT. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"So they can't bite or eat me," said Ubik, doing his best to put a positive spin on things.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No," said PT. "But they have claws that can dig through solid rock, so they can probably tear you into tiny pieces."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Okay, but you could probably stop them from doing that if you put your mind to it, couldn't you?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;PT didn't say anything in response.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'll take that as a yes," said Ubik.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They aren't the only problem," said PT. "We've got ships approaching. VendX, Seneca, Central Authority."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Finally," said Guardian Tezla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Don't be so pleased," said PT. "They're going to arrive at the same time. I doubt it will be in the spirit of mutual assistance. There's also the Antecessors. They're aware of us. They're just waiting to see who—"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;PT's face distorted and flickered. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik looked behind him. The pulsing lights had changed pattern again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes, I see now," said the head. It no longer sounded like PT. It didn't look like him, either.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Father?" said Fig. "Did you defeat the Intercessor?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Very interesting." Ramon Ollo's head looked around. "So this is how they controlled the asteroid." He returned his gaze to Ubik who was still hanging in front of him. "You arranged the pathways to isolate their routines. I must thank you for that. What was your name again?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik found himself being moved from side to side. "Wellden, sir. First name, Goodjob"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Goodjob Wellden?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Thank you very much," said Ubik. "I've always dreamed of hearing you say those words to me."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik was turned over and over. "This level of control is astonishing. Even more than I expected."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Father, you have full control now?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yes. I see everything."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Then you can see you have to give control back," said Ubik. "If you can access the pathways I built, so can they."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It is no longer an issue," said Ramon. "The network you built, it is the only route and I have already taken it. It is no longer needed."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Suddenly, Ubik was flying across the chamber, back towards the lattice. But he didn't slow down as he got closer. He smashed into it, sending pieces flying. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;His suit protected him but it still hurt. He made himself smaller to try to pass through the gaps, but he was bounced around with precise guidance to hit the key structural parts. Droid parts floated free.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik had hoped Ramon Ollo would be so impressed with his work, he would offer Ubik a position in his lab immediately. Things weren't going as well as he'd hoped. He slammed into another bunch of droid parts. They broke into pieces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;And then they stopped, hanging motionless, before returning to their original position, snapping back together. They all did, reforming the lattice perfectly. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;A second head appeared. This one was very clearly recognisable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You aren't Ramon Ollo," said PT. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He was a quick learner. He'd figured out how to reestablish pathways through the network quickly enough not to get disconnected. A quick learner who excelled under desperate conditions. Ubik was born to be his teacher.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"He isn't my father?" said Fig, a pained look on his face.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It's a copy," said PT. "They didn't keep back part of your father's mind, they copied the parts they could as best they could. But I can see their pathways. There's only one entity."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"A mimic?" said Ubik. "Makes sense. The real Ramon Ollo wouldn't be this easy to beat."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ramon Ollo's face changed. It became a blank slate. The lattice behind PT began breaking up and spreading out, leaving only the section that housed PT's body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Wait," said PT. "We can help you save them."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The flying droid parts stopped.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"How?" said a cold, emotionless voice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik found himself flying across the room once more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Him. He can save them. I don't know what they are, but you're here to protect them, aren't you? He's the only one who can help you. Even if you kill us, they will be destroyed. He's your only chance. "&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"He can not be controlled. He can not be trusted. He is unreliable."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"How long is this list going to be?" asked Ubik.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"He doesn't have to be controlled," said PT. "You just need to give him a problem to solve."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik was raised up to face the blank face. His suit separated from his body and broke down into its component parts, and just hung there. One small black rectangle moved away from the rest, towards the Guardian. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;She caught it, a look of surprise on her face. "Rex?" It jumped out of her hand and slotted into her waist. The suit lit up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik followed, flying into the Guardian's arms. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Take him," said PT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Take him where?" asked the Guardian. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;There was a grating sound. A hole spun open above them. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Follow the lighted path," said PT. "When you get to the room at the end, leave him there. This whole quadrant will be destroyed if you don't."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Tezla looked like she wanted to say something, but she grabbed Ubik instead. The suit fired thrusters in the arms and legs and she shot into the air, dragging a suitless Ubik with her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What am I supposed to do?" Ubik shouted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You'll think of something," said PT. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He was probably right. It was a bit chilly without his suit, but that was okay. PT had given Rex back to the Guardian, which made her one of the team. Although it wasn't the old Rex. This Rex was more of an Ubik upgrade. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">490363</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 11:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper Darker - Book 2 – 84:  All in the Mind</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/489296</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Third Quadrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Tethari.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Asteroid Core.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The images in Point-Two's mind were overwhelming. He was seeing too much at once and closing his eyes did nothing to alleviate the problem. He was everywhere at once, not able to control what he saw and no way to turn down the intensity. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He was aware of all the different beings on the asteroid and one group in particular. They were humanoid but not human — not even close. They were faceless and pale, sickly in their movements, struggling to emerge from a long sleep. And they were angry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They were furious, in fact, and searching for their enemy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two wasn't sure what they were or how he knew how they felt, but he didn't like it. They were emerging from somewhere even deeper within the asteroid, and they were all heading for the same location. A chamber somewhere between where he was currently and the surface.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He wasn't just seeing them the way you might via a camera, he was with them and around them and part of them. It made his skin crawl. He would have turned away if possible, but he couldn't move. Even though he wasn't touching the sides of the compartment he had slid into at Ubik's insistence — something he was deeply regretting — he was held in place by forces all around him applying invisible pressure, forcing him to keep watching.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"They're coming," he managed to shout. He didn't know what they were or what they wanted, but a warning to others seemed the correct response.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Who?" he heard Ubik ask.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I don't know. Things."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Droids?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"No, they're alive. There are lots of them and they don't have faces."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"So no mouths," said Ubik, which seemed an odd thing to focus on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Get me out of here." Point-Two's face was stretching, his mouth pulling back into a grimace as the images began piling up on top of each other. It was like being under several Gs but from the inside out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What else do you see?" said Ubik, ignoring the request.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik, you arghhhhh…." The noise coming out of his throat didn't seem to belong to him. He wasn't in pain but the discomfort was maddening, like being unable to scratch an itch deep in his brain. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He needed to get out. If Ubik wasn't going to help, he would have to find his own way. Chances were there was something to be learned here, a way to access information, maybe. He already felt like he was part of the inner-workings of what was clearly far more than just a big lump of rock. But he didn't care. It was too much for his brain to handle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Can you go any deeper?" said Ubik. "Look down. What's at the heart of the asteroid?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ubik wasn't appreciating Point-Two's position. It was all very well wanting to use this opportunity to their advantage, but it was completely different when you were the one having your brain stuffed to the point of bursting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Shut up and get me arghhhh…" It was coming in waves now. Blasts of images from all across the asteroid, everything of equal importance, from the desolate craters on the surface to the empty chambers inside the Antecessor facility. There were droids moving somewhere. There were people in suits — he thought he recognised them. There were strange glowing pods in the walls. There were ships in the sky and there were white, faceless creatures crawling through the rock.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Nothing took precedence, nothing was marked as important. It was all the same and he was drowning in it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Don't pass out," shouted Ubik from somewhere near Point-Two's feet. "You're doing really well. Also, try not to scream so much."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two was used to being in confined spaces. On the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Liberator Garu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;, maintenance work often required you to crawl into a tight passage between vast machines to get to a section that needed repairing or replacing. It wasn't safe and it was never comfortable, but you got used to it. Anyone with claustrophobia had it stripped out of them, either through repeated exposure or by surgical procedure. You couldn't afford to worry about irrational fear of small spaces when any problem with the ship's engines was likely to kill everyone aboard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It had never been a problem for Point-Two. He could slide into the narrowest of crawlspaces and do whatever needed to be done. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;But this was different. This was a conduit into a much bigger space. One that was too full of too much. It was like being in a compactor that was slowly closing in on him, crushing him with the weight of complete information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"It's too much, it's too much."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Try focusing on one thing," said Ubik. "Whatever feels the most important."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The only matter Point-Two considered important was getting out of his tube prison, but there was no way to get purchase on any surface to be able to push himself out. The pressure being exerted on him to keep him in place had no form or substance to it. While it could apply a force on him, he wasn't able to do the reverse.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik…" he yelled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Keep it down, you don't want to attract any attention."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I'm going to die, you bastard."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Don't exaggerate. You'll suffer brain damage at worst. We can keep you alive for years in that condition." There was going to be no sympathy coming his way from Ubik. The little shit had known this would happen. Had planned for it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Another wave of images hit him. He saw the Seneca women shooting their guns. Was he hallucinating now? Was any of what he was seeing real?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He was being too easily distracted. If he was going to extract himself from this place he would have to figure out a way to either turn off the pressure holding him in place or change it to push him out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He slowed his breath and tried to achieve some form of zenity in his mind. Panic would only make things worse, if that was possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;His mind was connected to this thing, this brain built by Ubik. If it could send images in, perhaps he could send them out. He wasn't sure what good that would do, but there didn't seem to be much else available to him. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two stopped trying to shield himself from the influx of images and looked directly into the source. He realised it was dangerous but he was ready to retreat if it became too painful.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It wasn't painful at all. In fact, he should have done this earlier. Instead of overwhelming his mind, he was able to surf over the images, skimming over the top without having to absorb them fully. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;With a little distance, he was able to see that there was a network that spread throughout the rock. He was able to see it all at once, which was disorienting, or he could move from one place to another.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two found he could follow different routes, flowing through them like he was in a waterslide. He had no idea where he was going but it was a lot less stressful than having everything poured into his brain at once. Now he just had to find the exit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Maybe the plan wasn't so bad. He could search the entire asteroid without moving and find the quickest way back to the surface, while avoiding anything that looked dangerous.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What about these creatures?" said Ubik. "Are they coming this way? Are they still angry? What are they wearing? PT, concentrate. Our lives are in your hands."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two's body began to tremble. It was because Ubik had grabbed his foot and was shaking it to get his attention. He found himself unable to stay apart from the data streams he had managed to skim over and dropped into them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Once more he became overwhelmed. The images were even faster now, flying in and out of his field of vision. He couldn't make sense of any of it. The only thing that stood out were the creatures. There were so many of them, they were impossible to miss.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;They were digging their way through solid rock, squeezing through cracks a worm would find it difficult to navigate. Their bodies seemed to have no bones even though they were built to look like humans, the same number of limbs, the same number of digits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two found it unpleasant to observe them. He felt as though they were going to infect him the way they had the asteroid. They were humanoid but they reminded him of maggots, infesting a corpse.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He passed beyond them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Lights glowed around him. They were different colours, emitting a power reminiscent of organics. But they were much bigger, and they contained something else.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two reached his mind towards the lights. They were spread out but he was able to approach them all at the same time. His mind touched them and the white creatures became aware of him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He could sense them looking at him, even though they had no eyes. Their hostility rose sharply, pushing his mind back. There was something they were protecting. It was inside the lights. He pushed his mind forward to investigate and hundreds of minds attacked him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Everything went black. There were no lights, no deluge of images. Darkness. Not even Ubik's voice could reach him here, so at least there was that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Like the wind, you must rush where you will. Like the sea, I must remain in place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It wasn't a voice, not words. The idea appeared in his head but he recognised that it hadn't come from him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;You will fail and fall again. I will renew and restart what was lost.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;This time from a different source. He was in the middle of a conversation. Between who?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Death is the beginning of life. I will rise from the ashes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;It was hard to follow what was being said, because it wasn't being said. The ideas were filtering into Point-Two's mind by some mysterious process. He wasn't even sure if he was following correctly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;My son is the only one who can control what will live on in spite of your wanton destruction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Ramon Ollo, it had to be. Arguing with the Intercessors? Somehow, Point-Two had found his way into the place where they existed. It wasn't somewhere he particularly wanted to be.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Who are you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two didn't respond. Maybe the thought wasn't directed at him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;How did you get here?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;He was still surrounded by pitch blackness. He wondered if he could quietly leave the same way he had come in. He would need to work out how he came in to do that, though.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;You can't leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;. He wasn't sure which of them was speaking now. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;You are part of us now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;The idea of being stuck here forever sent a surge of panic through Point-Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;No, don't do that, no…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Something reached for him. He felt its presence and twisted away from it instinctively, his mind responding the way his body would. There were obstructions in his mind, placed there to stop him. He bent and spun to avoid them. Mental gymnastics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two could suddenly see. He could see Fig standing in front of him, small and helpless. The Guardian was by his side.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You aren't my father." Fig looked slightly confused.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"I know," said Point-Two. "Where's Ubik? I'm going to kill him."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"PT?" said Fig, a look of wonder on his face. "Is that you?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Yeah. Why, can't you tell?" &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Hey!" called a voice from behind him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two turned slowly. The chamber seemed to rotate around him. He saw Ubik, a small figure inside a giant lattice. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"What do you want?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"You've taken control," said Ubik. "I knew you could do it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Taken control of what?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"The asteroid," said Ubik gleefully. "You are the asteroid."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Point-Two couldn't understand what Ubik was saying. He was still in the tube next to Ubik, he was just seeing the world from out here from the perspective of the giant head. That didn't mean he was the giant head.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik, get me out of there."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Out of where? You're already out."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;"Ubik…" He reached out to grab Ubik out of instinct but he didn't have any arms. Ubik came flying towards him. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Wait. He could feel the extension of his body. Gravity was his limbs. He was the asteroid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">489296</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 11:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/syndication/23290</link><description>Latest updates of (Deeper Darker)</description></rss>