<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Defiance of the Fall</title><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 334 - Hidden Wealth</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/503440</link><description>&lt;p&gt;"You wanted to see me, sir?" the young woman said with a shaky voice, clearly afraid to enter the large room where Zac had been training with his shield the past day. "I'm Emma."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac looked over with some confusion, not recognizing the girl by the entrance. But he quickly realized who it was, and stowed away his shield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you the scout I asked for?" Zac asked, trying to not sound threatening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Y-Yes. I was in charge of a scout team looking for valuable veins within the Unio- ahem, Lord Atwood's domain," Emma hastily explained, keeping her eyes at the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Great. Come with me for a bit," Zac said, leaving the training room and the group of Valkyries who had been his sparring partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The councilors from the Underworld Council left yesterday along with a group of ambassadors led by Tylia and Joanna, taking the impatient Emily with them. Zac himself had decided to follow up on the idea he had while waiting for things to get sorted out, and called for the person who had written it up, which was the girl currently following him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately she had been out on a mission and it looked like she only returned just now. So since Zac had some time to spare he decided to work on some of his undead skills. All of them were still at the Early Stage, and he hoped that one way to improve his battlefield impact if he upgraded them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Bulwark Mastery]&lt;/strong&gt; was the easiest, as it only required him to learn and incorporate the movements with the shield. It took him less than an hour to upgrade the skill to Middle mastery, and another 10 hours to reach late mastery. But just like with &lt;strong&gt;[Axe Mastery]&lt;/strong&gt; he found that there were something missing to push it toward peak mastery, so he could only stop there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrading &lt;strong&gt;[Bulwark Mastery]&lt;/strong&gt; did not improve his attributes or allowed him to unleash some new power, but it did help a lot in utilizing his shield, and the fractal equivalent in &lt;strong&gt;[Immutable Bulwark]&lt;/strong&gt;. It even showed him how to properly fight with a weapon in one hand and shield in the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now he had been a bit clumsy and limited in that department, but he quickly learned how to use both his weaponry to their full potential. The shield was not only a large plank to block out damage, but it was a tool that would also create the opening for him to finish his enemies with his weapon. His other skills, unfortunately, weren't as easy to level up, but he didn't despair. Hopefully he would be able to push some of them forward in the following weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't worry, you're not in trouble or anything like that. I have read some of your reports. You were the one who wrote this, correct?" Zac wanted to confirm after the two entered his office, handing Emma the report he found the other day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could understand Emma's nervousness. She had worked in the department under one of the leaders who were found guilty of human trafficking just this morning. Almost two-thirds of the leaders of the Union had been found complicit to the slave trade, and they were executed as punishment. It wasn't unthinkable that the minions would suffer for the sins of their boss as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wha- Oh? Yes!" she stammered after glancing over the first page. "I was the one who wrote it. I am the only survivor from that excursion."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Large vein deposit. Unknown resource. Quality - Highest. Danger level – Highest," Zac said, listing the main points from his memory. "Infested by, and I quote you, an insane number of mutated bugs. But no location?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Leonard, the department head, did not want us to write the location in the reports of very valuable things. He was afraid competing departments was spying on him. I only told him in person," the scout said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tell me about this place," Zac said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The vein is three day's travel from a remote outpost, hidden in a huge cave system at the bottom of a lake. We found it by accident when looking for valuable resources underwater. When we entered we realized there was some odd crystal that was emitting a really mysterious light, but we didn't have time to excavate even one before we were overrun."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By what?" Zac asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Insects, each about as large as a large dog. But they were so strong! We barely managed to harm them, but they slaughtered everyone in seconds. I only managed to use my identification skill once before I fled. The insect was level 68. That was one month ago," the scout said with horror in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Have you seen anything like that before?" Zac probed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, there are really some strong insects down here in the Underworld, but they are usually solitary. We saw thousands of peak F-Rank beasts, and we didn't even really enter the vein. I'm sure it's teeming with E-Grade beasts further down, especially now that so much time has passed," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How did you survive?" Zac asked with some suspicion. "You're only level 42, and I am sure you were lower at that point."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have a good movement skill," she said, "and the beasts stopped when I jumped into the water to get back to the surface."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac slowly nodded. He wasn't disappointed when he heard how dangerous the mysterious cavern was, but rather the opposite. A place crawling with extremely strong beasts was exactly what he needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His plan was simple. He wanted to throw himself into the thick of it, and with the help of &lt;strong&gt;[Deathwish]&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;[Fields of Despair]&lt;/strong&gt; grind all the way to level 60. Normally such a thing might have taken over a month, mainly because beasts strong enough to provide a nice boost of energy were few and far between.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this cavern was for some reason overflowing with powerful beasts that would each be able to control their own region on Mystic Island, turning the cave into a cultivator's paradise as long as one was strong enough to survive. Not even the rabid beasts in the hunt would be able to compare to the massive amounts of beasts in there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depending on how much stronger the beasts had become in the past weeks it would only take a week or two to get to level 60. If the skill he got at that point would allow him to confidently fight the invaders in his undead form without risking the lives of his people, great. If not, then he would turn into his human form to fight, even if that would result in a loss of cosmic energy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides, there was undoubtedly something interesting in that cave if it had turned it's inhabitants so powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why do you think the insects are so strong at that place?" Zac asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't know… But if I had to guess? I think it's those rocks somehow evolving the insects," she said with some hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded and asked some follow-up questions about anything that might be useful in his expedition. When he felt confident in finding the place he excused the scout after having her sign a temporary contract of confidentiality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personally, Zac believed there was another possibility to the one Emma provided. There might be a great natural treasure at the bottom of the cave, which was the source of both the mysterious crystals and the powerful beasts. He already knew that the planet was given a handful of great treasures by the System, items that normally shouldn't appear. His Tree of Ascension was such an example, and the Abbot's lotus was another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each such item could bring a great boost to the one who managed to seize it, but so far Zac had only gotten one even though he was so far ahead of the others of earth. The odd place in the report might be his chance at a second one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since he had everything he needed he didn't waste any time. He immediately set out after informing Mr. Trang about his decision. Zac knew this somewhat messed with the quest the Valkyries received, but he needed to focus on his own development at this point. He needed to improve as quickly as possible to be able to match the Dominators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He immediately teleported over to the small town cave that the scout mentioned and immediately rushed out into the open Underworld. The scout had mentioned three days of travel, but Zac didn't want to waste almost a week on travel for the round trip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, Zac changed into his human form for the first time in a while and rushed across the subterranean landscape with &lt;strong&gt;[Loamwalker]&lt;/strong&gt;, and he found himself at the lakefront in less than a day. The fact that he didn't have to skirt around the domain of powerful beasts saved him one day, while his movement skill saved him another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When he stood by the shore of the crystal clear lake he once again changed his race with the help of his transformation skill and quietly entered the depths when his change to his Draugr form was complete. Remembering the scout's description he swam down twenty meters and ripped apart some moss at the wall to expose the entrance to the cavern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He swam in the pitch-black water-filled tunnel for almost five minutes before finally finding air, and he couldn't believe that the scouting party dared to enter a scary place like this. Even with his massive pool of Endurance he felt it was a bit unsettling, like a beast of the depths could crop up at any moment to swallow him whole. But he managed to exit the tunnel without any problem, finding himself in a massive cave system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cave itself was a large and open area illuminated in green, but not by the usual luminescent moss and fungi. It was rather some crystals embedded in the walls that seemed to have green fireflies fluttering around inside. Zac immediately understood those crystals were what Emma was referring to, but he couldn't sense any special energy from them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac wanted to excavate one of the crystals to take a closer look, but incessant clattering echoing in the cave stopped him in his tracks. It looked like he was getting the same reception as the scouts, as a tidal wave of insects frenziedly rushed toward him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of the insects looked the same, though they were of slightly varying sizes. They most closely resembled a giant Weta or cricket, with three pairs of legs where the hindmost set was extra long. But they also possessed enormous mandibles that looked strong enough to bite a human in two. Finally they had a pointy stinger at the back, though the scout didn't know if these things possessed any venom or not as she had to immediately flee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their bodies were covered in layered shell, but they looked much thinner compared to the Ayr ants that he fought during the best waves. But in return they were much quicker, jumping toward him with greater speed than a charging Barghest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each one of them looked like a decent foe for any cultivator, with their combination of natural weapons and a pretty high speed. But what was truly intimidating was the wave of killing intent that pushed toward him upon their approach. Zac quickly used his eye skill before things got too hectic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[Lower Crust Battleroach – Insect – Level 73 - Strength]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result of &lt;strong&gt;[Inquisitive Eye]&lt;/strong&gt; proved that the beasts had improved a couple of levels in the short month since the scout was here, making Zac even more confident there was something in the cave that pushed these things to evolve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there was no time to do an in-depth analysis as the tidal wave of insects was upon him. He took out &lt;strong&gt;[Verun's Bite] &lt;/strong&gt;as the miasmic haze from &lt;strong&gt;[Fields of Despair]&lt;/strong&gt; spread through the cave. The change in energy made a few of the insects stop in confusion, but they were quickly overrun by frenzied brethren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fractal shield materialized behind Zac as his axe turned into a blur. Green liquid splattered in all directions as Zac felt a steady stream of energy enter his body, both through &lt;strong&gt;[Fields of Despair]&lt;/strong&gt; and the quick kills from his swings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shells of the insects barely hindered the upgraded &lt;strong&gt;[Verun's Bite]&lt;/strong&gt;, and even &lt;strong&gt;[Deathwish]&lt;/strong&gt; steadily killed one insect after another as they threw themselves at him from every direction. Specters kept popping up around him to retaliate any strike against him, his shield, or the fractal bulwark protecting his rear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mists of miasma rose from the air as the corpses started to transform into fuel for the fight, and Zac started to slowly push forward as to not get buried in insect corpses. His whole body was already covered in green goop, but he didn't care as he saw every disgusting insect as a burst of energy to progress his levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac resolutely kept moving downward in the cave, and between the increasingly thick haze of miasma and the constantly appearing specters, it looked like an Undying Legion was trying to break into the underworld. And in the middle of the carnage a system prompt appeared, telling him he had received a quest. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">503440</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 16:48:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 333 - The Underworld Council</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/503041</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Things went quite smoothly after the bodyguards were subdued. The leaders of the Union were swiftly captured and imprisoned as the forces of Port Atwood were called over. Ogras wanted to summarily execute everyone to make an example, but Zac decided on a proper investigation and trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Union was a huge enterprise, and it soon became obvious that not everyone was aware of the slave trade, even at the top. In fact, in the meeting that Zac interrupted, it wasn't obvious that it was a slave camp they lost, but it was rather called a mining camp. Everyone had known about the trade with the invaders, but many thought they were using raw materials rather than people as a currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Zac explained the situation with the slaves, everyone professed their ignorance of the matter, staunchly arguing that they only dealt with traditional business ventures. But as the days passed Calrin and his gnomes easily unraveled who was guilty and benefitted through the revenue streams, and with the interrogations that a shrouded Ogras led they soon had a full picture of what was going on.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the normal employees of the Union, things went even smoother than Zac could ever have expected. Verana had been proven right. The moment they started to release the news that they only wanted to deal with the brass because of the slave trade, the normal workers quickly calmed down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were a few that fled and disappeared among the large population, either for fear of the unknown, or perhaps because they had done something they were afraid would be unearthed. But most happily went about their days, especially after Zac increased the general salaries by 25%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But taking charge of the sprawling entity that was the Union wouldn't take just a day or two. There were so many businesses with complicated relationships, and dozens of strategic resources to inspect. Luckily they had the whole network in their hands already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Union had used the same type of system as the New World Government, with one Lord creating a hub for all the mayors in the network. It wasn't clear who the true Lord was, but many believed it to be Little Treasure who had fled before Zac made his entrance. And since he even didn't stay behind to defend his domain when their headquarters was assaulted the whole system was immediately awarded to Zac as the assaulting Lord.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac himself was mostly uninterested in the practical proceedings and rather focused on the massive archives of intelligence that the Union had gathered the past months. Their secret intelligence dossiers on the demonkin and human Incursions were probably even more thorough than the Council's due to their frequent encounters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He knew he had to deal with the Demon Incursion as quickly as possible, but he was a bit unsure of what to do. The reason he came here in his undead form was to level up his Undead Class, but after his recent battles he felt there were some clear limitations to his Undying Bulwark Class as it currently stood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of his skills were aimed at keeping himself alive, with &lt;strong&gt;[Deathwish]&lt;/strong&gt; being his only offensive skill along with his learned skill &lt;strong&gt;[Unholy Strike]&lt;/strong&gt;. He still kept training his utilization of the Dao every day with the trinket, but it would be some time until he could activate &lt;strong&gt;[Cyclic Strike]&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of offensive and movement skills made his impact on a battlefield limited. It was not like a video game, he didn't have any taunt skills that forced all enemies to attack him. The moment the invaders realized he was a tough nut to crack they could simply assault his allies, completely circumventing both &lt;strong&gt;[Deathwish]&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;[Immutable Bulwark]&lt;/strong&gt;. His whole plan was for naught if his gained levels came at the cost of the lives of his friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But as he read through the stacks of intelligence of the Underworld he found a possible solution to his problem in one of the scouting reports. But before he had time to send for the person who submitted this report a Valkyrie knocked on the door to the office he had commandeered for himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am sorry to disturb you," the Valkyrie said after entering. "Some ambassadors from the Underworld Council is here, what do you want to do?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So they came after all. Took them longer than we expected. Have Joanna and Sap Trang join me in Conference Room C," Zac said as he donned his mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had kept his modified appearance throughout the visit, but he only wore the mask when in public. As he walked through the richly decorated halls he sighed in wonder. Most of the original interiors remained, but most electrical functions had been swapped out with day crystals. It was an interesting mix of the old old world and the post-integration era, and it actually meshed quite well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The old fisherman and Joanna joined him soon after he sat down at the ornate table, and just minutes later three warriors entered the room. It was two humans and one of the molemen, each of them radiating even stronger auras than the bodyguards of the union. And it was clear that this power came from battle rather than absorbing crystals and eating pills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The female moleman especially gave off the aura of a powerhouse, and Zac realized that she might be at the same level as someone like Thea. It was to the point that he was a bit tempted to use &lt;strong&gt;[Inquisitive Eye]&lt;/strong&gt;, but he knew that it would likely fail or even backfire. The other two were likely rankers as well, or at worst just shy of making the cut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the humans was a middle-aged man that was built like a bear with a large sword on his back. With his large bushy beard he gave off the aura of a brute, but an intelligent light in his eyes indicated he wasn't all brawn. The other human was an old lady with graying hair. She didn't have any distinguishing items on her, but two snowballs slowly rotated around her, meaning she was likely some sort of ice mage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moleman had two large daggers fastened to her waist, and from the aura they emitted Zac realized they were actually one Spirit Tool. Spirit Tools that were split into dual items were far harder to create from what Zac understood, making them as rare as defensive Spirit Tools, or perhaps even rarer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That this rogue had gotten her hands on such a good item proved once more she had survived some trials and found her lucky encounters, just like him. The only way she could have gotten such a good item was if she completed some harsh quest from the system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was clear that the Underworld Council hadn't sent some middlemen to meet with him, but rather some of their core warriors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Welcome," Sap Trang said with a kindly smile. "I am Sap Trang, ambassador of Port Atwood. This is Joanna, leader of the Valkyries, and lastly Mr. Black. We apologize for not getting in contact with the Underworld Council sooner, our time down here has been a bit hectic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'd say," the large man said with a wry smile. "I am-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait," the moleman interjected, looking at Zac with animosity. "You are no human. You are not one of the four founding races. You reek of death, and not like a warrior."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac was a bit surprised that his origin was immediately exposed by the moleman. Not even the people of Port Atwood knew he wasn't human. They just thought he had gotten some odd class like Death Knight, which gave him such a spooky aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After hesitating for a second he removed his mask, exposing his deathly pale skin and pitch-black eyes. The burly man couldn't stop himself from twitching when he saw the eyes that seemingly led into an endless abyss, and the old woman frowned in consternation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your senses are sharp," Zac said, not surprised about the reactions. "I am undead."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So The Super Brother-Man gobbles up the Union because they work with the invaders, while himself working with invaders," the moleman said, some anger burning in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lara-," the man said, but was stopped by a glare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac smiled slightly at the accusation, not angry at the questioning. If anything it proved that at least the Council hadn't gotten their priorities mixed up, and truly tried to stop the invaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lord Atwood recognizes that the world is not black or white," Sap Trang explained. "The Incursions are a problem that needs to be dealt with, but it doesn't mean he can't recruit talents from the various factions that have invaded our planet. It helps us to gain all sorts of information, allowing us to adapt to this new reality much faster. Just like the Council have benefited from the Union's trade with the invaders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But what we're doing is different from the Union. The aliens working for Lord Atwood have already had their Incursions closed, making them dependent on Port Atwood. Lord Atwood would also never sell or sacrifice our own people," Joanna added. "You should understand, the moment an invader uses a teleportation array, it means they have truly given up on invading Earth, meaning everyone here works for Lord Atwood."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moleman didn't seem completely satisfied with the explanation, but she didn't press the issue further as she sat down with a harrumph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am sorry about the questioning," the man said with a smile. "We have been isolated down here, constantly fighting the invaders for months. I am Gregor, and these two are Oksana and Lararia. We are three of the 11 seats of the Underworld council."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What brings the Underworld Council here today?" Joanna asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"First we simply wanted to make your acquaintance, but we also wish to inquire about your future plans," Gregor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We cannot divulge any specifics, but suffice to say our goal is to close the incursions of the underworld, which would allow us to focus on the real enemies of Earth," Joanna said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Real enemies?" Gregor said with confusion. "Who would that be?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should have heard of two of them. Inevitability and Harbinger, the two top positions on the ladder for the hunt," Joanna said. "But what you might not know is that those two are under command of someone far more dangerous."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From there Joanna proceeded to explain the situation about The Great Redeemer and the impending threat he posed. The trio mostly listened silently, sometimes interjecting with incisive questions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We learned about the existence of these people from the Zhix down here even before the hunt," Gregor said with a frown. "And we have heard about the Dominators from their old world as well. But who would have thought that was just the beginning of the conspiracy?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not even Lord Atwood is ready to fight against the Dominators just yet. They are monstrously strong and possess hidden means provided by their master. But he's desperately cultivating to gain the power to stop them, and we hope the Council will join us in that battle when the time comes," Joanna said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This topic is far beyond our expectations, and we cannot speak for the whole Council on this matter. But I joined the battle to protect Earth and secure a position in the multiverse. I won't shy away from any battle to protect our home, no matter if it's invaders or Dominators," Gregor said, and the old lady nodded in agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac internally breathed out in relief, as one of the most important goals of the Underworld was somewhat accomplished. The discussions went on for a while, and it became clear that one of the biggest worries of the Underworld Council had been that Zac wanted to gobble up the whole Underworld. That he was only using the fight with the Invaders as an excuse to get his foot in the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the fact that they could easily prove that they had closed multiple incursions through Joanna's quest quickly warmed the council members, and discussions rather moved to the topic of cooperation. Zac eventually decided to send over a group of ambassadors to get a better understanding of the battle with the Fire Golems. The squad would also act as Emily's protectors while she looked for her sister since he didn't have time to go himself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large problem with the golems was that they were the only force seemingly unencumbered by the extremely hard rock in the Underworld, allowing them to freely create new paths, and flood the ones the Council used with Lava. The council could only perform quick raids against the golems nowadays, afraid that their path of retreat would be cut off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the fact that a group of extremely powerful people had entered the Underworld brought hope for the Council that they could finally launch a decisive strike against the core of the Golem Incursion, Stopping the threat for good. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can we ask when Lord Atwood plans on moving against the Fire Golems? They are the largest threat to the survival of the Underworld," Gregor finally asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither Joanna or Sap Trang dared to speak up regarding this subject, as Zac still hadn't made his decision on how to proceed. There was the issue of the demon Incursion, and also that report that had caught his eye. After mulling it over for a few seconds Zac looked up at Gregor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are some things we need to deal with before we turn our eyes toward the Fire Golem Incursion. But we hope to launch an all-out strike within three weeks at the latest."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">503041</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 16:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 332 - New Management</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/502506</link><description>&lt;p&gt;"We've been used as a tool from the start," Ogras snorted as he glared at Smaug, some killing intent leaking from his body. "I knew something was off about this brat."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac glared at the young man as well, quickly putting two and two together. Smaug had mixed truths and lies in order to push Zac and his group into a collision course with the Union. The fact that the conglomerate sold people as slaves to the invaders had already been proven, but whether they ever pressured Smaug to attack his party was another matter entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why?" was all that Zac said with a cold voice, somewhat regretting they had removed his shackles so that he would be able to keep up with them as they traveled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My sister is innocent in this. I saw an opportunity. I couldn't be sure how you would act in the underworld, so I needed to create a conflict with these assholes. But they deserve to be run to the ground," Smaug said, some ruthlessness flashing in his eyes before his face returned to that of a hapless youngster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You asshole!" a muffled voice came from within the sack. "You've been tricking people again? You've already got me kidnapped, now you're going to get me killed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ogras glanced at the sack with some humor before putting the girl down on the ground and untied her cover. A beautiful girl in her teens emerged, and her energetic emerald eyes were an obvious sign she was related to Smaug. She had long black hair with a thin braid running down her side, and she wore a hipster ensemble from the old world. A glance with &lt;strong&gt;[Inquisive Eye]&lt;/strong&gt; showed that her name was Rima and that she was level 25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was a completely different sight from the dirty and bedraggled slaves they had just emancipated, and it looked like she hadn't suffered any injustice in captivity. She glared at Smaug for a second before pushing closer to a bemused Ogras.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry about my useless brother, Mr. Knight. He's an idiot and a liar, but he's a good guy," she said, looking up at the demon with adoring eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mr. Knight?" the demon echoed with confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well, you're my handsome knight in shining armor. You broke into the stronghold of the bad guys and saved me," she explained, showing no inclination to walk over to her brother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sorry girl, you're a bit young for my taste," Ogras said with a snort, but after a brief pause looked her up and down once more. "Come back in five years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Animal," Joanna and Verana echoed in unison, but the demon was completely unaffected by their ire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Rima, don't be like that," Smaug entreated, looking a bit embarrassed. "I did what I had to do to keep us safe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Stop using me to justify your shady business practices," Rima said with a roll of her eyes. "Do you know how it feels to be mentioned as the reason for you turning into a drug lord?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're a drug dealer?" Zac said with a frown. "Is that why you're so rich?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I worked in, uh, pain management before the integration," Smaug said with a cough. "I haven't dabbled in that since the world turned crazy though, even though there is a massive demand from people who want to escape reality."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mr. Mask, is it true you work for the Super Brother-Man?" Rima said, looking at Zac with interest. "I heard from Mr. Knight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm Mr. Black," Zac said. "And yes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mr. Black? How is that any better?" Rima muttered, before perking up again. "Is the Super Brother-Man handsome? How old is he? Is he single?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Already abandoning me, girl?" Ogras grunted, though he clearly was just messing around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Enough," Zac said and knocked the girl unconscious with a burst of his aura before taking out &lt;strong&gt;[Hunger]&lt;/strong&gt;. "You attacked us, using arrays that would kill most people. I was already considering what punishment you deserved when I thought you acted under duress. Why shouldn't I kill you right now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am useful!" Smaug hurriedly said, some fear appearing on his face. "I can provide all sorts of information on the Underworld. I possess riches, and know where to find more."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can get information from the Union and the Council and we already possess more wealth than you," Ogras laughed. "Try again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I… I'll work for the Super Brother-Man as well!" Smaug said. "You should understand I'm good with money from my Ladder ranking."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People willing to work for The Super Brother-Man would be able to fill a country. Why should we risk letting a shady person like you close to our business interests?" Joanna asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll sign a contract of servitude! I'll make you money to the best of my abilities for 50 years!" he said, finally starting to panic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sounds annoying to have you around. Who knows what hidden troubles you would cause," Zac shrugged, lifting his sword as if he wanted to decapitate him just like the two merchants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait! I have an incomplete license with a limited product line!" Smaug screamed as he backed away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Five hundred years," Zac said, the sword frozen mid-swing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wh-" Smaug was about to exclaim, but forcibly stopped himself. "Five hundred, happy to be on board."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good. Joanna will be your handler," Zac said, "She is under a contract of servitude as well, so signing with her will be like signing with the Super Brother-Man."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smaug sighed, and soon enough he had entered a 500-year contract with Joanna. Smaug clearly had a complicated relationship with the truth, and Zac didn't want the man to know of his real identity. Having Joanna sign the contract still counted toward his contract limit though, and with all the Valkyries he only had four spots remaining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luckily the contracts to keep silent about his identity was a simple agreement between two parties, and those one could enter as many as one pleased. However, since it was a contract of reciprocity he needed to give something in return, which in his case was a monthly stipend for as long as the contract was active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Zac looked at Smaug's forlorn figure with some humor, knowing things were not really as they seemed. It might have appeared as though the man was forced to sign the contract, but that was simply impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless the man wanted to form a contract and work for him the contract wouldn't even materialize, proving that it was all a ploy. Zac guessed that the only thing that Smaug hadn't planned was to share the fact that he had an incomplete license.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, he got his hand on a helper that he sorely needed. He had wanted to find someone to manage his business interests while he focused on cultivation. As time passed his ventures only got more numerous, and someone needed to take charge. Zac himself didn't know exactly what he owned any longer as his empire kept expanding through conquest and development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's an incomplete license?" Zac asked when the contract was signed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have a mercantile class as you already know," Smaug shrugged, his sad demeanor already gone. "I got a quest to rise as high as possible on the Wealth ladder, and the license was the reward. I think I would have gotten a real license if it wasn't for your boss keeping the first spot for himself. Uh, our boss."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's the difference?" Zac asked, and even Ogras perked up in interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calrin had been pretty fleeting in his explanations about the mercantile system since the start, likely wanting to keep details vague so that others wouldn't know when he was scamming them. Ogras had no idea either, only knowing it enabled intergalactic trade as long as you fulfilled certain criteria. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Mercantile System is like a hidden website where you need to unlock every ware one by one. A Mercantile License is your login to the main website, but it is only the start from what I understand. You still need to perform various tasks to upgrade the license to give access to better wares and rates. My license is limited, meaning that it only lasts for 100 years, and I can only buy wares from a corporation called &lt;strong&gt;[Stumpbugle Bombs]&lt;/strong&gt;," Smaug explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's some name," Ogras whistled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a goblin company, and they make weird arrays, like the ones I… presented to you earlier," Smaug coughed. "They only sell consumable weapons, from simple arrays to weapons of mass destruction. I can't access those though."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We'll find some work for you. Remember, if we find you're working against the interest of Port Atwood…" Zac said, lifting &lt;strong&gt;[Hunger]&lt;/strong&gt; again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I know, I know," Smaug said with a disarming smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac would look further into that Smaug could bring to the table at a later date, but for now he wanted to focus on the Union. He saw no reason to change his plan just because Smaug had been lying. The Union still needed to be stopped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ogras had already made some preliminary reconnaissance while scouring the Union headquarters for Rima, and as luck would have it the top brass of the Union was holding an emergency meeting in response to suddenly losing the transit camp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the hostage was saved Zac felt there to be no need for any subversion as he walked toward the main gate of the newly erected wall that ran around the headquarters. It was guarded by over twenty cultivators, and the Union had even got their hands on some nasty-looking turrets placed upon the wall walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Halt! This is a restricted area," a guard shouted as the large mounted weapons turned toward Zac.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Super Brother-Man has judged the Union to be working with the foreign invaders. Stand down and you will not be hurt. We are only interested in the leaders," Zac said as his aura billowed out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The guards were shocked by the unexpected turn and looked at Zac like he was a primordial beast. It was no surprise since the strongest warriors of Earth could barely release an aura by now, whereas Zac's aura was heavy enough to almost feel like solid matter. Worse yet, it was rife with killing intent he had accumulated through his constant battles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few of the cultivators immediately ran away, not giving their companions a second look. But a few stood still with indecision on their faces. Seeing the guards not stand down Zac rolled his eyes and took out two metal balls from his cosmos sack, and threw them at the two turrets in quick succession. The balls ripped through the air and the weapons instantly turned to scrap metal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The display of might was all that was needed to sway the last few guards who remained, and Zac was able to push open the gate without having to kill anyone. But a shimmering wall suddenly stopped him in his tracks, and Zac frowned when he realized someone had activated a defensive array.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac quickly realized it was just a standard array bought from the Town Shop, and his right arm started swelling from infusing it with &lt;strong&gt;[Unholy Strike]&lt;/strong&gt;. He didn't even deign to push the skill to its limit before he punched out with enough force to make the air distort around his fist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The barrier shuddered and large cracks started to spread, but the barrier held fast. However, Zac only snorted and punched out again, making the shield completely crumble this time. Ogras, now completely shrouded in shadows, and the others walked through as this was the most normal thing in the world, leaving a shocked Smaug behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Monster," Smaug muttered from behind as he carried his unconscious sister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group ripped through the building without any resistance. Any time a guard or an employee saw their approach they needlessly ran away, no one even pretending to muster a resistance. It proved how fragile a force like the Union was in the face of true power. There were many weaker forces around, but many would put up a far fiercer resistance against invaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac followed Ogras' directions, but it was barely needed as he could sense a clump of weak auras gathered together at the same spot. With their superhuman speeds, it took them less than 20 seconds before they barged into a large hall, where almost forty people were seated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These were the leaders of the Union, and behind them stood just as many warriors with somewhat impressive auras. But both hesitation and unwillingness to act was clear on their faces as Zac, Verana, and Ogras all released their auras. It submerged the whole building in oppressive might, and most immediately threw their weapons on the ground in hopes of being spared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few tried to unleash desperate attacks on Zac's group, perhaps knowing their sins were too heavy to be spared if they were captured. But they were quickly and ruthlessly dealt with, leaving a dozen corpses on the ground. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the seated leaders tried to flee in the commotion, but between Ogras' shadow spears and Zac's oppressive aura they found themselves trapped. Zac looked over the group of fearful people, noticing that people from all races apart from Zhix were represented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is this them?" Zac asked with a sighed as he turned to Smaug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, a few people are missing, like Little Treasure and Copperfield, the Ishiate at the 11&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; spot of the wealth ladder," Smaug said as he looked across the room. "But this is over 80% of the top brass of the Union."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a bit disheartening to Zac to see this diverse ensemble. This group represented some of the best and the brightest of the underworld, bringing together not only strong warriors but skilled non-combat cultivators. The group even transcended the racial barriers, something the surface still hadn't accomplished. But instead of working together to rebuff the invaders, they had sold their souls for riches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Starting today, the Union and all its subsidiaries are under new management."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">502506</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 17:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 331 - Truths and Lies</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/502037</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Zac, who was about to head over to interrogate the two terrified merchants stopped in his tracks when he heard Emily's cry. He turned over with confusion to see the teenager clawing at the manacles binding a malnourished teenager.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't let those two move," Zac said to Joanna, who nodded in confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He walked over to Emily and with a tug ripped the chains apart, freeing the young woman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's going on?" he asked as he turned to Emily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is Millie, Camilla. She went to the same school as me. She's from Allentown!" she said with some panic in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac understood the thoughts running through her head. If one of her schoolmates had found herself captured by the Union, then it wasn't a great sign for the well-being of her siblings. They might even be in the large pile of corpses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Calm down, we'll get to the bottom of things," Zac said as he took out a healing pill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millie wasn't truly wounded, but she was clearly malnourished and it looked like she had been whipped judging by the tears in her tunic's back. But mostly she seemed to have shut down from trauma. She looked at Zac with a blank stare and only took the pill when he directly put it in her hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a healing pill," Zac said before taking a step back, aware of the immense pressure he had just released across the whole town.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Millie, it's me, Emily Larkin from Southfield High," she said as she handed Millie a canteen. "Hurry and take the pill to regain your strength."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mention of the school seemed to wake the girl out from her stupor, and she rapidly blinked at Emily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Emily? From class B? I never saw you in the tutorial, what's going on?" the girl asked, making some of the close-by slaves surreptitiously look over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was too young to enter the tutorial. We come from the surface," Emily explained after receiving a nod from Zac. "We work for the Super Brother-Man, and we have come to close the incursions in the Underworld. But when we arrived we heard about the Union capturing people and selling them to the invaders, so we came here first to free you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The words were like a match igniting a fire, and a wave of clamors for help rose from the captives. The situation felt a bit annoying, but when Zac looked around he couldn't find the demon or Verana anywhere. Both were keeping a low profile as to not spread any rumors about invaders before their position was completely solidified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What about the other cultivators of Allentown? Where are they?" Emily pressed on. "Do you know where my siblings are? Oscar and Johanna."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The town we were dropped off in was destroyed by the flame golems four months ago," Millie said with a sigh. "But most of us managed to flee since it had so many exits. Some of us settled in various towns, others joined the Union or the Council. I think your sister joined the Council to fight the invaders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And my brother? Do you know what happened to Oscar, Oscar Larkin?" Emily hurriedly asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He... Died…" Millie said, looking down at the ground. "He joined the town guard after the tutorial ended. The flame golems killed all the guards to cause chaos and slow our response."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily slumped down on the ground when she heard the news, a blank stare in her face. Zac sighed with a pang of sadness in his heart. He knew had been the most likely outcome from the start with how few that were still alive after the integration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's find your sister. She'll know what happened for sure," Zac said as he crouched down next to Emily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The teenager quickly perked up, desperately grasping on to his words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're right! Millie, you never saw Oscar die, right?" she said, getting a hesitant nod in response. "He might have survived!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac personally wasn't so sure, especially considering the actions of her sister. Joining the Council to fight the invaders sounded like something a person looking for revenge would do. But he didn't say anything, not wanting to dash her hopes. After giving the teenager a comforting pat he walked over to Joanna, who still kept guard over the terrified merchants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily's words had been heard by quite a few people in the camp, and the clamors from the slaves were getting louder and louder. Conversely, the guards had turned even more subdued, looking like they wished they could simply sink into the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can you handle this?" Zac asked with a wave toward the ruckus when he came back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure, but could you silence them first?" Joanna said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded, and another burst of his aura erupted through the camp, immediately cutting all conversations short. Joanna winked at him before jumping up at a rooftop, making her visible to all the captured slaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am Joanna Thompson, Ranked at the 96th spot of the power ladder," she said, her voice echoing across the camp. "As some of you heard, we come from the surface. Zachary Atwood, also known as the Super Brother-Man is currently busy closing the Incursions on the surface, leading humanity in the battle against the invaders. But after hearing of the plight of the Underworld he spared no expense to find a way to reach this place. We have come to liberate you all, and rebuff the underworld invaders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another wave of exclamations immediately erupted in the crowd. Some were jubilant while others were confused. There were also a decent number of people who suspiciously looked at the proceedings, perhaps not trusting such a fantastical tale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You might be skeptical, but let me show you something," Joanna said, and the next moment a System screen appeared in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the quest that she and the other Valkyries received after closing three Incursions, where they were supposed to assist in closing as many Incursions as possible within a month. It already showed the progress of four, meaning that golem incursion she assisted in closing before she received the quest was counted as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As you can see I have personally assisted the forces of Port Atwood in closing four incursions, just one shy of the total number of Incursions in the underworld. The Super Brother-Man has closed even more, sometimes only relying on his own power," she explained. "I only show you this to prove the truth of my words."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"However, when we finally arrived at the Underworld we quickly learned of the despicable acts of the Union, enslaving our people and siding with our enemies. The Super Brother-Man wouldn't stand for such a thing, so from today forth the Union will cease to exist," Joanna said, looking like a heroic general with the spear in her hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So please be patient. We will help everyone here, but it will take some time," she finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac felt a bit embarrassed by the grandiose speech, and he didn't really know what to say when the Valkyrie jumped back down on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lord Atwood works so hard, but never claims any credit," Joanna said as she pointedly looked at Zac. "Someone needed to speak up for him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He coughed and nodded in thanks before turning to the merchants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You- The Union are no traitors! We have worked hard to protect the people in the underworld!" one of the men said, but his eyes were skittering and the fear was clear on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac didn't bother responding only taking a pointed glance at the rows upon rows of captured slaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are facing an extinction event," the merchant said. "If we didn't provide people to the incursions they would start raiding our settlements, resulting in a far larger loss of life. Besides, these people are convicted criminals!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lies!" one of the slaves roared in anger. "We were only too poor to pay the protection fees of the Union."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After calling over Smaug and questioning both the merchants and a few of the slave's Zac finally got a full understanding of the situation. In the beginning, the Union truly only sold murderers, rapists, and other heinous criminals to the Incursions. It was a simple solution to get rid of dangerous people while also appeasing a very strong enemy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the Incursion's demands for slaves were insatiable, and the Union ran out of criminals soon enough. So eventually they started to capture anyone that didn't provide any benefits to them or was unable to pay the fees to live within their cities, convicting them with fabricated charges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When that wasn't enough they started to target whole settlements that wanted to relocate to the Union for safety. The slaves in the transit camp, including Emily's schoolmate, were almost all of the latter type, with a few enemies of the Union thrown in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both of the merchants were just middle-management sent to inspect the latest batch of slaves before delivery, and they knew nothing of the inner workings of the Union or the situation of Smaug's sister. They were also only level 35, their strength completely propped up by Crystals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac knew just how many crystals were needed to reach such a high level. The Nexus Crystals were a good boost for recovery, but they were only really useful for leveling right at the beginning of a stage. Even the E-Grade crystals he got his hands on were only enough for a scant few levels, and Zac had already confirmed that E-Grade crystals were still quite rare in the underworld as well. They were not something that these two people could get their hands on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soon enough there was nothing else the two merchants could divulge, and Zac ended their lives with two quick swipes of his sword before turning to Smaug. The merchants had already been doomed the moment they started to dabble in slavery, and the kills didn't even register in Zac's mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How do we get to New London?" Zac asked Smaug who looked down at the two lifeless bodies with some shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I own another hidden outpost an hour's travel away," Smaug quickly explained after he roused himself. "We should hurry. They have likely already realized that this place has been conquered. Hopefully they'll assume the invaders got tired of paying for the slaves and raided the place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Couldn't you have placed your teleporters closer?" Zac muttered with some complaint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's not possible, don't you know? If I placed it any closer a quest would start where only one town could remain within a month," Smaug said with a shake of his head. "Towns of competing factions can't be too close."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, there's such a thing?" Zac said with some surprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's true, and the distance only increases as the rank of the town is upgraded," Verana said as she walked over. "Lower-ranked towns can be pretty close, but capitals requires over a week of travel, limiting the number of kingdoms on a planet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded in understanding before dragging Smaug over to the building with the teleporter. The spatial disruption had already dissipated, which allowed Zac to bring a squad of soldiers over to handle the situation in the camp. Of course, the demons still stayed behind as to not expose their identities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The slaves would be transported to the Underworld Nexus for now, since staying at the transit camp wasn't an option. The camp was placed extremely close to the Incursion, and the invaders could come knocking at any moment. Zac felt there was no need to expend resources to defend it either since it held no strategic value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group of Ogras, Verana, Joanna, Smaug, and Emily once again joined Zac and left through the teleporter after the soldiers had taken charge of the slaves, quickly freeing them and sending them away. And thanks to Smaug they managed to quickly and effortlessly infiltrate New London. Smaug clearly had all kinds of contacts and confidantes, as they entered the large city through a hidden passageway that led into the cellar of a bar. When the owner noticed the group walking up the stairs he pretended to see nothing and simply went about his day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soon the group stood in an alley some distance from the sprawling headquarters of the Union. It was actually the Admiralty House of London that had been randomized to the Underworld along with a large section of downtown London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New London was the central hub of The Union, and it was one of the few large settlements that were placed in the open Underworld rather than in a town cave. This had benefited the Union quite a bit when the Flame Golems went on the offensive, flooding one cave after another. Hundreds of thousands of settlers had wanted to relocate to New London, rather braving the Underworld beasts than the Fire Golems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large conglomerate had claimed a large number of former Government buildings and turned them into their own. The old world government itself had quickly fallen with the return of the cultivators, and after a couple of tumultuous weeks, the Union became the premier force in the town. And with the help of the resources they got from the slave trade their grasp of the town was rock solid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll go fetch the girl," Ogras said without any preamble, holding a picture of a young girl in his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you sure you can do this?" Smaug said with worry as he took out a handful of things from his hidden space. "I have a few items-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ogras immediately snatched all of the treasures, though Zac suspected that the demon wouldn't need help to infiltrate some old-world structure with no real powerhouses standing guard. And just as Zac suspected the demon was back just twenty minutes later, with a squirming sack over his shoulder. Smaug immediately ran over to release his sister, but Ogras suddenly summoned his black spear and used it to keep the man at bay. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to have a little chat. This brat has been a captive for weeks, not a few hours as you said."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">502037</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 15:49:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 330 - Transit Camp</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/501641</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The scene below was even worse than Zac had feared when he first heard Smaug mention the slave trade. There were long rows of people kept in place by fetters, placed like cattle in small enclosures. All four races could be spotted amongst the slaves, though humans were by far the most common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Groups of slavers patrolled the area, and there were robust fortifications at all the exits to prevent any slaves from escaping from the cave. There was also a pile of corpses lying in plain view in the encampment, just a few meters from the pens where the slaves were kept. Perhaps they were left there as a deterrent, or perhaps they simply hadn't had time to throw the corpses out to the beasts in the open Underworld.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Underworld was quite different from how Zac had imagined it, and it was only after traveling for the last hour he realized that the Underworld wasn't an intricate network of tunnels and caverns. Most of the Underworld was actually an open expanse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prevalent belief amongst those who were teleported here was that the underworld was between two layers of tectonic plates or just between two rock sediments. It created a continuous subterranean landscape that sometimes had a ceiling height of thousands of meters, and sometimes it was so narrow that one had to crouch to move forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were even forests and arable farmland, though the things that could be grown were generally different types of edible moss or mushrooms. Rivers ran across the hilly grounds, and it if wasn't for the utter lack of sunlight, one might have forgotten they were underground. Instead, everything was illuminated by luminescent plants, creating a mesmerizing display of colorful spots that lit up the boundless darkness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most towns were constructed in caves like the one they were spectating through, as the open world was quite dangerous for most people. Enormous packs of mutated bats roved in the sky, and all kinds of subterranean beasts walked the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the insects had mutated and turned into monstrous creatures in the underworld, perhaps due to the massive amount of Nexus Crystals boosting the energy in the atmosphere. Getting caught in ten-meter tall spiderwebs or skewered by a scorpion pincer were both real risks in the underworld. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extremely solid rock walls of the caverns made for a natural defense against the horrors of the underworld, and people only had to fortify the cave exits to create a safe space. Top tier caves were the ones who possessed a natural ecosystem to sustain them, like the cave the Underworld Nexus was built inside, with its own lake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was this reliance on caves that the Flame Golems exploited in with their ruthless tactics. They simply blocked up the few exits in the town before flooding it with lava. A few of the citizens had time to rush to a teleportation array, but most towns didn't possess one and could only helplessly wait to get swallowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tunnel they stood in was something that Smaug himself had created to spy on the slaving activities of the Union. It ran for hundreds of meters from a hidden spot in the open underworld, with both sides hidden by arrays. The walls of the tunnel looked oddly melted, and Zac guessed that Smaug had used some treasure to somehow melt the extremely hard stones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being reminded that the mysterious fellow might be useful during the fight Zac released the energy restraints that shackled Smaug. Of course only after giving him a stern warning to not mess around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But any interest in finding out Smaug's hidden means was long pushed to the back of Zac's head as he looked down at the misery beneath them. He was just about to jump down and start a rampage when the energy in the camp started to fluctuate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The teleportation array just activated," Ogras commented as he looked down with curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This transit camp was located close to the human incursion since the invaders they traded with weren't able to use teleportation arrays. This also meant that whoever was arriving was not an invader, but rather someone from the Union. The fluctuations soon ended and a small group of people emerged from a building not too far away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Here, use this," Smaug suddenly said, producing yet another ball from nowhere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A temporal destabilizer?" Ogras said with surprise. "Where did you get your hands on this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A what?" Zac asked with confusion as he looked down on the thing in Smaug's hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The teleporters transport people through subspace or whatever the fantasy equivalent is," Smaug said. "If you crush this ball within 50 meters of the teleporter subspace will be made unstable and safeguards in the array will make it impossible to activate for 10 minutes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac shot a glance at Ogras who nodded in confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can you get your hands on more of this?" Zac asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was an extremely convenient item that could change the course of a battle. It would make sure that his target wasn't able to escape, or that his activities wouldn't leak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is my last one, I got it as a reward for a quest," Smaug said with a shake of his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac looked into Smaug's eyes for a few seconds, but he couldn't tell if the man was lying or not. In any case, there would be time to find out more after the situation in the underworld was stabilized. So he grabbed the ball with a nod, and Zac leaped straight out from their hiding spot immediately after, with Emily throwing a fiery axe into his back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac soared straight toward the large stone building the group of people emerged from. It was likely the place that housed the teleportation array, as it was guarded by a squad of soldiers armed to their teeth. With Zac's power, he had no problem jumping all the way to the structure, and he ripped through the air toward the soldiers like a falling star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Attack!" one of the guards shouted with panic in his eyes as he spotted Zac in the air, but the next moment he was crushed by the massive weight of Zac's shield as it slammed straight into him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac's landing killed three of the guards and threw the others in the air from the kinetic energy in his landing. He immediately crushed the orb in his hand before taking out his sword. &lt;strong&gt;[Hunger]&lt;/strong&gt; keened as it turned into a grey streak, dismembering the remaining seven guards in a flash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With his attributes, it didn't matter that he barely possessed any offensive skills in his current class. Against random warriors on Earth he was essentially an unkillable monster. The commotion alerted the soldiers stationed in the camp, and they streamed toward his location. There were actually over a hundred of them, most having stayed out of sight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac didn't mind that as he instead turned his attention toward the group who had just arrived. It was two middle-aged men dressed in some sort of defensive gear, but it was clear they were not warriors. They had no weapons and they did not emit any dangerous aura, making Zac believe they were businessmen from the Union.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This belief was only strengthened by the four bodyguards who accompanied the two. The moment Zac had arrived they created a protective barrier in front of the merchants, and they didn't care in the slightest that Zac dismembered their presumptive allies. They were only interested in protecting the two VIP's. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yet another idealistic fool trying to rescue these wretched people?" one of the merchants sneered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac didn't answer, instead unleashing both his aura and &lt;strong&gt;[Fields of Despair]&lt;/strong&gt;. The insidious energies from the splinter in his mind were already magnifying the rage in his heart, and it somehow entered his aura as well. It made his killing intent almost palpable, and a few soldiers actually started to bleed from their noses or ears when they were buffeted by his aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The soldiers were obviously not part of some elite force, and the hastily erected line the warriors just formed immediately collapsed, with over half heedlessly fleeing from the towering killing intent that radiated from Zac. The four bodyguards were better off, but they still slowly backed away, likely looking for an opportunity to escape as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Activate the array!" one of the merchants screamed in fright, the arrogant demeanor replaced with abject horror. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An immense weight immediately descended upon Zac, but how could some random restrictive array stop his onslaught? He had ripped through even stronger arrays when he was looting summit palaces during the hunt, and since then he had only grown even more monstrous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He took a step forward with a grunt, and a loud snapping sound could be heard as a shockwave was released from his body. The sound came from the array collapsing from brute force, and the sight was so shocking that one of the merchants fell to his knees in despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait!" the still standing merchant screamed when Zac started to approach them. "We can pay you! One hundred million Nexus Coins! Just let us leave with our lives!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac was completely indifferent to the pleas, and he steadily took step after step toward the group. The stationed soldiers of the town had given up any idea of sticking their noses into the battle, and one after one they started to flee toward the various exits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But long before anyone managed to escape through one of the tunnels they fell over with large holes in their bodies, caused by some unseen attacks. Zac noted the shadowy spears that appeared and quickly disappeared though, and he realized that Ogras and the others were containing everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't care that Ogras killed these soldiers at all since they had been complicit to the horrors of this place. If he had been in his human form he would have already mowed down that rabble with a few fractal edges. But he was currently out of ranged attacks since his shield's spike attack still hadn't recharged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Two hundred million! And precious cultivation pills!" the merchant screamed when Zac ignored him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You forfeited your lives the moment you betrayed humanity," Zac said a hollow voice. "I do not need your blood money."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four guards disappeared the moment Zac finished his sentence, but they immediately appeared all around him. Their weapons were already sailing toward his body the moment they reappeared, and it looked like they tried a surprise attack as a last-ditch-effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four guards were likely around level 40 to 45 from their auras, just a handful of levels shy from entering the ladder. But Zac also sensed that their auras were, for a lack of a better word, hollow. He hadn't sensed anything like it before, but he had learned from Alyn that it likely meant their levels were mostly propped up by pills and crystals rather than battle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All four of them were sword wielders, and it even looked like they possessed the same skill. The swords lit up in blue flames as they sailed toward Zac's body from four different directions, but Zac opted to not even respond to the attacks, instead only activating the Dao of Hardness across his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four specters appeared and launched attacks the moment the swords landed on his body. It was &lt;strong&gt;[Deathwish]&lt;/strong&gt; that activated, starting the dance of death. Zac could easily have intercepted the attacks with his sword, but he wanted to see the effect of his skill against cultivators since he hadn't sensed any real danger from the attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were surprisingly different even though each attack was the same. One of the guards was taken completely by surprise and didn't even react when a spectral sword slit his throat open. He fell down on the ground, and Zac knew the man would bleed out in less than a minute unless he got immediate medical attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second guard managed to react in time and angled his body as he was being attacked, changing the trajectory of the blade as it entered his body. Instead of getting his heart pierced he only got a lung punctured. It was still a pretty bad wound, but not lethal with the existence of healing pills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A golden shield appeared around the last two warriors, completely blocking the reflected attack. The shield came from a bracer they both wore. They originally had four crystals inlaid, but one of them cracked when the shield blocked the attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pleased with the result of &lt;strong&gt;[Dethwish]&lt;/strong&gt; Zac killed the man on the ground with a stomp as he decapitated the wounded guard with a swing of &lt;strong&gt;[Hunger]&lt;/strong&gt;. His own wounds were negligible, and he only needed to pat his robe a few times to snuff out the flames. A small amount of black ichor ran down his throat from one of the swords hitting his neck, but the swing had barely managed to break his skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The remaining two guards looked at Zac with despair, knowing that they never would be able to kill Zac even if he didn't put up any resistance. Zac's body was already far sturdier than that of the Corpse Lord he fought during the beast waves, and only the strongest warriors on Earth would be able to wound him by now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two immediately started to run away, they were soon rebuffed by two lightning-quick stabs from a long spear. It was Joanna who had joined the battle, and Nenothep's spear was a blur in her hands as she unleashed a barrage of attacks at the two guards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac stopped in his tracks when he saw the Valkyrie take over, and he looked with interest at how deftly she handled her weapon. The two bodyguards assaulted at her like rabid dogs since she was standing in the way of their escape, and flames danced around them as they tried everything to cut her down. However, she was like an impenetrable spear wall, not budging an inch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The remaining defensive charges on the guards' bracers were expended in less than 20 seconds, and a few seconds later the last guard fell, his throat torn open by a quick stab from Joanna. The Valkyrie's skills weren't flashy but they were direct and lethal, without any frills or unnecessary motion. Every move she performed was to kill or maim with as little energy expenditure as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the last of the elite guards fell a suffocated silence spread through the camp, with no one daring to speak up. There was a small group of soldiers who stood rooted at their spot, neither daring to retreat or advance, and the merchants looked like their souls had left their bodies, blankly staring at their downed bodyguards. Even the slaves were completely silent, peeking at the proceedings with sunken eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But suddenly the silence was broken by a shocked scream from Emily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Millie!"&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">501641</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 16:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 329 - Negotiations</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/501211</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As Zac oversaw his people streaming out through the teleporter a thought suddenly struck him, and he motioned for Harvath to join him. The demon captain walked over, throwing a curious glance at Smaug and his wretched appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We've learned that there is a second demonkin Incursion in the underworld," Zac explained after covering them in a sound-isolating array. "Will it be a problem for you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harvath thoughtfully furrowed his brows before he looked at Smaug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Does this one possess information about our cousins?" he asked, getting a nod from Zac.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smaug himself gaped when he stood in front of the demon, making Zac realize the man had never stood face to face with one of the invaders before. It looked like he was hovering between fear of being eaten and fascination with the unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do these demons look like us?" Harvath asked, pointing at his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"N-No, not really," Smaug stammered. "Well, they have horns, but I am told that they look a lot bulkier, and don't have hair?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Big black horns?" Harvath probed, "And they are over two meters tall?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes!" Smaug hurriedly nodded. "And tails."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Abyssal Demons," Harvath said with a grimace before turning to Zac. "Can we speak privately?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded and had Verana take over the task of keeping a watch on Smaug. He still didn't understand how he could take out items when he was stripped of his possessions, and Zac didn't want him to take out something else and cause even more trouble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's going on?" Zac asked when the two were alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harvath hesitated a bit before speaking up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you know how Demon society works?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Isn't it a feudal society? Your former clan controls a certain area, but you are part of a larger kingdom. That kingdom ultimately reports to the planet's leader, though they are largely independent," Zac asked with some confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's true for our planet, but our planet is just a backwater member of something larger," Harvath said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Azh'Kir'Khat Horde?" Zac ventured, remembering Verana mentioning the odd name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Exactly," Harvath nodded. "I am not too sure about all the details since clan Azh'Rezak was the lowest rung of what could be called a noble clan, and our information was somewhat limited. But the horde consists of hundreds of demonic species."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded, still not sure what he was getting at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The position of the races in the horde depends on their respective powerhouses at the top. The Abyssal Demons has a terrifying leader who controls one of the top ten clans, making them one of the most prominent demonic species in the horde. These Abyssal Demons are likely not part of that clan, but they still hold some sway back home. I fear that if we rout them it might have dire implications for clan Azh'Rezak," Harvath said with some hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded with a sigh. It was as Zac had feared. He hadn't expected running into a second demonkin Incursion on Earth, and he knew it might cause trouble for the demons of Port Atwood, or rather their former clan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if they left their clan behind many still had people they cared for back home. Even Ogras had his grandfather. Everyone had friends or relatives who were still part of the clan, and while they chose to cut ties to forge their own path they didn't want to bring trouble down on the head of Azh'Rezak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So what do you think we should do?" Zac finally asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I cannot make this decision for our people," Harvath finally said. "I think we should call the young master."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac agreed with the demon's assessment. Exploring the Mystic Realm was important, but they had other pressing matters. It would be for the best to call Ogras over now that it turned out that there were four other Incursions in the underworld that weren't fire-attuned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fine, I'll have someone get Ogras," Zac agreed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac had one of the Valkyries head over to the mystic realm to look for Ogras. Most people still didn't know that the realm was already being explored, though scattered rumors had started to spread about its existence. But he wanted to keep the details Vague, so only the Valkyries and a few other core personnel were allowed close to the center of Mystic Island. It had turned to a restricted area just like his own zone in Port Atwood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since he knew it would take some time before Ogras arrived he decided to deal with some other matters. First he went over to Calrin, who seemed extremely impatient to get going.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I hear we're taking over a rival business?" Calrin said with excitement in his eyes. "It's quite exhilarating, all that free money. It's a lot harder to do something like this when mercantile licenses are involved. We truly should consolidate all budding enterprises before people manage to get their hands on licenses."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac understood what Calrin meant. His own consortium was targeted by a mighty C-grade Clan, but even they had been forced to use trickery and bribes to steadily whittle down the Thayer Consortia for an eventual takeover. Brute force was not an option when mercantile licenses were involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll consider it," Zac said with a smile. "Do you know if Cosmos Sacks can take different shapes than actual sacks?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"High-grade spatial tools can look like rings or other jewelry, or anything for that matter," Calrin said. "But it's usually not worth the trouble unless you're a true magnate. That kind of spatial tools requires actual insight into the Dao of Space to create, making them over a thousand times more expensive. Why do you ask?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That guy over there managed to take out an item from thin air. I am trying to figure out how," Zac said as he glanced at Smaug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh," Calrin said thoughtfully before a small dagger suddenly appeared in his hand from nowhere, without touching one of his Cosmos Sacks. "Like this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, exactly like that," Zac said with surprise. "How did you do it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He has a mercantile class or at least a hybrid class. We get actual skills that work like Cosmos Sacks, allowing us to hide and protect our wares as we travel. A Cosmos Sack can be stolen, but our personal space can't."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Makes sense, he's the second-place holder on the wealth ladder," Zac nodded. "Is there any way to prevent it?" &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure, if you have energy shackles," Calrin nodded. "If he can't circulate his energy he won't be able to activate his skill."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac's eyes lit up and he immediately produced the chain that he stowed away when he saved Thea from the Medhin clan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Will this work?" Zac asked as he handed it over to Calrin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's not a high-quality restraint, but it should suffice against someone like him," Calrin nodded. "I'll handle it. I am a bit curious about him anyway."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded and let Calrin walk away with the chain. Soon enough everyone had entered the Underworld, but Zac chose to wait for Ogras to arrive before deciding on the next course of action. He instead erected an array and sat down to absorb a few Miasma crystals to restore his energy reserves and rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't know how long he had rested when he sensed a person close-by, and he saw the familiar form of Ogras when he opened his eyes. He temporarily deactivated the array and let the demon enter. Ogras looked annoyed for some reason, making Zac look at him curiously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not making headway with the Mystic Realm? It's only been a day," Zac said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can't believe those Abyssal assholes got placed in the middle of a mountain of resources with no enemies in sight while I got stuck with you," Ogras muttered, obviously having been appraised of the situation in the underworld. "The Ruthless Heavens is truly playing favorites. I say we take down that incursion first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And that is your unbiased opinion?" Zac snorted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not really, but it makes sense. The sooner we kick those people out of here the sooner the demons will be able to act in the open. Most demons would be hesitant to show their faces with them lurking in the area," Ogras shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Agreed. We'll keep the demons hidden while we deal with the Union," Zac said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How will we split the profits?" Ogras asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was something that Zac had thought about earlier. He was currently the de-facto owner of pretty much everything in Port Atwood, but that wasn't a long-term solution. He didn't plan on becoming a tyrant with people toiling under his hegemony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All matters related to the underworld will be considered a separate company from Port Atwood and the Thayer Consortia. Port Atwood will own half and the Academy will own 10% to become self-sustaining," Zac said. "You, Verana, and Calrin can figure out what to do with the rest."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Isn't it a bit early to start giving those people a bunch of benefits?" Ogras said with a frown as he nodded at a clump of Tal-Eladar close-by. "Furthermore, Calrin should be a trading partner rather than a shareholder."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As I thought, you are up to no good the moment you arrive," a frosty voice said as Verana walked straight through the array.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No manners, spying on a private conversation," Ogras retorted with a straight face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait, where's Smaug?" Zac said with a frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I knocked him out when I saw this demon approach you with greed in his eyes and deceit in his heart," Verana said. "I had no choice but to listen in to make sure he didn't do anything stupid."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Be careful, I don't want to turn the guy into a vegetable. I've already knocked him out once, it can't be good for you for that to happen over and over," Zac said with a shake of his head. "What's your proposal?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Twenty percent to my clan, ten each to the demons and the merchant," Verana said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Negotiation comes from a place of power. You're barely bringing anything to the table and want twenty percent?" Ogras snorted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you?" Verana retorted. "Your people won't fight against the demons. My people are arguing about who gets to be the vanguard."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But the beasts of your soldiers will be limited in the underworld. Besides, this isn't just about how much effort each party exerts in the underworld. The citizens of Port Atwood has slaved away for months with hundreds dying. The resources of this place will be used to repay those who have bled for our force," Ogras retorted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac sighed as he listened to the two bicker, and things only got more chaotic when the Sky Gnome joined in. In the end the Demons went victorious from the battle, largely thanks to Zac's support. They would get 25% of the shares, with Verana getting 10% and Calrin 5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calrin wasn't happy, but he would still make a lot of money from the Underworld since he would become the sole trading partner for the Underworld Venture, while also setting up a network of Thayer Consortia shops through the Underworld to rid all the wealthy Cultivators of their Crystals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verana was less than enthused with the results as well, but what Ogras said was true. The demons had risked their lives for Port Atwood over and over without any payment apart from getting to pick a skill. They were long overdue to reap some benefits for their work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, what's the plan? Are we heading straight to this Union?" Verana asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get Smaug first," Zac said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soon the merchant was dragged over, and he sat down opposite Zac after throwing Verana a sullen look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Isn't it a bunch of merchants without a license to protect them?" Ogras said after throwing Smaug a dismissive glance. "Just kick down the front door and kill everyone who disagrees with the change in management."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No! They might kill my sister if you storm their headquarters like that!" Smaug shouted with worry. "Their Arrays will be able to hinder you for a minute or two, who knows what they will do in the meantime?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fine. I'll save the girl first, then Mr. Black and Snake Girl will kick in the front door," Ogras said with a roll of his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Snake girl?" Verana said with a frosty tone. "Just, keep it up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need proof what you've said is true," Joanna cut in before the two leaders started bickering again. "Do you know where they keep slaves, and where your sister is kept?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes to both!" Smaug nodded enthusiastically. "I have created a private network, I can bring us within an hour's travel from one of their transit camps where they keep slaves before they are sold off. My sister is likely kept at their headquarters."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fine, we'll take a look at the camp before taking down their headquarters. This group is enough for that, no need to bring the soldiers. They'll be sent to stabilize the various mines and subsidiaries after we've made our move," Zac said. "Agreed?" &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others nodded in agreement, with Ogras and Verana adding a few suggestions. Zac closed down the array and the group immediately walked toward the teleportation array. Suddenly their group grew with three people as Emily and two helpless Valkyries joined in. He down looked at the teenager for a second, and only got a stubborn look in return. He sighed and nodded slightly, drawing a wide grin from the girl.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Less than an hour later the group stood in a cave mouth, overlooking a large encampment twenty meters below them. An illusion array had already been installed by the exit, obscuring it from the people walking along the streets in the transit camp. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Animals," Joanna growled as she looked at the scene with wide eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac slightly nodded in agreement, anger burning in his heart as he listened to the cries from the shackled people below. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We proceed. The Union will cease to exist today."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">501211</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 16:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 328 - Captive</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/500357</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Zac looked down at Smaug that was still being kept at sword-point, unsure what to think about the rapid change in his demeanor. It looked like he was truly telling the truth about his sister, but it wouldn't be surprising if the second-place holder on the wealth ladder was someone adept at deception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides, even if he was telling the truth, did it even matter? Zac if anyone could sympathize with the desire to save and protect one's sister, but the fact remained that Smaug had launched a terrifying barrage of attacks on them. If Zac wasn't strong enough he and his people would have been blasted to pieces by the offensive arrays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Zac finally decided it was worth to keep asking questions before deciding what to do about this man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why would the Union want to attack us?" Zac finally asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They are working with the invaders," Smaug said, looking relieved Zac held off on skewering him. "Not the flame golem one, but the others. They are trying to take all of Earth's natural resources for themselves. The invaders provide the Union with pills and other items that are hard to get down here, and the Union provides them with raw resources and Slaves."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Slaves?" Zac repeated with a frown, though it couldn't be seen through his mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have been investigating them for months. Some settlements that were said to be eradicated by the golems were actually captured by the Union's people and sold to the invaders for forced labor," Smaug wheezed. "They don't want you here because they are afraid their profiteering will be cut short."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should know that if we fell the Super Brother-Man would just come here in person," Zac retorted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By that time they would have been able to turn black to white, pinning all the blame on me," Smaug sighed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Still, it's quite the coincidence that they managed to kidnap your sister just when we arrived, and immediately had you attack us?" Zac said. "We haven't even been in the underworld for an hour."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't know how, but they must have known her identity for some time. I had bodyguards around her, but more than half turned out to be the Union's men. They acted just 5minutes after you left with Farid," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac was about to continue the line of questions but the sound of disturbed rubble from behind stopped him in his tracks. He turned around to see it was Joanna who had come over, her spear at the ready. Zac quickly deactivated the array, making her almost launch an attack at him in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get the others, but just our people," Zac said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No problem. The manager started running for his life the moment the fighting subsided," Joanna nodded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait, help me disarm this guy first," Zac said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joanna understood what he meant, and she quickly took off every piece of equipment on Smaug that might have been a treasure. Soon enough a small mound of jewelry lay to the side of the man, and Joanna had even found a few talisman papers stuck to his inner thighs. He was truly a walking arsenal, decked head to toe with treasures. Even Calrin would likely have to admit defeat against that kind of collection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A minute later the whole Port Atwood party stood hidden within an array, and Zac recounted his exchange with Smaug, whose real name turned out to be Hassan. He was originally from Syria, but had lived in Europe the past years with his sister. However, it looked like Hassan had completely discarded his old identity, and insisted of being called Smaug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What forces do the four Incursions contain?" Mr. Trang asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One looks like humans, though they have vertical pupils," Smaug quickly said, still stressed even though Zac no longer pointed a sword at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verana's snake had instead scuttled over to his shoulder and was seemingly napping with its head against his throat. But Smaug was obviously aware of the snake's power since he had turned extremely pale the moment the snake moved over to him. After that he became even more cooperative, and it felt like he couldn't spill all the secrets of the underworld quick enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One has literal demons, it's pretty crazy. Horns and everything. These two are the ones who have bought the most slaves. They keep mostly to themselves, relentlessly mining. The third has some odd walking fish or something, they look pretty scary. I don't think the Union works with them, they attack everything," Smaug explained. "The fourth is the fire golems, and they are the strongest. But there is actually a fifth incursion"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A fifth?" Zac asked with surprise. "The guard earlier said there was only four."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I only know about them because of a leak in the Union. They have never appeared and they are even more holed up than the first two incursions. I have no idea what they are up to, but I guess they're busy mining as well," Smaug shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac didn't care too much about there being a fifth incursion. The fact that they kept to themselves hopefully meant that they didn't feel confident in their strength to expand, and instead opted to gather as many resources as possible from their area. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do the Underworld Council work with the invaders as well?" Joanna asked next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not really, though they are indirectly benefitting from them. They buy things from the Union that they, in turn, have gotten from the invaders. And they almost exclusively fight with the fishmen and the fire golems, so I'm pretty sure they know about the dealings with the other incursions," Smaug explained. "It's all pretty muddy down here, no clear black and white."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac slowly nodded, not feeling the actions of the Council was too big of a deal. They had their hands full as it was, and if they could get resources from the one incursion to fight another it was making the best of a bad situation. It wouldn't be too late to turn their attention toward the demons and invading humans after the more dangerous invaders were dealt with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He felt the actions of the Union to be far more troublesome. He had seen the treatment of slaves on the surface, and he knew that almost no force would treat them as well as Verana had. To profiteer from something like that in a time of crisis was beyond reprehensible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could have looked the other way if the Union just traded normally with the invaders, but since they decided to use their own people as currency he knew he would have to act. If it was true that the Union sells people as slaves to the invaders they didn't need to continue existing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When they had gotten all out of Smaug that they could Zac suddenly flashed forward and knocked Smaug out cold, giving the rest some privacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So what do you guys think?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That Union seems even more shady than the New World Government," Joanna said with disgust. "If they are into the slave trade I'm sure they're doing all kinds of evil stuff."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think it's a good target for a take-over," Verana said, drawing skeptical glances from the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's not kid ourselves," the Beast Master said with a roll of her eyes. "Getting our hand on the resources for our war efforts is one of the main objectives of this expedition. If we kill the leaders of this Merchant Organization and put our own people there we'll have a working infrastructure for everything from Teleportation Arrays to Mines to personnel. We will even gain their intelligence which is likely invaluable."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Will their people even work for us?" Zac asked hesitantly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The rabbits in the forest do not care which wolf is the pack alpha. They just want to survive," Verana said with a shrug. "We can simply cleanse the arm of the organization that dealt in slavery if it bothers you, and claim the rest."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I agree. You have so much to deal with as is," Joanna said. "This will save a lot of time, allowing us to focus on what's important."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Trang nodded in agreement as well, essentially meaning the matter was decided since Zac felt it was the most convenient method as well. But there was still one issue remaining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fine. We'll confirm what Smaug said about the slave trade. If what he says is true we'll take control of the Union, taking out everyone at the top" Zac said before motioning at the unconscious man on the ground. "What do we to about this guy though?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I say keep him," Joanna said. "He might seem like a helpless victim, but he must be hiding some secrets. He has been on the top of the Wealth ladder all this time, even eclipsing people like Thea Marshall and Billy who both have closed Incursions. Besides, he attacked us so he owes us restitution, but there is no way his real wealth is on his person"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think we should help the sister if possible," Mr. Trang added. "The child was captured because of our arrival, after all. She's innocent in all this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fair enough," Zac agreed. "Wake him up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joanna took out a bottle of water and poured it over his face, making him wake up sputtering and disoriented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will help save your sister," Joanna said. "And we'll also take care of the Union if what you've said is true. Of course, if it turns out that you've been lying we'll remove you and Dragonwing Enterprises from the underworld."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My words are as true as gold!" the man hurriedly said. "But the Union must know something is wrong by now. We've been here for a while, they must wonder what's going on. I have an idea, but you must trust me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Trust you?" Zac snorted, but the next moment his eyes widened in alarm as Smaug produced another crystal from nowhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac's mind blanked out for a second when he saw the pitch-black ball in Smaug's hand. The first thing Joanna had looked for on his body was a cosmos sack, but there was nothing like that on him. They had assumed he simply left it behind before going into battle because he was afraid of losing his wealth. But they were obviously wrong since he still was able to produce objects from nowhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it was just another fire-spewing crystal Zac wouldn't be too worried, but he was actually quite familiar with the thing in Smaug's hand. It was a &lt;strong&gt;[Void Ball]&lt;/strong&gt;, identical to the one Zac found during the hunt, and something he still kept on his person as an ace. If that thing went off in this close proximity then even he would perish, since it would release an onslaught of spatial tears destroying everything in the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verana seemed to realize the danger as well, and energy blasted out from her as she started to activate some protective treasure. Zac was much more straightforward and aimed to kill Smaug before he could set the thing off. But before Zac's swing could reach the man the world lurched, making Zac lose his balance and fall to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sprung right back up, but he froze when he realized that the surroundings had completely changed. Everyone was there, but they clearly were no longer in the ruins of the Dragonwing complex. Instead they found themselves in some hidden chamber illuminated by a few Day Crystals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac's eyes immediately snapped to Smaug and he was relieved to see that the &lt;strong&gt;[Void Ball]&lt;/strong&gt; was nowhere in sight. But he was still infuriated by that brush with death, and he immediately resumed his advance on him as killing intent started leaking. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait! I needed to make the Union think you were dead, or at least unsure what happened! Otherwise they might have harmed my sister!" Smaug hurriedly explained as he scrambled away from Zac. "So I activated the bomb and used a teleportation treasure to move us to my predesignated spot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And you are aware that a &lt;strong&gt;[Void Ball]&lt;/strong&gt; disrupts space, making teleportation an extremely dangerous venture even before it sets off?" Verana said with a voice that could turn water to ice. "We are lucky to not arrive here in a dozen pieces."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Uh…" was all that Smaug said in response, a sheepish smile spreading on his face as he shrunk further back from the four murderous stares. "Well, there was no instruction manual when I got that thing. My bad, truly."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The bomb should have destroyed everything in the area where we stood. Hopefully, the Union thinks I took most of you out before escaping. This place is my hidden compartment beneath the Underworld Nexus. I have a private Teleportation array here," Smaug continued, clearly wanting to change the subject. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A minute later the group arrived at the hidden teleportation array, with Smaug sporting swollen lips, a crooked nose, and two black eyes giving him the fabled panda-look. Joanna and Mr. Trang immediately stepped through the teleporter after shooting a last glare at the man, leaving the trio of Zac, Verana, and Smaug behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just moments later battle-hardened warriors of three races started to stream through the teleporter, filling the spacious hall that the teleporter was placed in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What is going on?" Smaug stammered as his swollen eyes stared at the demons and the Tal-Eladar all emitting powerful auras. "Those are invaders!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They were invaders," Zac corrected him. "Now they fight for the Super Brother-Man."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shit, that guy must be a real monster," Smaug muttered with some awe in his voice. "If he can even make those bloodthirsty demons fight for him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You have no idea."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">500357</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 16:19:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 327 - Billionaires' Brawl</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/500015</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A massive wave of electricity slammed into Zac's shield as he imbued himself with the Dao of Hardness. The ball had been something similar to his own&lt;strong&gt; [Thunder Punishment],&lt;/strong&gt; though the energies were far more concentrated. It gave up the massive area of &lt;strong&gt;[Thunder Punishment]&lt;/strong&gt; but instead gained a far greater intensity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A scream from behind told Zac that his shield wasn't' able to properly block out the energies as it was, and he tried imbuing &lt;strong&gt;[Immutable Bulwark]&lt;/strong&gt; with the Dao of Sanctuary to see if it would change anything. The shield quickly started transforming, turning into something that looked like a wall that circled his group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dao imbuement apparently changed the way the shield worked, where it gave up some of its strength to instead be able to protect from all directions. Luckily the durability of the shield was still enough even though it was spread out over a wider area. The problem was that the Miasmic consumption drastically increased, though he would be able to keep it up for some time before he started to run out of energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Zac didn't want to wait for his attacker to tire himself or herself out, and he looked in all directions for the source of the attack. But it was impossible to see a thing through the storm of lightning outside the protective shield, and he could only growl in frustration. Joanna meanwhile looked ready to rip the Dragonwing manager into pieces as she threw him down on the ground and pointed her spear at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's going on?" she spat out through grit teeth. "Who's attacking us?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I swear I do not know! We have had some friction with the Union lately, perhaps it's them?" the manager frantically said, trying to keep his head as far away from the spearhead as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soon enough the lightning storm abated, but Zac barely had time to glance around before a dozen more spheres flew toward them, releasing an inferno of flames that tried to eat through his protective layers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac sighed as he realized that whoever was attacking them was unwittingly a pretty good counter to his undead class. He had activated &lt;strong&gt;[Deathwish]&lt;/strong&gt; the moment he realized they were under attack, but he sensed that it hadn't been used even once. It meant the skill didn't work against treasures, allowing their attacker to go on as he pleased without receiving any retribution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you want me to help out?" Verana suddenly asked from behind, not sounding alarmed in the slightest even though flames raged all around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No need," Zac said after a brief pause. "Protect the others while I deal with this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verana would likely not have too much trouble dealing with this attacker, but Zac wanted to gain some experience in fighting in his undead form. He had only fought dumb animals when using Undying Bulwark, most of them turned even more rabid and irrational from the Darkness in the caverns beneath the Eastern Trigram Sect. Fighting a person in disadvantageous conditions felt like a pretty good way to find the limitations and strengths of his current class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, Zac managed to spot a hooded figure in the distance, and he immediately activated &lt;strong&gt;[Inquisitive Eye]&lt;/strong&gt; to get some idea about their attacker. But either the man possessed tremendous Intelligence, or more likely he owned a protective treasure because Zac could not even get the man's name from the skill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The limits of the ocular skill were once shining through, and Zac was starting to wonder if it was even worth that he relearned and evolved the skill for his undead form. But he was still unable to get his hands on a better option, as the only ancillary skill that the lowest floor of his Dao Repository contained was &lt;strong&gt;[Thousand Faces]&lt;/strong&gt;. Hopefully, there would be some more options for supportive skills on the next floor, as those were the only skills that seemed to work for both his classes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looked like the man in the distance was imbuing yet another ball with Cosmic Energy, though this one shuddered with another type of energy than electricity. Zac didn't want to give him time to lob yet another of those things at him and slammed his shield into the ground with a roar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A huge shockwave of spikes ripped out of the ground and pushed toward the masked man with great speed, destroying anything in its path. It was the attack engraved into the shield itself, and its effect was even better than Zac had expected. The attacker looked up in alarm, but before he could move the wave of spikes was upon him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A green shimmer appeared around the masked attacker, and the spikes immediately turned into a murky liquid formed a corrosive pool on the ground. Zac tsk'ed in annoyance and pushed forward, inwardly annoyed with the lack of movement options in his undead class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he was still extraordinarily fast due to his massive pool of Dexterity, and Zac was upon the man before he could finish fueling the next offensive array. But the masked attacker seemed to possess an almost endless bag of tricks, and two of his rings lit up when Zac swung his sword down with furious momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man disappeared in the blink of an eye, replaced with a large head of a humanoid skeleton that radiated extremely sinister energies. Zac's brows rose in surprise, but before he had time to create any distance the skeleton spewed out a large gust of a grey haze, covering every inch of his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac froze for a second, but he soon realized the odd attack simply had no effect on him. He once again thanked the cheat-like constitution of a Draugr, realizing that the mist was likely some poison his undead body was immune to. He swung his huge tower shield with a grunt, creating a gust that blew the mists away, and he immediately spotted the man in the distance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Smaug?" Zac ventured, and the man stopped moving before once again starting to prepare for his next wave of assaults, pretty much confirming his hunch. "Why are you attacking us? Port Atwood and The Super Brother-Man has no enmity with you or your faction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It does not matter," Smaug answered with a flat voice, taking out a smaller crystal this time. "Sometimes we're just leaves drifting in the wind."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The crystal released a shockwave before a blue fractal appeared in the sky above him. Zac wouldn't have been alarmed if that was all it did, but he looked on in trepidation as another fractal hundreds of meters across also appeared in the air above the lake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong winds that had no place in the Underworld buffeted the whole cave as waves rose over ten meters in the air from the disturbance caused by the huge fractal. Zac was even having some trouble keeping his footing from the torrential winds, and he finally punched the shield into the ground to get a proper footing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac was unsure what to do as five enormous streams rose from the lake, causing dozens of fishing vessels to capsize. The streams melded together into an enormous leviathan that reached the ceiling of the cave before falling toward him. He wasn't sure if Verana could handle an attack of this magnitude, but she gave a signal that they were fine when he looked back at them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others had moved far away from the battle, and a sturdy-looking red barrier shone around them. It gave Zac some confidence as he turned back to face the incoming attack of the array. His muscles swelled to almost ridiculous proportions as he empowered his arms with &lt;strong&gt;[Unholy Strike]&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last moment before the humongous water creature slammed into the ground he infused his shield with the Dao of Heaviness and Swung it forward with a punching motion. Between his massive pool of Strength and the multiplicative boost of &lt;strong&gt;[Unholy Strike],&lt;/strong&gt; the shield contained terrifying force and the moment it hit the water creature they both froze for a fraction of a second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next moment a massive shockwave exploded from the point of impact, shooting water and hurricane-like gusts across half the cave. The massive energies ripped the whole complex of Dragonwing Enterprises to pieces, and quite a few of the surrounding structures were toppled even though they were made from stone and metal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One small relief was that he got no streams of energy from any kills, meaning that people in the vicinity had managed to evacuate in time before the battle reached a crescendo. It had been a worry in the back of his head since the battle started. He didn't want any innocent bystanders to lose their lives due to Smaug's crazed assault. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac's whole body hurt from being right next to the impact, but he ignored the pain as he looked around with wild eyes. He was tired of all the nasty things Smaug seemed to have up in his sleeves, and he wanted to end this now. He quickly spotted a bedraggled Smaug currently scrambling to his feet, his clothes ripped and in disarray. He hadn't been unscathed from the shockwave either, and blood was running down his forehead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The true appearance of the wealthiest man of the Underworld was finally exposed, and it was not what Zac expected. He was a young man that might be from India or the Middle East, with a pair of emerald green eyes. He had olive-colored skin and short black hair, and pretty fine features. Zac would guess he was around 20 if he went by the standards of the Old world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smaug's eyes widened in alarm when he noted Zac's glare, and he quickly took out a heavily inscribed rapier as Zac barreled toward him like an angry bull. The rapier slightly reminded Zac of the terrible array that Hannah stabbed him with once upon a time, and rage flared up in his heart when remembering the betrayal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac pushed his speed to his limit as he swung &lt;strong&gt;[Hunger] &lt;/strong&gt;with ferocious force straight at Smaug himself. The man desperately tried to defend with his weapon, but a snap could be heard as soon as the two weapons collided. It was Smaug's wrist not being able to withstand the power in Zac's swings, immediately shattering from the force.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smaug wailed in pain, but the scream was quickly cut short as Zac's boot slammed into his chest with the force of a truck, launching him like a ragdoll into the ruins of what might once have been an office building. Zac was right behind him and before he could get up Smaug found &lt;strong&gt;[Hunger]&lt;/strong&gt; against his throat, the sword actually shivering with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac's boot was firmly pressed on the man's chest, and his shield was slammed into the ground right next to Smaug's head. His eyes were red and he breathed heavily even though there was no need for it in his current body. Bloodlust had almost completely clouded his mind when he saw the rapier, but he finally managed to calm down before he killed his captive in a fit of rage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why?" was all Zac said through grit teeth as he looked down at the man who had attacked them with a storm of treasures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man didn't answer, instead looking back and forth to the sides with some panic. Zac frowned and looked around, but they were in the middle of a pile of rubble and sight was obscured in every direction. A thought struck Zac and he took out one of the mobile array disks with his free hand and threw it down on the ground next to them. It quickly shuddered before a small shield encapsulated the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This area has been obscured by an array," Zac said with a frosty voice, his foot still on Smaug's chest. "Now tell me what the fuck is going on or I'll skewer you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please, save my sister," Smaug coughed out with a pitiful voice, his demeanor completely changed. "I was forced to attack you by those bastards of the Union. Why the hell would I want to attack monsters like you people, only to drag your boss here on the off-chance I survived?"&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">500015</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 17:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 326 - Subterranean Diplomacy</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/499522</link><description>&lt;p&gt;"He controls this town by himself? How is that possible? He is not even on the power Ladder," Mr. Trang said with some suspicion after hearing the inscriber's proclamation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wealth trumps over power," the inscriber said. "Anyone who tries to cause trouble will get blasted by his various treasures or arrays. I doubt even the Super Brother-Man would dare to cause a ruckus in the Underworld Nexus."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac slowly nodded, remembering Ogras' words. With enough wealth it was possible to completely ensconce yourself within your sphere of influence, buying layers after layers of defensive and offensive structures. Of course, while it was entirely possible to smash your enemies with piles of money it was also true that wealth couldn't trump over supreme power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So he's not part of any force?" Mr. Trang asked curiously. "Seems like he would be better off joining this Union."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He has his own company, Dragonwing Enterprises, and many underlings here in the city. I work for Dragonwing Enterprises for example," the inscriber explained drawing a glare from the guard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They only recruit locally though," the Ishiate hurriedly added. "So how about it? Shall we head to the Union? Or if fighting is more your style, I actually have some friends working for the Council as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac didn't immediately answer but instead went over what they had learned. He knew they might only have scratched the surface, but it still felt like they had a good enough understanding of the underworld to get to work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The splintered forces had generally clumped together into larger groups, but it seemed there were no individuals strong enough to become sole leaders. Instead, councils were formed where power was shared. The only exception was this Smaug character who seemed solely to control this town by virtue of wealth rather than strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that they knew who the players were and what kind of place they had arrived at there was no longer any need for subterfuge. Zac never meant for them to keep their anonymity forever, as there was no point in doing so. They needed to speak with Smaug, and the quickest way to do this was to explain who they were. Mr. Trang seemed to be of the same idea, as he shot a glance at Zac who made a small signal with his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am afraid that we do not plan to join any force," Mr. Trang said with a smile at the Ishiate, before turning toward the inscriber. "We would like to meet your boss."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the ishiate and the inscriber looked a bit startled at the quick change in demeanor before the beastman let out a guffaw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you crazy? Do you think just anyone can just walk in here and act as they please?" the guard laughed derisively. "I am being nice enough to help you out, but you better smarten up before something bad happens."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the inscriber's eyes thinned as he glanced at Zac's party, and he seemed to take the situation seriously even though all of their auras were completely restrained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who are you?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We come from the surface, and we represent the Super Brother-Man," Mr. Trang said, hiding nothing. "The forces of the surface world all tried to reach this place the moment the hunt ended, but currently it is only the Super Brother-Man who possess the capabilities needed to reach this place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, the Super Brother-Man, is it?" the Ishiate laughed even harder. "I forgot to introduce myself, I am Starlight's long-lost brother, and this inscriber here is the cousin of Thea Marshall."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's enough Terre-" the inscriber said, but his words got caught in his throat as an aura as heavy as a mountain spread out, suffused with killing intent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The whole cavernous room started shaking and the two men both were unable to move. The Ishiate had fallen down on his belly and was crawling toward the door with horror in his eyes. The inscriber was not much better off as he had fallen back into the pile of empty tokens, his face white as a sheet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wasn't Zac, but rather the snake who peeked out of Verana's sleeve that was emitting the dense aura, proving that it was another E-Grade beast under her command. In fact, the aura it emitted was even stronger than those of Grub and Lulu, making Zac wonder if Verana held back during their fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Super Brother-Man has closed multiple incursions in the past week, but there is far more to do. He sent his right-hand man and a general to close the incursions down here, and help the people stuck here," Joanna explained when the snake finally crawled back inside Verana's sleeve and restrained its aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you… truly from the surface?" the inscriber said, clearly starting to believe their words. "Then why have only you arrived and no one else? We have waited for so long for assistance. And do you have any proof you're with the Super Brother-Man?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is simple. Most of the people on the surface believe that our new world consists of one huge continent, but that isn't true. There is, in fact, a second continent, but it is separated by a vast ocean. The Super Brother-Man is the only one with a fleet powerful enough to cross the ocean and survive the leviathans of the sea," Sap Trang explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shortly after we set up our outpost we noticed this place appearing now and then on the teleportation panel," Joanna added. "And as for proof? The force of the Super-Brother-man is Port Atwood, which you should know after the hunt."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next moment both her alignment from her status screen appeared, and her current position on the ladder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Atwood Valkyrie… a ranker!" the inscriber said with shock. "Are you his right-hand man? Or General?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, I am not strong enough for that yet," Joanna said, looking a bit pained before gesturing at Zac and Verana. "It's those two."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The implication was clear, and the inscriber immediately understood what she was getting at. Not even low rankers were strong enough to become generals under the Super Brother-Man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, can you take us to Smaug now?" Mr. Trang asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well… It's not that simple," the inscriber said with a grimace before turning to the Ishiate who was still on the ground. "Terrek, you can leave. I will take it from here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ishiate had been frozen by the door, both afraid to speak up and leave. When he heard the inscriber's words it was as though he was granted a pardon, and after giving Zac's party a deep bow he scrambled out of the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why can't we meet him?" Joanna pressured, her eyes thinning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't know where he is. No one does," the inscriber hurriedly explained. "We don't know what Smaug looks like or where he lives. He's only communicating through the network he has set up here, and the few times he appeared he has been disguised."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So what now?" Joanna asked with some displeasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can take your party to the headquarters of Dragonwing Enterprises. I am only middle management so I can't contact the Lord, but someone there should be able to," the appraiser said and got up from his seat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group nodded since it seemed as good a plan as any. They might have been able to force the man out by wreaking havoc on the town, but they had come to help people, not cause trouble. The appraiser, who introduced himself as Farid, led them out of the passageways into the town proper. A few scared faces peeked out through doors along the way, but hurriedly shied away when they passed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Underworld Nexus was completely different from what Zac had expected. It was still a cave, but it was just massive, likely even larger than Port Atwood. It was at least 100 meters to the roof, helping quite a bit with the claustrophobic feeling. There was even some wind getting generated by a massive waterfall that fell into a lake where Zac clearly could spot a large number of fishing vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The structures were simple but sturdy, mainly created from a mix of metal and stone. Many rooms didn't have roofs or walls though, instead opting for open architecture. Perhaps people felt enough closed-in as it was, and didn't want to box themselves in even further. Besides, it was not like there was going to be any bad weather down here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The oddest thing was that the whole thing was brightly lit up as though it was the middle of the day on the surface. The whole cave was illuminated by a couple of massive crystals placed on top of sturdy metal towers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We call them Day Crystals, and use them instead of sunlight," Farid explained when he saw the group's looks. "Smaug owns a mine where they extract them. These crystals are lit up 18 hours a day, with the first and last hour being at half power. We also sell smaller versions to add to your home because electricity is limited."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded, quite impressed by how quickly these people had adapted to life underground. But even with these pretty optimal conditions for a subterranean town, it was impossible to forget they were stuck under miles of rock. The town sharply ended where it reached the wall, and a few barricaded gates led out into the wild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As they walked it seemed to become more apparent that the explanation of the guard wasn't completely accurate. It was true that the Union and the Underworld Council were the two most powerful forces along with Hive Arbak, the strongest Zhix hive in the underworld. In truth, their numbers only made up around 10 to 15% of the people in the Underworld Nexus rather than the 60%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But their influence reached far and wide in the underworld, and it was obvious by how they could so overtly bribe the Underground Nexus guards to do their bidding. As Zac suspected guard did get a commission for enlisting new towns into these forces, which was why he made them sound grander than they truly were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Farid explained how there was a large number of varying forces and independent warlords who controlled their respective sectors, making the underworld almost as chaotic as the surface. The towns were far more integrated between species though, mainly since the surface species were dropped off together at the same place when the randomization of the planet took place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there was also a large number of refugees as the things Zac heard about the fire incursion was all too real. Every day more refugees streamed through the teleporter, and by now there was no more room to house them in the Underworld Nexus. Luckily there was no lack of crystals, meaning the refugees could be teleported away to reinforce other towns in the underworld network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So why has no one of you come to the surface?" Joanna asked as they walked toward the Dragonwing headquarters. "You've had half a year to dig your way out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We tried," Farid said with a sigh. "We all tried the first months. But something is odd with the stone, most of it is incredibly hard. Unless you're at least level 30 you can forget about even cutting out a chip from the walls, and even the stronger people have trouble making way. Not even the Geomancers are any good. Perhaps when people start reaching E-rank they will be strong enough."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just like there are mines with minerals and Crystals there are also mines with softer stone that can be extracted," the inscriber explained. "Most settlements are made by the molemen though. The Underworld Nexus is almost unique in the fact that it is completely made from scratch. The cave was found by Lord Smaug, and he founded the Nexus by the shore."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group soon enough reached the Dragonwing Headquarters, a vast complex next to the lake. As they passed through the gate Zac couldn't help but notice there were multiple layers of arrays around the building. He wasn't worried now that they had already been let through, but if he read the energy fluctuations right he guessed that even he would have trouble cracking this place open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After Farid explained their identities and the snake once again exhibited it's might things proceeded quite quickly from there. The group was led to an open-air conference room while the manager sent an emergency transmission to their boss. The manager kept them company as they waited, ensuring that Smaug never took longer than 20 minutes to respond to a message.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minutes passed and refreshments were brought in as they waited. The manager was extremely curious about the state of the surface and was elated when he heard that the Super Brother-Man was going around closing one incursion after another. The fact that he had started eyeing the underworld wasn't met with suspicion at all by the stocky middle-aged man, but rather delight. The fire golems had truly pushed people to their limits, and it looked like there wasn't a single person who hadn't lost someone to their attacks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Zac suddenly got a bad feeling as a gust made his black cloak flutter. He immediately looked around and spotted an odd sphere beneath the table that he knew wasn't there before. It didn't emit any energy, but the feeling only got worse by the second, and Zac knew he could tarry any longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Behind me!" he growled as a field of death expanded around him from &lt;strong&gt;[Fields of Despair]&lt;/strong&gt;, while his defensive layers were erected one by one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large fractal shield was the last to materialize, and Zac placed it square between the rapidly enlarging ball and the group. The manager was held by his neck by a furious Joanna, but he was clearly not part of what was happening since he was screaming in fear, looking completely shocked by the change in atmosphere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suddenly it sounded like a piece of glass cracking, and then the world turned white.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">499522</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 16:14:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defiance of the Fall - Chapter 325 - Underworld Nexus</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/499006</link><description>&lt;p&gt;"Who's going first through the teleporter?" Mr. Trang suddenly asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac was about to say that he would enter first, but he suddenly froze when he saw the old man imperceptibly glance at the new addition to Port Atwood's forces. Only at that point did he realize the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he went first Verana would become the strongest person above-ground, and she could easily destroy the teleporter, effectively trapping Zac in the underworld. He didn't know what she would gain from doing something like that, but he also wasn't willing to take the risk with so many things riding on him. This place was the only link to the surface, and if it was that easy to reach it by foot the people of the underworld would already have left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Verana, Joanna, Mr. Trang, and I will all go down together. When the situation is secured Joanna will return to get the rest," Zac said, quickly adjusting his plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verana looked a bit surprised at being included in the advance group, but a small smile suddenly crept up on her face and she simply nodded in agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I want to go as well," Emily said as she burst through the door, clearly having eavesdropped on them. "You promised."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"… No, you'll join the second group," Zac finally rejected after some hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things might get a bit crazy when they arrived unprompted, especially when they brought an alien, so bringing Emily in the earliest group was without benefit. He was also worried she would act hastily when she got down there, so he wanted to stabilize the situation first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My goal is to make whoever is on the other side open the teleporter within an hour to let the rest of you through," Zac then added when he saw Emily's face scrunch up. "If that doesn't happen something might have gone wrong. But don't enter the teleporter before Joanna has come out even if it opens again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others quickly nodded in agreement before they ironed out the finer details of the expedition. The name of the teleportation destination was Underworld Nexus, and it hinted at what sort of place they were heading into. Since the teleporter opened to the public every day there should be some strong people holding down the fort, and there might also be quite some foot traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it was possible they would avoid causing any commotion since it might be more convenient to get a better understanding of the underground if their true identities weren't exposed yet. The fact that Verana would join them would make that a bit harder, but she said she possessed a treasure that would allow her to accompany them without her origins getting exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was also the risk that the place was like the Cradle of God, a death trap that tried to swallow everyone foolish enough to enter, which was another reason why Zac was hesitant to bring Emily. Better the small group of elites go first and sound out the situation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, there was only so much that could be done when they had no idea what they dealt with, so soon enough everyone retreated to their respective groups to sit down and meditate while waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac briefly pondered on the Dao of Rot until one of Mr. Trang's men let him know that the teleporter was open on the other side. Zac only grunted in affirmation as he got to his feet, and was soon joined by the other three who would go with him as the advance group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac was interested to note that Lulu and Grub were nowhere to be seen, replaced with a rocklike snake that circled her left arm like a bracer. The Beast Master noticed Zac's look and smiled as she scratched the head of the snake, eliciting an odd purring sound.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is Slither," she introduced. "Lulu and Grub might be out of their element in the underworld considering their size. Slither is much more accustomed to subterranean fighting and scouting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac nodded in understanding, feeling that Beast Master was a pretty convenient class. One could simply shore up any weakness by capturing another beast, and you stayed out of harm's way while your beasts battled for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then again, Zac knew things weren't that simple. It took both time and a large number of resources to rear a battle beast. And just capturing it was not enough since if there was no connection it might refuse to fight for you, or even betray you at a critical juncture. Zac didn't like the concept of relying on others for keeping himself safe. He would rather depend on his own to fists for protection than some familiar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time was of the essence so the small group immediately headed over to the Teleportation array. Zac still donned his mask, making him look like a human hiding his identity. Verana instead wrapped a white cowl to obscure her features, and it completely hid her non-human features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More interestingly the cowl seemed to possess some magical feature that made Verana less conspicuous, and Zac had a hard time focusing on her even though he knew about it. It was as though he got distracted by stray thoughts any time he looked in her direction, and soon his eyes drifted away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How curious," Mr. Trang muttered with some interest, clearly having realized the magical feature of the cowl as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since it looked like Verana wouldn't be a problem Zac immediately activated the array, and in short order all four had stepped through and disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a brief stint in the darkness, the foursome found themselves in a large vaulted cavern teeming with people. They stood on a platform that was raised around a meter into the air, and as he looked over the sea of people he noted that most were streaming toward two large exits on the opposite side of the cave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cave itself didn't feel as stuffy as Zac had feared, and the ceiling reached almost twenty meters in the air. The area was also pretty well lit by a combination of large inlaid crystals in the walls and the ever-present glowing moss. The air was a bit stale though, and the lack of any natural light was a bit uncomfortable. But Zac easily adjusted his state of mind, since he had been in a similar place for weeks during the hunt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A quick estimation would put the number in the cave above a thousand, and he noted that this place was far more integrated between the races than how it was on the surface. Humans made up almost half of the people in the cave, which wasn't surprising considering how populous the old Earth was compared to the other planets that got smashed together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there were representatives from all three of the other races in the streams of pedestrians, and many groups consisted of a mix of human, Ishiate and the Ratmen. Even a handful of Zhix walked along without causing any trouble, though it looked that the Zhix always only walked with their own kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; "Hey, stop dawdling! Present your tokens and make way for the next group," a gruff voice said, making Zac look over at a guard who glared at them from beneath the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac realized that over twenty guards were standing there, and apart from three who inspected a group in front of them they all looked in their direction. The one who had spoken to them was a muscular Ishiate, but all four races apart from the Zhix were represented among the guards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could also breathe out in relief when he realized that neither his nor Verana's hidden features had caused any alarm amongst the guards. Actually, quite a few of the people in the area had obscured their features to varying degrees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end Sap Trang stepped forward after shooting a brief glance at Zac and Verana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We do not possess any tokens," he explained with a smile. "It is our first time coming here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You cannot enter the Underworld Nexus without a token," the beastman said with a shake of his head. "Are you members of the Union or the Council?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Union? Council? We are not part of either," Sap Trang said with some confusion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fresh meat?" the Ishiate interrupted with some surprise. "You're the first in a while, must be from a pretty secluded sector. Come with me and I'll explain things."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man seemed pretty eager, and Zac noted that the other guards looked at the beastman who had spoken up with some envy as he ushered them away from the teleportation platform. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He wasn't worried that this place was a trap since the people who were continuously streaming out of the teleporter seemed aware of the rules of this place, and they hurriedly presented the same sort of token upon arrival. At the same time, there was a smaller stream of people leaving as well, walking against the stream to use another teleportation array to return to wherever they came from.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Underworld Nexus is a neutral town meant as a gathering place for all the native factions of the underworld. Most of those you see coming and going either belong to the Union or the Underworld Council. The Union is led by a group of merchants," the guard started explaining as they entered the side passage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A notable name among you humans from the Union is Little Treasure, who is one of the eight top figures. The union control most of the high-grade mines and many other lucrative resources, so they are extremely wealthy. That's why many elite cultivators have joined them to enjoy great benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Council is a group of extremely strong warriors. They are on the frontline in the fight against the incursions, but they also control a lot of the best training grounds. They aren't as wealthy as the Union, but they make up for it with military might."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Incursions? What does that mean?" Zac asked, thankful his voice didn't change too much in his Draugr form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac, of course, knew what the beastman was talking about. But from how he explained it, it sounded like there was more than one incursion in the underworld.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are truly lucky if you haven't been impacted by those alien cultivators in all this time," the Ishiate guard muttered as he led the group to a guarded side-exit of the cave. "When the Integration took place it also opened portals to other worlds, and foreign invaders have come through those gates. The main goal of the Council is to close those gates, and the Union is generally helping the war effort with resources."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How many gates are there?" Mr. Trang asked, understanding what Zac wanted to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are four that we know off, and the worst of them are the fire golems. They have killed millions of people," the Ishiate sighed. "I moved here after they flooded my hometown with lava. Only a fraction of us survived, our ancestral halls turned to cinders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zac was truthfully not too surprised that there were multiple incursions. The Underworld spanned a huge area, and hundreds of millions of humans had been teleported here. In fact, he felt it was pretty good news to hear there was more than one. If the system only sent one incursion to test the whole underworld it would likely have meant that particular incursion was terrifyingly strong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So where are we headed?" Sap Trang finally asked after they had walked the empty passage for some time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to issue tokens if you wish to enter this place. Please beware, these tokens are not free as they require inscriptions to work. Each one costs 50 000 Nexus Coins," the guard explained until he finally stopped in front of a door. "In here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group entered and saw a human sit with an engraving kit in his hands, with a small mountain of tokens behind him. The process of acquiring tokens was pretty simple, with only a drop of blood being needed to bind the Token while the inscriber activated it. But Zac suspected the tokens contained a tracking array just like the one in Westfort. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you want my advice you should quickly join one of the forces as quickly as possible. There is some semblance of order in the Nexus, but truthfully it is quite dangerous for a small unaffiliated group to walk the streets. You might get robbed of your treasures, or even killed," the guard suddenly said as they got their tokens. "As luck would have it I know a few people in the Union, and I could introduce you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are the two forces the only ones around?" Mr. Trang asked, sidestepping the offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The guard looked a bit irritated at getting his pitch derailed, but he quickly controlled his mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well, there are some smaller groups and towns that are not directly affiliated with the Union or the Underworld Council, but at least 60% of those who walk the streets here are part of either of them. So what do you say, do you want to head over to my friends in the union? It's a pretty rare opportunity, and I wouldn't offer if I hadn't felt that you guys are pretty strong," the Ishiate explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some disdain flashed in the eyes of the inscriber as he worked on the final token, but it quickly disappeared a moment later as the man refocused on his work. But both Zac and Verana had noted it, and they threw each other a look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed to Zac that the great opportunity was nothing more than a scam. Perhaps joining the Union would mean something like joining the New World Government, getting an overlord taking control of your hometown. It was most likely not very hard to join on one's own, and the guard in front of them perhaps even got a commission for leading new blood to the slaughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is it the Council or the Union that controls this place?" Zac suddenly asked, as he never heard the guard mention it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Actually, neither," the Ishiate said as he scratched his chin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this time the inscriber spoke up for the first time, briefly shooting Zac a glance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This place is under the control of the richest man in the underworld, Lord Smaug himself."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">499006</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 15:51:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/syndication/24709</link><description>Latest updates of (Defiance of the Fall)</description></rss>