<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Scribble Hub</title><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 70: Forging Bonds</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/115568/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As soon as the barrier Aperio had previously created had fully dissipated, Caethya stepped closer, the concern clear on her face. "Is everything alright?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before she could continue, Laelia took a step forward and spoke. "We could feel your anger; your grief. It was not as pronounced as before, but your emotions are still quite strong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;That's my theme, is it not? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio thought.&lt;em&gt; Too much strength. &lt;/em&gt;That her emotions still affected the ones she had blessed was not to her liking but, nonetheless, she had expected it. &lt;em&gt;It isn't as though realizing where the emotions come from would have changed much. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I apologise,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, the vile taste in her mouth an annoying reminder at her own inadequacy. "&lt;em&gt;The discussion we had was required, however.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya looked at Aperio for a moment longer before she cast her gaze down. "I just hope you share more of yourself in the future."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mother is not the most sociable of people," Ferio said, taking the surprisingly heavy burden of an answer off Aperio's shoulders. "You will need to give her some time. It's not like either of you will have a shortage of that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia's eyebrows scrunched as Ferio's words washed over her. "What do you mean?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Your age. Time's clock no longer holds as strong a sway over you.&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; that the mana she had given was more than enough to keep their bodies going for as long as they needed. They were functionally immortal, if they didn't do anything foolhardy to get themselves killed by other causes. &lt;em&gt;And if they manage to ascend, they wouldn't age anymore either.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As neither of the two replied, Ferio took a step towards them. "Don't worry, you'll get used to it. Besides, both of you would have lived a lot longer than normal, even without mother's blessing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I don't think &lt;/em&gt;I&lt;em&gt; have gotten used to the idea of living forever yet. &lt;/em&gt;Aperio doubted her two followers would easily accept the reality either. &lt;em&gt;Though, do normal people even think about death as much as I did? &lt;/em&gt;She had once spent a good part of her days simply trying to come up with ways to end her life, always knowing just how fragile she was but never quite able to actually end it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She somehow doubted that that was normal behaviour. Most mortals seemingly believed they were immortal anyway, something she had seen a few times in the dungeon below. They went into impossible fights thinking that they would win, and then struggled until she killed the monster for them. &lt;em&gt;Why would they do that? They can't possibly be that foolhardy. Do they, perhaps, have no other choice?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio couldn't claim to know how life worked in the city. She did not know how much it would cost for a mortal to stay alive and healthy, not having needed to know such things in either of her lives. "&lt;em&gt;If you want to talk, I will gladly listen,&lt;/em&gt;" the winged Goddess said as the pair continued their silence. "&lt;em&gt;Though I might not be the best to ask about such things.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Perhaps I should try talking to Mayeia? She was once a mortal.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, she could also go and ask Natio — he was in the same building after all — but Aperio felt no need to ask for advice from someone who had not only tried to kill her but also insulted her while doing so. She was also fairly certain that the fallen God would not speak to her on his own accord, and to force the conversation would most likely result in him saying what he thought she wanted to hear, and not any actual truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, you wouldn't be a good source for any of this," Ferio agreed. "But neither would I."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite having said it herself, Aperio still felt a bit of anger at her daughter's words. It was easily dismissed, of course, but its continued appearance only annoyed her. &lt;em&gt;Just focus on something else. &lt;/em&gt;Luckily for her, that was an easy task. All she had to do was to remind herself that she could hear everything that happened in the city at once which, while distracting, was probably not the best thing to allow her to regain a sense of calm. &lt;em&gt;I will learn how to deal with this someday.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could simply live in ignorance, but that would only work if she somehow never focused on the act of hearing. &lt;em&gt;How can I even ignore all of this? &lt;/em&gt;she thought as her ears twitched a little at a particular grinding sound. Someone, somewhere, had not taken proper care of their equipment. It wasn't like the sound hurt her, but it was still uncomfortable to listen to. That the people around her now had even less privacy than before just added to the discomfort that spread through her. &lt;em&gt;I understand why I did not like cities before.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think we can manage on our own," Laelia said, glancing at Caethya who nodded her consent shortly afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A small smile briefly settled on Aperio's face at the words. Even if it was only a small matter, she liked that her two followers chose to deal with the situation themselves and not depend on her aid. &lt;em&gt;Even if I would enjoy helping them. &lt;/em&gt;In fact, upon further reflection she was not quite sure which way she would prefer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the one hand, she wanted to be useful in a way; show that she could do things besides break reality wherever she went. On the other, however, she wished for the people to not depend on the Gods, and specifically on her. Once the masses figured out who and what she was, Aperio had no doubts that they would seek her favour in order to use her might for their own goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her brows furrowed ever so slightly at the thought. &lt;em&gt;What should I do when random people start seeking me out? &lt;/em&gt;The best choice was probably to ignore them, but she also had little doubts that some would simply claim to do things under her guidance; no matter how silly their claimed notion might be. What she would do with those she knew already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Still, should you wish to talk, I am willing to listen. And, should I not be able to, find someone that can help you if necessary,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied, directing her thoughts away from potential mortal troublemakers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That she only got hesitant nods in reply hurt Aperio, but should not have been unexpected. &lt;em&gt;I did just leave after becoming unreasonably angry, after all. &lt;/em&gt;It was still better than outright refusal or no answer at all. &lt;em&gt;Though, perhaps they only did so because they were scared?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a slight sigh, Aperio moved towards the door. "&lt;em&gt;I plan to visit Maria; you are free to accompany me.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just as she had expected, Ferio joined her immediately while Laelia and Caethya took a moment longer to follow her. Stepping out of the room required Aperio to duck slightly to avoid ramming her head into the wooden frame. Aside from the mild discomfort she might have potentially felt, she had little doubts that the wood would lose that encounter. &lt;em&gt;Ridiculous.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hallway outside was devoid of people, all of them scattered throughout the building; either in conversational groups, or occupied with taking care of those that could not do so themselves. Aperio had to note that those she had healed the first time she had come here were mostly gone, replaced more injured and sick. &lt;em&gt;Should I heal them too?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio did feel like she owed the people here something. She had left them with a rather large group of very confused people, after all. &lt;em&gt;And they take care of Laelia's children. &lt;/em&gt;A small flex of her mental muscles caused her aura to briefly flare, her mana quickly spreading into the sick and injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to what she could do now, her first attempt at healing a large group of people had been clumsy at best. Guiding her mana to aid in the healing of the bodies of the sick had become an easy task, something that required no more thought than breathing had before her sacrifice. The thought of having her aura simply heal everyone within its reach briefly crossed her mind, but was swiftly followed by the fact that, technically, her aura had no limit as it was comprised of the same threads that made up reality itself. &lt;em&gt;Probably not the best idea.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also did not want to solve everyone's problems simply because she could. As the people who actually ran this house of healing had previously helped her, and helped those she cared about, lending a hand to tend to the patients here was something Aperio felt no issues with. The same couldn't be said about the rest of all creation. Most of them would probably welcome her as a one-stop solution to their problems, but that was decidedly &lt;em&gt;not &lt;/em&gt;what she wanted to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Can't really hide myself either… Not without losing what I like, at least. &lt;/em&gt;She could let her wings disappear and stop drawing on her well, but she would still be someone that could, quite literally, talk someone into the ground. &lt;em&gt;Or break something by simply existing. &lt;/em&gt;She was still grateful that Ebenlowe made no use of wards. Whatever the [Guides] had set up was a much better solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before leaving, Aperio made a small detour, ducking into the room that appeared to be the home of Laelia's children. Brenia was the only one to approach, running at the winged Goddess as soon as she caught sight of her. Aperio caught the girl as she jumped into her arms, using a touch of her magic to properly slow her. While she did not know if Brenia would have injured herself with her action, Aperio had no desire to find out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The girl bombarded her with questions, the rapid babbling in a language Aperio did not know. "&lt;em&gt;She does not understand me, correct?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, gently stroking the girl's back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're right," Laelia replied with a small smile. "She does not speak anything besides Common. The new Common, I mean. But, can you understand her?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio shook her head lightly, and her ears twitched at a particularly high-pitched noise outside. She tilted her head away from Brenia, who was now reaching for her ears with interest. "&lt;em&gt;Don't.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was, perhaps, a bit of an overreaction, as the mortal child would be unable to hurt her in any meaningful way. But, Aperio did not want anyone touching her ears when she had only just gotten them back. She had no need for a reminder of the scarred mess that the Empire had given her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I cannot understand her, no,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said once Brenia had stopped trying to go for her ears, having settled on simply watching the pointed tips move ever so slightly whenever Aperio heard something loud or grating. "&lt;em&gt;I do not speak your new Common. Something I should, perhaps, fix sometime soon.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can teach you," Caethya exclaimed, the enthusiasm apparent in her voice before it faltered a little as she continued, "if you even require any help with that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Your help is appreciated,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, gently setting Brenia down. "&lt;em&gt;I would like to acquire a book on the language first, however. And it will also have to wait until after we have visited Maria, which brings me to something else I wanted to ask.&lt;/em&gt;" With those words she turned and settled her gaze on Laelia who, perhaps fearing a reprimand of some form, shrunk a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Maria has been isolated for most of her life,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio explained. "&lt;em&gt;I thought that, perhaps, she could meet with your children. If you are fine with that, of course.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't see a reason why not," Laelia replied after a moment, standing up straight again. "But, do you think her parents will agree to that? It sounds like there was a reason for her isolation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio watched Brenia wander over to her disciple, carefully tugging at her dress to get her attention. "&lt;em&gt;The reasons for her isolation are gone. I would also keep an eye on her, just in case someone seeks misguided retribution."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio paused briefly as she watched Caethya pick up the girl and tilt her head so Brenia might touch her ear, answering the question Brenia had asked at the same time. "&lt;em&gt;I think your daughter is fascinated with Elves.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What did you expect, mother?" Ferio asked. "You are the first one she has actually met, at least as far as I can tell. That had led her to believe that all Elves are of divine origin. Something your disciple has just told her is not the case."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Oh.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;There will be a group of supremacist Elves that think they are better because I look like them, won't there? &lt;/em&gt;She could only sigh at the thought. Even if she would not be the target of their hostilities, the last thing she desired was for another incarnation of the Inaru Empire to arise. It would be the opposite of what she &lt;em&gt;wanted &lt;/em&gt;to stand for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is also another thing, mother. Why don't you just bring all of us to the Terenyk estate? I doubt they would complain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter certainly had a point, but Aperio disliked the idea of popping in unannounced with a large entourage. &lt;em&gt;Then again, even if I were to be the only one showing up, it would still cause a stir. &lt;/em&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Perhaps you are correct.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With those words, and a small flex of her mental muscles, Aperio twisted reality apart and formed a portal that led to the Terenyk estate. "&lt;em&gt;Please, follow me.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for choosing Aperio Teleportation Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 69: Regret</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/115567/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio cautiously appeared above Ebenlowe, her wings holding her aloft. She did not want to appear in front of her daughter and succumb to the anger the same way she had before. No, first she had to actually know how the world affected her. &lt;em&gt;And after that, I have to apologise.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that she was back in the reach of the planet and its inhabitants, she could already feel the anger rising within her. Since she now knew that the emotion wasn't her own, she could tell that it had a distinct alien feeling to it. Looking at the countless network of mana threads that linked all of creation to herself, she could see the emotional qualities — which had been absent in space — interwoven within.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That she had not noticed them before was not something that surprised Aperio. Every thread only carried a minuscule amount of what she would identify as emotion through the subtle differences in the mana that reached her. Each thread alone would not be much of a problem, barely noticeable and definitely not able to influence her. But, with millions of them feeding her the collective anger of the people, it became a tide that dragged her along and threatened to drown her in seething rage. &lt;em&gt;How do I even know these bits are emotions?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer was likely that, since she had created all that there was, her body simply remembered what everything meant on a base level. It was just that her mind had to ask the right question first. &lt;em&gt;But, can I simply ignore this? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio was no longer angry like she had been before; the emotions she felt from the threads of reality were somehow distant, removed from the rest of her feelings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Only one way to find out, no? &lt;/em&gt;With those thoughts, Aperio vanished from the skies of Ebenlowe and appeared next to her daughter in the house of healing. For the briefest of moments the thought of using her teleport ability in a fight crossed her mind before she pushed it down and, instead, wrapped her wings around Ferio as she pulled her daughter into a hug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I'm sorry,&lt;/em&gt;" she whispered, gently stroking the back of Ferio's head. Aperio had seen how distraught her daughter had been, how she had been on the verge of tears. Something that was very much unbecoming of a Goddess, especially so in front of mortals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio did not say anything, simply holding onto her mother tightly. That Aperio could feel an ever-so-slight discomfort from her daughter's hug spoke volumes about how much strength the Goddess of Light and Life was putting into it. &lt;em&gt;And yet, I still have to be careful to not use too much. &lt;/em&gt;Her daughter's embrace had also strained Aperio's dress to the point of being pulled apart — nothing a little repairing wouldn't fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;It's okay,&lt;/em&gt;" she whispered as she felt tiny drops of wetness stain her shoulder. Aperio also spread more of her mana in the room, creating a small barrier that visually and physically separated Ferio and herself from others who were nearby. She enjoyed their company, and she still had to deliver an apology to them, but it felt wrong to let them freely witness Ferio in her current state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter mumbled something that Aperio did not understand as she gripped her mother a little tighter still. The All-Mother gently stroked her daughter's back as she asked herself how her actions could have resulted in this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had been angry, unreasonably so, but what Ferio displayed now was not only unbecoming of a Goddess but wildly out of proportion for what had transpired. &lt;em&gt;...Or was my previous self always so mercurial, and she fears that I will become so once more?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Very carefully, Aperio separated herself from her daughter, setting her down on a chair made from her mana. "&lt;em&gt;Did something happen after I left?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio inquired, no longer so sure that the reaction of her daughter was entirely her fault.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No," Ferio said with a shaking voice, wiping away a few remaining tears. "It's just too much. Trying to act all right and proper like you taught me to, only for you to still get angry and then disappear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I know this is not 'befitting of a Goddess' and surely not something someone my age should do," she said, "but I don't care anymore. I had hoped I would finally have a family, that you had changed. Then you disappeared again, dashing my hopes. But now you are back, hugging me in front of mortals. Trying to comfort me. I understand you now even less than I did before."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio cast her gaze towards the floor at her daughter's words; she was also confused with herself. Though she now knew the source of her anger, telling her daughter that the world itself was the reason felt like a cheap excuse. She could have done more to control herself. She was the All-Mother, older than everything – surely she should have mastered her own emotions by now? &lt;em&gt;Even as a slave I was able to control them better.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I do not understand myself either,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said as softly as she could. "&lt;em&gt;I do not know why I can feel the anger of the world, nor why it would influence me to such a degree. It is not an excuse for my actions — cannot be one – but you deserve to know the reason for my current state. I did not mean to cause you distress, Ferio. I care about you.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;More than I ever thought I would.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only thing in her mortal life that had come vaguely close to the notion of family had been Moria, but that paled in comparison to what she was feeling now. Even before she had retrieved the memories of Ferio's childhood she had &lt;em&gt;known &lt;/em&gt;the Goddess was her daughter, something she could not say about the other Gods or Goddesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio sighed at her mother's words. "This is what I mean. It's like you are flipping between the old you and some new you, but can't decide which one you truly are. I had hoped that, perhaps, I would have someone who cares now. Who doesn't expect the impossible from me simply because I am your daughter. I am not you; nor will I ever be."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I am not 'me' either. &lt;/em&gt;The thought was kept to herself, her daughter having already pointed out the occasional dissonance of her actions and words. "&lt;em&gt;I am doing my best,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said with a sigh, pointedly ignoring the disgust that was already making itself known. "&lt;em&gt;But I do not know how anything is supposed to work. I have to fight with myself to even say these words. The bits and pieces that I can recall are not of much help.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I understand that, but it still hurts when you get angry for no reason, when you don't let me help you. I am not the only one, either. Laelia and Caethya want to help you too. For different reasons, perhaps, but nonetheless they do care."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Did you tell them what had happened to me? Why I disappeared?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I did not, mother," Ferio said, lifting her gaze from the floor. "I wouldn't reveal that unless you were gone for years again. But, you have to understand that you aren't alone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio looked over her shoulder at the words, seeing Laelia and Caethya kneeling in front of the barrier she had erected; her magic only blocking sight from their direction. With only a little focus necessary on the bond they shared, she could sense their emotions. She knew that they both were worried. Not the cause, but only that they were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I am not good at being a Goddess, am I? &lt;/em&gt;While she had never wanted to be one, Aperio still felt that she should, at the very least, bring her followers surety and comfort in the world. Causing them to fret certainly didn't fall under either of those two categories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please mother," Ferio said, standing up from the chair Aperio had made. "I can't bear the thought of you disappearing for ages at a time, or the idea of you becoming your old, cold and distant self. I don't want to lose you again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio found that something in her daughter's statement didn't quite make sense. "If you don't want me to become who I was, why are you helping me to retrieve my memories?" Why, indeed, should her daughter help to retrieve what her mother had once been? Aperio doubted she would ever be the same as her old self, but the more she learned about her past, the less eager she became to track down the next piece of her history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Because it would be wrong to deny you the knowledge of who you were," Ferio said after a moment's hesitation. "And it wasn't like I hated you. I simply wished you would have continued to care like you had in the beginning. But, perhaps, the novelty of having a child simply wore off for you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio scrunched her brows at the words. &lt;em&gt;If you decide to have a child&lt;/em&gt;,&lt;em&gt; it's not something you can just discard when they annoy you. …Was I like my own mother? Did I, too, get bored of my child, and simply throw them away? &lt;/em&gt;She suppressed a shudder at the thought, turning her mind in a slightly different direction. There was also the question of whether her remembered mortal mother was actually her biological mother. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps I simply appeared in the world and she found me?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering what she was, Aperio somehow doubted that she had been a normal child. &lt;em&gt;But then, at the time I had no powers, or anything of the like. I was just a normal Elf. &lt;/em&gt;She shook her head, dismissing the thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I do not think of you as a novelty. You are my daughter, and I care for you more than I am able to show,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, stepping in front of Ferio. "&lt;em&gt;I am sorry for what I have done in the past; even if I cannot remember it. But, I am afraid that my best is currently not enough.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Admitting even my tiniest flaw fills me with disgust and I do not know why. Knowing your weaknesses should be the first step towards improvement, and yet I can seldom bring myself to say what I want aloud.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She blinked. What she just said had revealed to her a new level of wrongness she could not quite believe existed. Aperio sunk to the floor with a sigh, uncaring of how the wood broke below her. &lt;em&gt;Where are these feelings coming from?&lt;/em&gt; A glimmer of hope rose within her, and she began examining her connections with the world. No matter how hard she looked, she could not find a source for the fallacious feelings. Her heart sank further. &lt;em&gt;So it does come from me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hand brushed over Aperio's cheek, stopping her thoughts. Ferio, face full of what looked to be concern, had knelt down in front of her. "Just... let yourself be helped, mother," her daughter said. "I do not expect that you tell Laelia and Caethya everything, but you should at least let them know that you are not as perfect as they think."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being portrayed as anything less than perfect was not something she enjoyed, but as both of them had pointed out, her behaviour did not make sense. "&lt;em&gt;I will try.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your aura is feeling a lot more serene, now. You are already feeling better than before, are you not?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head as she directed her senses inward. She could not find a change; everything looked as it had before. The anger still flowed to her on the threads of reality, the mana in her body was still dutifully improving her physical self, and the wisps that danced around her shone in their usual faint bluish-silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She did, however, feel like some weight had been lifted off of her. &lt;em&gt;But all I did was go against my instincts. &lt;/em&gt;The same instincts that had, thus far, always been right about her abilities. &lt;em&gt;Not trusting those instincts did not last long, now did it?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio had been back in the world of the living for... well, she did not know how long it had been, exactly. &lt;em&gt;A few months, at least.&lt;/em&gt; But in that stretch of time, she had undergone more changes than in her entire life as a slave. &lt;em&gt;However long that life was.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had told herself that she would not trust instincts that weren't her own, and yet she had done so. In matters of physicality it had been the right choice most of the time, as her body seemed to know more about what it could do than she herself did. But when it came to matters of the mind, her old instincts had continually been nothing but a hindrance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I do feel better, yes,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said. "&lt;em&gt;But I do not think I am ready to tell Laelia and Caethya.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then wait a little while longer. Just, try to accept their help when they offer it. You might be able to solve it on your own, but having others lend a hand is not a bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please, promise me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I promise,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, her words accompanied by a slight pulse of her mana as she dismissed the barrier she had created. Her two followers rose to their feet as they saw the magic of their Goddess vanish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 68: The Formless</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/115564/</link><description>&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, before this chapter starts I have a few things to address. Namely the translations of this story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently found out that someone regularly visits this story from what looks to be the Chinese version of gdocs. Could be many things, but my mind wanders to translation. So I asked an acquaintance if such a thing exists — it does — but was unable to find my work posted in such places.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I did find, however, was a russian translation (Technically two, but one of them only did two chapters). Not only did they not ask if it was okay to translate this story — it would have been, but you lost that chance &lt;a href="https://tl.rulate.ru/users/73980" rel="nofollow"&gt;Nimura&lt;/a&gt;. — but they also appear to charge people for it. (Also, the image of the Elf you have on there is not close to Aperio's actual appearance.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some might think that, as I run a Patreon, such a statement is hypocritical. I disagree. Aside from the fact that I'm the one who actually comes up with the story, in the end everyone gets to read the main story at no cost but the time they invest. The money I do make is used to pay my editor and (finally) get art done. Though I might only post that on the discord, and potentially only for those from Patreon, considering that it might end up stolen and used to promote even more theft of my work if I do so here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the worst part is that I am not even against it. If it's translated more people can read it, perhaps some will even enjoy it. But, just taking a story and translating it without asking the author for their approval is still theft and annoys me in all the wrong ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, if you happen to be the one that for some reason comes to this story from docs.qq.com, please contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope your day is going better than mine. Enjoy the chapter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Two visits so shortly after millennia of silence," the ever-shifting cloud of shadows said. Its voices overlapped one another, never staying in the same cadence or pace. "Have I upset you, Mistress? Are you here to punish me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Punish?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio did not even know what the being really was, nor why it spoke to her now when it did not do so before. "&lt;em&gt;I came here to think; to clear my head.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The darkness seemed to be happy at her words, a few of the mana wisps that floated around Aperio's form disappearing as the shadows chased them. "Space is silent and uncaring; perfect to shield yourself from the annoying voices of the mortals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Annoying voices? &lt;/em&gt;She had to be honest with herself, she &lt;em&gt;had &lt;/em&gt;gotten fairly irritated with them. &lt;em&gt;Over nothing, too… Why was I angry when they cared about me?&lt;/em&gt; Upon further reflection, the rage that had previously bubbled inside her had mostly subsided, with only a small portion still remaining. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps space is more like my Void than I had previously thought?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She laid down on the nothing that surrounded her, the shadows that inhabited it gently embracing her, and closed her eyes, allowing her weapon to vanish. Breathing in &lt;em&gt;space&lt;/em&gt; was a weird sensation. No air filled her lungs, but neither did the motion bring comfort as it did in her Void. Somehow, there was even less… &lt;em&gt;nothing&lt;/em&gt; present here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another thing Aperio noticed was the calm she felt now; not quite on the level of her Void, but close enough. &lt;em&gt;So they are related. ...Or is it something else? &lt;/em&gt;She wasn't quite willing to believe that her Dominion and plain old space had much in common, but that meant something else had to have helped her regain her calm. &lt;em&gt;The shadow?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;What are you?&lt;/em&gt;" she asked, more to herself than anyone else. Aperio sat up straight as she realised she had been able to hear her own voice. &lt;em&gt;Does the shadow speak too, then? &lt;/em&gt;She had presumed it to be a mind-to-mind communication, just in a form she had not previously encountered. "&lt;em&gt;How?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You have never been bound by the same rules as the rest of us; why would you now?" the shadow asked, the chorus of voices laced with a few slight giggles. Then the timbre of the voice changed, and quiet sobs replaced the laughter. "But... You do not remember me, Mistress? I have dutifully kept watch over your creations, guiding the emergence of the new worlds, just like you had asked."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head, trying to remember something about the formless darkness in front of her despite already knowing it would not work. The winged Goddess was only able to retrieve a mild headache, just as she had expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I do not know who, or even what you are… I cannot remember much of anything,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, her last words a quiet murmur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could feel the darkness flow away from her, the ever-shifting cloud gaining more shape and substance until it had coalesced into a shadowy form of an Elf. Aperio looked at the reflection of herself, and was reminded of the other imitation of herself the dungeon had created before she destroyed it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of anger rising up at the sight of something that imitated her likeness caused no small amount of confusion. Aperio had long resigned herself to dealing with random bouts of anger, and was expecting to have to put up with it for an extended period of time. &lt;em&gt;Until I get my memories back, at least.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of such emotions now, however, caused her to shift her gaze to the planet below. She could sense how the shadowy Elf took a seat on the nothing next to her, seemingly wanting to comfort her. It did not answer the question she had asked, something that &lt;em&gt;did &lt;/em&gt;cause a good bit of angered irritation to stir inside Aperio, but the feeling was nothing compared to the seething rage she had felt at her followers' rather innocent questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Why?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio mumbled to herself. It made no sense to her. She &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;that her Void was one of a kind, that nothing could compare. &lt;em&gt;Does Verenier make me… angry? &lt;/em&gt;She doubted that the shadow was doing anything to calm her, as a quick glance revealed nothing traveling along the mana threads that connected them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But how does that work? &lt;/em&gt;It was obvious that the world reacted to her, and why wouldn't it? She had made it. &lt;em&gt;Do I... react to the world? But, it doesn't feel; it's a rock. Then again, I am an Elf with wings — the All-Mother — that &lt;/em&gt;can kill &lt;em&gt;Gods like it's nothing… Perhaps a feeling piece of rock is not that far-fetched?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;What is your name?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, not taking her eyes off the continent she knew to be Vetus. &lt;em&gt;So small. &lt;/em&gt;Knowing that she only needed to use a tiny fraction of her might to remove it from existence was a frightening, yet intoxicating experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Diskrye," the shadow replied, not a trace of the playful note in its voices left. "That is the name you have given me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hearing what the shadow was called had sadly not helped Aperio remember. &lt;em&gt;Not that it should have. &lt;/em&gt;How could she recall something that wasn't there? &lt;em&gt;But… something is there. &lt;/em&gt;She wasn't sure if it was the memories she had retrieved from the Ebenlowe dungeon slowly integrating themselves, or if she was somehow starting to remember things on her own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nor does it tell me if being on Verenier makes me angry. &lt;/em&gt;She could, of course, just go back down and see what happened, but as it stood, she had no desire to meet anyone. The only reason she had not asked Diskrye to leave her alone was because she &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;that it couldn't; it &lt;em&gt;was &lt;/em&gt;the space that surrounded her. It had taken her longer than she wanted to admit to realise it, but now that she did, it was obvious. &lt;em&gt;What else have I missed?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Had she been blinded by the anger she had felt? Could she even live on a world that did this to her? &lt;em&gt;Do all the worlds do that? ...&lt;/em&gt;Why&lt;em&gt; do they do that? &lt;/em&gt;She knew that, to an extent at least, the world reacted to how she felt. It had especially been reactive since...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio shuddered, pulling her wings in around herself at the memory. She had forced herself upon Laelia when she had healed her, irrevocably changing who — what — the woman was. It had been a needed action, yes, but as she now was painfully aware, she could have done it much differently. &lt;em&gt;Without forcing my way. Without going against all that I want to stand for.&lt;/em&gt; Remembering the scope of the impact she had on people was more difficult than she wanted to admit, and the lingering instincts of her mortal life as a slave did not help matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mistress?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The echoing voice of Diskrye brought Aperio out of her trance, causing her to turn her head and face the shadowy figure. The title it had chosen for her was questionable at best, but Aperio could not find a reason to change it aside from her dislike for its connotations. "&lt;em&gt;Yes?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you intend to stay here?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio did not reply immediately, instead shifting her gaze back to the world below. She didn't want to just leave everything behind and become some sort of space-faring hermit. She liked the people she had met and, perhaps most importantly, she wanted to spend more time with her daughter. &lt;em&gt;Though, after what I just did to them I should probably not expect the same level of goodwill they once had.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her reaction had by, all accounts, been irrational — almost hysterical, even. Definitely not something becoming of a Goddess, much less of the All-Mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;No,&lt;/em&gt;" she whispered, shifting her wings around herself to better hide from the world surrounding her. "&lt;em&gt;I like the people I met and I promised Maria I would visit her again… I just want a life.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is weird, seeing you like this, Mistress. What happened?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio wrapped her wings tighter around herself at the question, the soft warmth of her feathered appendages bringing her a comfort little else could. "&lt;em&gt;A lot.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could feel the shifting in space as the shadow drew some mana to itself. If it was for an attack, Aperio did not know, and neither did she care, for the amount Diskrye was summoning up was insignificant to the winged Goddess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bit of mana the presumed deity of space had sent against its maker faded before it even managed to touch its target. The only response the winged Goddess gave was the slight lowering of her wing to set her gaze on the shadowy being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diskrye dissolved a little under Aperio's stare, a gesture the winged Goddess assumed to mean embarrassment. "I did not mean to offend you. It is just that you are nothing like the Creator I remember.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She wouldn't cower like that, or willingly subject herself to the anger of a world. No, she would remove that world. Or simply go elsewhere. But despite all of this, you look like her, sound like her; &lt;em&gt;feel &lt;/em&gt;like her."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio narrowed her eyes at the shadow. "&lt;em&gt;People change.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diskrye slithered closer, the motion somehow easily recognisable despite the formless nature of the being. "They do," it said, the echoes in its voice more pronounced than before. "But you can hardly compare yourself to them, now can you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can feel the vastness of your being hidden inside that shell. I can see how you are constantly reinforcing it so it may one day be able to hold the true extent of your might. That is not something &lt;em&gt;people&lt;/em&gt; do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head, absentmindedly brushing her hand over the feathers of her wings as she pondered the words. It was, perhaps, meant as an insult, but she didn't think that it was, nor did she perceive it as such. There was a kernel of truth in it, after all. She was no longer a normal mortal, something Aperio thought she had already accepted and internalised. &lt;em&gt;Apparently not.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having it so bluntly pointed out to her that she was more than met the eye did drive the point home. That she could feel the anger of an entire world, and it could feel hers, was definitely something extraordinary; even for the other Gods and Goddesses. &lt;em&gt;It's like my aura, isn't it? Just, bigger.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If her aura caused pain because she had not accepted who she was on a personal level, why should the world — something that was still made from her mana — not react to her own less than complete self-acceptance. &lt;em&gt;Or is it because I killed Vigil and Inanis?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio's hand stopped brushing over her feathers as something clicked in her mind. &lt;em&gt;It's the mortals. &lt;/em&gt;It made much more sense than the world itself doing anything that she did not tell it to do. She &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;that her mood affected the people around her; had seen how her mana brought her feelings to the ones she had blessed. It only made sense that a small portion of the mortals' feelings would find their way back to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;And I'm connected to everything.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enough drops would cause even the largest barrel to overflow. &lt;em&gt;And I killed three deities, two of which had a very large following. &lt;/em&gt;The number of people stricken with grief or thrown into a rage surely numbered in the millions. &lt;em&gt;And it's not just Verenier.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If her daughter had followers on other worlds, Vigil and Inanis would have had some too. &lt;em&gt;What have I done? &lt;/em&gt;She hadn't stopped to think before she executed the two of them; the memory she had reclaimed underlined their betrayal with inescapable truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A defeated sigh escaped Aperio's lips as she stood up to her full height, the tiny wisps that floated around her glowing slightly brighter as she drew a bit more mana from her well. &lt;em&gt;That really became second nature fast, didn't it?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had not directly thought about drawing more from her well, having simply sighed and taken a breath of the nothing. &lt;em&gt;Now, how do I calm millions of mortals that lost their God or Goddess? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio asked herself, ignoring that Diskrye had started to play with her mana wisps again. &lt;em&gt;Reveal myself as the one true Goddess? No, that would be stupid. Once they figured things out, it would direct their anger more squarely at me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why can't I feel their emotions up here? Mana doesn't care if it is in space or not. &lt;/em&gt;So many things did not make sense to her, things that seemed like contradictions to how she perceived the world to work. Aperio started to pace back and forth, her feet somehow finding purchase on the nothing of space even without a conscious use of her magic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An inspection revealed nothing to her. The threads that connected Verenier to her were devoid of any emotion, just a steady stream of mana that informed her about the world itself. Aperio, however, had no use for the information it provided. &lt;em&gt;Why do I need to know how hot a specific spot is? &lt;/em&gt;The world gave off more information than anyone would ever need to know, but still somehow lacked the specific thing she was looking for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could not exactly cut herself off from the world and simply ignore what came from it. Nor did she want to force anything on the mortals below; they were not responsible for what their Gods did and had every right to be upset. Aperio was also still angry with herself for what she had done to Laelia, even if the woman herself did not seem to mind it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So, the best I can do is to just ignore it? &lt;/em&gt;She did not like the idea, for it came too close to taking away her freedom to do as she pleased. &lt;em&gt;But forcing the issue could make it worse… Perhaps Ferio could help? Or one of the others? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio did think that at least one of them would know about shielding themselves from outside influence. &lt;em&gt;But then, what they deal with is most likely very different.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only thing she could do to find out was go and ask them. The thought of doing that brought forth the feeling of disgust that had already become a companion to her. &lt;em&gt;A rather annoying one. At least it's getting better. &lt;/em&gt;She was no longer feeling like her nonexistent breakfast would leave her any time she wanted to ask a question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Thank you,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said to the formless shadow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The entity seemed cheery again, appearing to have forgotten their rather heavy talk from just moments ago. "I do hope you visit me again soon, Mistress. At least within the next century, yes?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A century is not soon by any stretch. &lt;/em&gt;While that might be true for most everyone, Aperio had to remind herself that she did spend a week floating in a bath of soul-water without even noticing the passage of time. &lt;em&gt;Do I just turn off? &lt;/em&gt;She had not done much at the time, simply concentrating on healing the mortals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a slight shake of her head, Aperio focused on the planet below her. It was an easy task to find her little group of friends, all of them still in the house of healing. They seemed to be consoling a very distraught-looking Ferio, her daughter seemingly unable to deal with what had transpired much better than Aperio herself. &lt;em&gt;I'm not a good mother, am I?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Farewell, Diskrye,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, offering a small wave at nothing in particular before she vanished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello? Yes, this is Space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 67: Piercing Truth</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/115554/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio noted with mild annoyance how everyone seemed to stand just a little bit straighter as she drew closer; as if they somehow expected her to perform an inspection. &lt;em&gt;Or is it because of the weapon? &lt;/em&gt;Holding it felt natural to her, making it easy to forget that she was currently grasping something out of the ordinary in the eyes of the mortals in front of her. &lt;em&gt;But then, Laelia also has a weapon I made and that doesn't seem to influence them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though, it had to be noted that the bow she had given her Scion lacked the blue lines that flowed along the haft of her swordstaff. It had been the same when Inanis had wielded it, as though the weapon itself was not wanting to be used by anyone but Aperio. &lt;em&gt;They only really work for me, don't they? &lt;/em&gt;Perhaps it would work for her Scion with enough time — the woman did carry a large amount of her mana, after all. &lt;em&gt;But is it really still my mana?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious answer was yes. Everything was technically hers, even if only in a very literal sense. She had made the universe, but Aperio wouldn't claim she was the creator of every piece of art or anything of the sort. To claim that the blessing given to Laelia still belonged to Aperio wasn't quite right either. Yes, she could control the mana she had given away, but that was true for every bit of magic that existed. &lt;em&gt;Probably.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if she could wrest control of the mana away from the one who had used it before, Aperio no longer considered it hers. She did not receive information from it like she did with her aura, and neither did it call to her to be used like the mana residing in her well. For all intents and purposes it was not hers, something she was more than fine with. &lt;em&gt;Not that I would ever need to draw mana from someone else. I have more than enough.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She pushed the thoughts away as she arrived in front of the small group, letting go of her weapon and returning it to the Void. "&lt;em&gt;Is there a reason everyone present is so… tense?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first to respond was Laelia who, after adjusting the bow slung across her shoulder, took a step forward. "You disappeared for a week, and answered neither Caethya's prayers nor my own. We were worried, my Goddess."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio turned her head to face Ferio at the words, sending her a mental query with perhaps a bit too much force. Laelia's choice of words had struck a chord of panic in Aperio's mind. &lt;em&gt;Did she tell them?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter was quick to deny Aperio's rather accusatory question, telling her mother that she had not revealed Aperio's history. The answer caused Aperio's wings to twitch in irritation. &lt;em&gt;If they are unaware of my previous disappearance, why, then, did they worry? Do they think I am weak?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As silly as the notion was, it still managed to cause a bit of anger to bubble up inside her. &lt;em&gt;I am not weak. &lt;/em&gt;Nor would she let anyone else think she was. She was no longer a helpless slave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The voice of her daughter echoed through her mind, urging her to remain calm. Without Ferio's prompting, Aperio would never have noticed how the wisps of mana floating around her had started to increase, or how tiny arcs of energy had started to jump between the feathers of her slightly flared wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio took a deep breath, the slightly sour smell of the city air not doing a great job of helping her maintain a grip on her sense of calm. They had been worried for her, not because she was weak and could not look out for herself, but because they cared. It was what she had wanted — that someone cared — and here she was completely ignoring that. She could blame it on the fact that nobody had cared before, but that felt like a cheap excuse; something she did not want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Thank you,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio finally said, her voice a lot softer than usual. "&lt;em&gt;But there was no reason to worry. Healing them merely took a bit of time.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hand of her daughter gently slipping past her wings and resting on her back caused Aperio to turn her head. Ferio's eyes were cast slightly downwards, the smile that usually graced her features somehow looking sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't always assume the worst, mother," Ferio said, her words barely audible. "You might not see it just yet, but there are people that care. About &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;, not just because you are the All-Mother and they want your favour."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia nodded at Ferio's words, the motion so subtle that Aperio barely noticed it. &lt;em&gt;She heard her? &lt;/em&gt;It shouldn't have been a surprise; with the power her Scion had, she should be able to hear a few more things than a regular mortal. &lt;em&gt;Probably could've done so before, too.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Perhaps,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied. Though what her daughter had said was likely true, she still had trouble fully accepting the idea of people caring about her person and not just wanting to use the favor of the All-Mother for their own gain. The only one she could fully trust at the moment was her daughter, which perhaps meant that Aperio should take the words to heart a little more. &lt;em&gt;But why should &lt;/em&gt;they &lt;em&gt;care?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you intend to do now, my Goddess?" Caethya asked, her gaze shifting rapidly between Aperio and the floor. &lt;em&gt;Did I scare her?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given that her disciple seemed to have shrugged off the way her Goddess had disappeared for a week, Aperio was led to believe that it was her small outburst that had scared the young Elf. The question Caethya had asked did cause Aperio to think, however. She had told Ferio about the things she wanted to do, but most of them had been grander goals that would take a while to accomplish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What Aperio wanted to do right this moment was something she was still unsure about. She wanted to visit Maria, but the continued silence of the girl was a sign to the Goddess that her youngest follower did not want to see her. &lt;em&gt;But what if something happened?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I wanted to visit Maria again,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied, having made up her mind. "&lt;em&gt;She is much like you, Caethya.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Like me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;She, too, had her soul touched by me,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya remained silent for a brief moment, her eyes fixed on her feet, before she spoke again. "Are there more?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winged Goddess lightly shook her head in reply. "&lt;em&gt;Laelia carries a different blessing. Maria and you are the only ones whose soul I personally touched.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"May I join you?" Caethya asked. "I would very much like to meet the other one you have blessed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Of course you are free to join,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, a smile settling on her lips — a reaction far outside of her usual composed demeanour. "&lt;em&gt;I would also like Laelia to join us. Introducing you three to one another is something I should have done sooner.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Not that I could have done so before...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was something her followers did not need to know, however. They could think of her as the somewhat mysterious All-Mother for a little while longer. That she had no idea what she was doing half the time was something she would not tell them until she actually &lt;em&gt;did &lt;/em&gt;know what she was doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shouldn't you address the world, my Goddess? Or, at least, this city?" Laelia asked. "You removed two of the most prominent Gods. The people still have questions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio remained silent for a moment, thinking of an answer. She had hoped that she would not have to address anyone, that her accidental week-long disappearance would have been long enough to allow people to forget, or at least move on. &lt;em&gt;That was a silly belief, wasn't it?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;And what do you expect me to tell them? That I killed their Gods for transgressions they would not understand?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio sighed and shook her head. "&lt;em&gt;I do not like taking an overly active role in the happenings of the worlds. I want to be left alone and not need to run after rebellious deities that think the rules do not apply to them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;So I think, unless it becomes absolutely necessary, that I will not address everyone. The people will figure out who it was that killed their Gods soon enough on their own, anyway.&lt;/em&gt;" Who she was and what she could do was not exactly a secret in the city, it was simply a matter of the people not yet choosing to believe that she could do what the rumours said she could.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia offered a hesitant nod in reply. "I understand… I think. You don't want to orchestrate a public crusade against the deities that… rebelled? I am not quite sure what they have done, just that you are supremely angry at their actions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio's eyes narrowed her Scion's words and she took a step closer, the stone cracking beneath her feet. "&lt;em&gt;Do you think what Vigil did to your soul was in any way acceptable?&lt;/em&gt;" Laelia blinked, startled, which brought further words to the Goddess' reprimand.&lt;em&gt; "Did you think he was alone in his actions? That he was the only one who could do it?"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After she received a rather hesitant shake of the head from Laelia, Aperio continued. "&lt;em&gt;He etched runes into your very soul. Servitude, Obedience and the like. I do &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;tolerate slavery in any form, and it would seem that some members of the pantheon need reminding.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;That said, I have no interest in involving legions of mortals. Only a few of you would be strong enough to be of use, and it is not your fight to begin with.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Nor do I know how I would even rally people to my cause… Or if I would want to do that in the first place.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio was fine with having a grand total of three followers. She did not need them to gain power, nor did she want their undying loyalty because they thought she would give them something if they prayed hard enough. &lt;em&gt;If I ever bless anyone again, it will be because I like them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was perhaps a luxury the other deities did not have, but Aperio truly had no need for a legion to fight her battles. &lt;em&gt;At least, I don't think so. &lt;/em&gt;The excitement that swelled within her at the idea of fighting an entire army on her own, the self-surety of the certain victory to follow, only furthered her belief. &lt;em&gt;And &lt;/em&gt;if &lt;em&gt;I ever did need help, I can ask Ferio, or Laelia and Caethya.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria was too young for a battle of any form, but her other two followers were stronger than most anyone she herself had seen. &lt;em&gt;Though, how can Laelia only be level 230 and feel more powerful than Caethya? ...Is the level part of the System also broken? &lt;/em&gt;Once the question had been so clearly formed in her mind, a part of her instantly knew for certain that the levels were, indeed, not working as they should. As by now expected, this newfound knowledge did not come with an ability to fix the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh mother," Ferio mumbled beside her, removing the hand that had rested on Aperio's back the entire time. "When will you learn to accept help?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;How exactly are they supposed to help me?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, the irritation apparent in her voice. "&lt;em&gt;You yourself were unable to fight another God in their Dominion.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter rubbed the bridge of her nose at Aperio's words. "Yes, they can't help you with the fight, but that is not the only thing they could do. Take Laelia here. She is a capable fighter, yes, but she also knows firsthand about Vigil's church. How it functioned. What it expected. She would be the perfect choice to help those who lost their God. Let &lt;em&gt;her&lt;/em&gt; tell them what he did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You don't want to involve yourself too much, and I understand why, but someone has to be involved at this juncture. If not you, then someone that could at least ask you for clarification on issues they themselves can't answer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio's wings twitched slightly, a good part of her not liking that her &lt;em&gt;daughter &lt;/em&gt;was giving her a lecture. She had no real reason to be angry of course, as what Ferio said was very much valid — good advice, even. It was just her inherent dislike of someone being better or knowing more than she did acting up again. &lt;em&gt;Can't I just cut that part out?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;And what if something happens to her when she goes out and does something I told her to do? I am responsible for enough already, I do not want to be the one that sent someone on a trivial mission only for them to be killed by a vengeful lunatic.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I doubt anyone in this city — besides your two followers themselves — could injure them, much less kill them. They might appear weak and fragile to you, but so does everything else," Ferio said with a sigh. "I know you don't want to depend on others, but haven't you done enough already? If you continue to do everything on your own, it will just play out like before."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A multitude of blue and silver arcs danced across Aperio's skin and wings as she turned to face her daughter. The world surrounding the two had darkened, Aperio's Void starting to leak into the mortal realm. "&lt;em&gt;Nothing will be like before. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I will not be a slave.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio took a slight step back as the arcs of mana lashed out at their surroundings. "Calm, mother. I never meant to imply that. It's just that you are starting to behave like you did before. You never let yourself be helped, would not even accept advice, even from me. I fear that if you do the same again, you will just turn three potential new Goddesses against you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;If they are against me, they will not ascend,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;" Aperio spat, her voice causing Ferio to wince slightly. "&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I will not be bound to anyone; to anything.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio took another step back as the fury in her mother's eyes did not relent. "And I did not say that. Accepting help or delegating tasks does not bind you to them. I understand that the life you lived as a mortal was not pleasant, but that is finished. You are free now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winged Goddess remained unmoved, her eyes fixed on Ferio as the arcs of mana jumped between the feathers of her flared wings. The stone beneath her feet suddenly cracked as Aperio kicked off of it, rocketing into the sky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as she had pierced the dome of darkness, her Void retreated from the mortal realm. Aperio did not look down as she darted through the sky, only stopping when she was high above the city. She took a deep breath of the cold air, closing her eyes as she felt the world itself resonate with the rage that still flowed through her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She did not know why, but the words of Laelia and Ferio had set something in motion, causing a looping chain of her most unpleasant memories to surface in her mind. How the nobles that had forced themselves on her had always told her how dependable she was, how they could not think of a world where they did not have such an obedient puppet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had left before she could do anything that she might regret. She couldn't help but recall the way she had felt her mana react to her emotional state, growing somehow sharper in the air. Recall how she could feel it spreading to Laelia, and to Caethya. They had told her before that they could feel her anger, but now that she had clearly witnessed it happening she could no longer shrug their concerns off. &lt;em&gt;Why am I like this?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why did she make the world depend on her? Everything connected to her, in one way or another. &lt;em&gt;And yet, it still worked when I was gone? &lt;/em&gt;She shook her head, trying to free her mind from the train of thought that had started to form. It was not important right now. First she would need to calm herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio flew upwards, soaring higher and farther until she reached the vast nothing beyond Verenier. Though she could have returned to her Void, and she sorely missed the calming effect it surely would have had, she did not want to become reliant on it. Running to her Dominion every time she got worked up about something didn't seem like a good idea. &lt;em&gt;Not that this is much better.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She stopped beating her wings, simply spreading them out as she let herself drift through the nothing with a touch of magic. Her awareness of things other than herself opened up, and she noticed that the presence that had played with the wisps of her mana was back. This time it seemed more reserved, somehow managing to not approach her despite being woven into every bit of the inky black.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a silent sigh Aperio closed her eyes again. While her body might have forgotten how to get tired, the same could not be said for her mind. Making sense of what her old instincts were telling her and what she actually remembered took quite a toll on her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had wanted to visit Maria, introduce the girl to the other two she had blessed so that they might be able to help one another should the need arise. But, instead, she had failed not only her daughter but the two followers she had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio did not like failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the absence of sound, there was a silent whispering creeping up on the edges of her hearing. Immediately, Aperio opened her eyes and summoned her weapon. Against all logic, a formless shadow was taking shape in front of her. It was clearly the source of the whispering, as it grew louder as the entity coalesced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It only took a little while longer before the countless voices called out as one, addressing the only person in the black nothing. "Welcome, Mistress."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, there is a reason for why she got unresonably mad. It's not just because.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 66: Family Talk</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/115552/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio raised an eyebrow at the empty street in front of her. The only sign that she had returned to the right place was the house of healing. It was still there, and Aperio could sense the people inside — including Laelia and Ferio — but the large crowd outside had disappeared. &lt;em&gt;How long was I gone?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time might not truly matter for her, but the four mortals would have had to eat and sleep at some point. &lt;em&gt;Unless my Void takes away that requirement? ...Or did bathing in that soul-water change them after all?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A quick check on the mortals that currently accompanied her revealed nothing of note. They were just as normal and fragile as before. That she now saw a group of mortals that could have probably killed her in her previous life as something weak and fragile brought her an odd mixture of happiness and apprehension. &lt;em&gt;I will have to be very careful with them, won't I?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wasn't going to get weaker anytime soon; quite the opposite in fact. If her encounter with the first dungeon core was any indication, her power increase would get a sharp uptick every time she retrieved a set of memories and mana held captive by a core. &lt;em&gt;Permanently drawing on my well is also not helping, is it? …Still not going to stop, though.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a slight shake of her head, Aperio sent a small mental nudge to her daughter, asking where everybody went. She did not receive a mental reply. Instead, her daughter appeared before her and hugged Aperio in a rather ungodly display of affection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't just disappear for a week!" Ferio's muffled voice was easier to understand for Aperio than it should; the realisation also brought with it the noise of the city surrounding them, something Aperio could have done without. "At least warn me before you do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;A week?&lt;/em&gt;" the winged Goddess asked, lightly patting her daughter's head. "&lt;em&gt;It most certainly did not feel that long.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;What would happen if I went to my Void and started fiddling with the System? Would I just disappear for a millennia and not notice?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio simply sighed and separated herself from her mother, just in time to preserve her dignity as Caethya, Laelia and a few workers left the house of healing. "Your perception of time is off at the best of times, mother. Staying in your Void only makes it worse."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But I like my Void… &lt;/em&gt;Staying in the black nothing was something she would likely do a lot more once she had retrieved all her memories. &lt;em&gt;How long will that take? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio also still felt uneasy about retrieving all the memories pertaining to her former self.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first set she had reclaimed had brought her untold happiness, as very little could compare to being able to actually remember raising her daughter. What she had gotten from Vigil and Inanis, however, was something she could have done without. It did answer some questions she had, but it also only underlined the betrayal of the two deities; a fact that did not need reminding. Now that she had the memories back, they would stay with her. &lt;em&gt;Until the next set of Gods decide to kill me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was something she would make sure would not happen again. &lt;em&gt;But to do that, I need to remember. &lt;/em&gt;With a sigh, Aperio pushed the never-ending circle of thoughts down, focusing on the group that had stepped outside to join her and her daughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia still had the bow slung over her shoulder with no arrows in sight. She had, however, changed the rest of her attire. Besides no longer having her hair in a braid, she was now wearing a set of black and blue leather armour that, to Aperio, looked suspiciously similar to what a few of Ferio's followers wore. &lt;em&gt;Did she give her that to show her allegiance to me?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likely answer was yes as Caethya, too, now wore a dress that sported Aperio's preferred colours of silver, blue, and black. &lt;em&gt;All they need is an emblem… Should I make one? &lt;/em&gt;She had not really intended on founding a new religion — &lt;em&gt;Or is it reviving an old one? — &lt;/em&gt;but, like her daughter had said, one would form regardless unless she actively prevented it. &lt;em&gt;I'd rather they know what I want instead of wildly interpreting anything I say.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Where did the others move to?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked again, this time addressing everyone present. She could have gone and used her aura to search for everyone she had brought from the moon, but asking the people in front of her felt like the right thing to do. That the four people she had healed in her Void were frantically looking around was ignored; she had healed them, what they did now was their business. &lt;em&gt;Why do I even want to know where the others went?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had been irritated that the people she had brought here had disappeared, but thinking about it for even a bit longer showed that she honestly did not care. That it had been a gut reaction to someone undoing what she had made. &lt;em&gt;Like someone took my clothes. &lt;/em&gt;She had teleported them there and someone had had the audacity to take them away without asking for her permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of recognising people as a thing — something to be placed where she wanted and used for what she wanted — on an instinctual level was something she did not like. &lt;em&gt;Is that really me? &lt;/em&gt;It had been her gut reaction, the first thing that had come to her mind without thinking. She shook her head in an attempt to clear it. &lt;em&gt;Just another thing to overcome.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a part of her, yes, but she could change. Already had changed. Much of what she knew of her old self was far outside of what she would consider proper or even reasonable. &lt;em&gt;I wouldn't have liked myself, would I?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mother?" Ferio asked, lightly touching her Aperio's shoulder. "Are you okay?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I am fine,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied, not wanting to elaborate further. Her reply did not seem to convince either her daughter or the small group that had come outside. Ferio retracted her hand but lingered for a second longer in front of her mother before stepping aside, seemingly unsure if she should have said something more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A few of them stayed here," Ferio said as she fell into step next to her mother. "We sent the rest to the [Guides]. O'lymni was more than happy to offer her help."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;That's good, is it not? &lt;/em&gt;As far as Aperio knew, the [Guides] were devoted to the collection and distribution of knowledge, something she had nothing against. The fact that they were close to Roots, however, did unnerve her a little. It was rather fond of her, and Aperio was starting to believe that it may have led the [Guides] to view her in a more favourable light. &lt;em&gt;But that was the old me, someone I am not even close to becoming. ...Or want to become.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter did not seem to mind anything she had done in the past, never having voiced any critique of it. The reactions she had, what she felt when people did not follow her word exactly, was something that had led Aperio to believe she had not previously been much of a pleasant person. &lt;em&gt;Did I just hide it from her? And what about Roots? &lt;/em&gt;She would soon have to ask Ferio about her former self.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Did anything else happen in my absence that you would like to inform me about?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, pointedly looking at Caethya and Laelia. She wanted to say that a dress was perhaps not the best working attire but, considering what she herself chose to wear, Aperio elected to keep that comment to herself. &lt;em&gt;But then, I also don't need armour.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike her Elven disciple, she would not get injured by anything less than the weapon of a God. &lt;em&gt;Though, even that would need more testing now, &lt;/em&gt;Aperio thought as she looked at the tiny wisps of mana that were floating around her, melting into her skin whenever they touched it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I got your two most prominent followers something more fitting to wear," her daughter replied. Her next words were whispered, accompanied a small ripple of mana that flowed around them as she leaned closer to her mother. "Are you sure you want her to have one of your weapons? The last time you gave one away, the mortals almost destroyed their world with it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio stopped at the words. Her gaze, which had been slipping towards the cautiously approaching members of the house of healing, zipped back to the weapon she still held firmly in her hand. "&lt;em&gt;How?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It's a bow, how would she destroy a planet with that? &lt;/em&gt;She knew her weapons were powerful, but only in the sense that they enabled her to fight properly, not because they had inherent abilities of their own. &lt;em&gt;Or do they?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Because&lt;/em&gt; of it, might have been a better way to put it. But, what matters is that it did not end well," Ferio said, slightly shaking her head. "At the time I had not paid it much mind — and I still wouldn't now — but you seem to care for the mortals now and until you can remember on your own… I feel like not telling you would be wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Why would you not care for them?&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Why did &lt;/em&gt;I&lt;em&gt; not care for them? I &lt;/em&gt;made &lt;em&gt;them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You misunderstand, mother. I care for those who follow me, but not in what world they do so. You made more than enough for them to choose from, after all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;So anyone that does not follow is worthless to you?&lt;/em&gt;" The idea stung. That her own daughter thought that way hurt more than she would have expected, even if she should have seen it coming. &lt;em&gt;She was never a mortal… Why would she care? &lt;/em&gt;It also begged the question of why she herself should care. Nearly every mortal she had dealt with in her previous life had been detestable, and even her first encounter with them after returning had been less than stellar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio did not reply immediately. She simply stared at her mother for a moment, then sighed. "It's not that they are worthless, but that I don't really care what happens to them. I take after you in that regard; the old you, at least. And, if I am being honest, I don't understand why you would like them now. They enslaved you, treated you like their plaything."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter was right, to a degree at least. There was no real reason for her to care about all of them. And she didn't. Aperio only really &lt;em&gt;cared &lt;/em&gt;about her daughter, and the few mortals that were close to her, but still she found the idea of simply letting millions die to be abhorrent. That she had apparently done that in the past was just another thing she wished she did not know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Some mortals did that, yes,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said after a brief pause. She was having trouble finding the right words to express her thoughts, something she usually had no problems with. "&lt;em&gt;But they are long dead, and these ones have done nothing wrong yet. I would even go as far as to say that I enjoy their company.&lt;/em&gt;" She took an extra moment to double-check her spoken statement, and the emotions in it rang true. Simply spending time with Caethya and Laelia, being in their presence and feeling comfortable, was something that brought a tiny bit of happiness to the winged Goddess. The brief time she had spent with Maria had been fun for her as well, even if she had severely misunderstood the little girl's father. &lt;em&gt;I should visit her again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her mother's words brought a small smile to Ferio's face, something Aperio had not really expected. "So you care for the ones that follow you, just like I do about those that follow me. But, in the end, what I think of them doesn't really matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just wanted you to know the dangers of giving one of your weapons to a mortal. Anything given by a deity is polarising for them. And, considering you are the one that reigns above the rest of us, having a weapon that was made to work with your strength is something that appeals to more than just mortals," Ferio said. "I doubt your Scion would do anything stupid like giving it away, but at the moment she is far from capable of defending that bow. Vigil and Inanis weren't the only ones that benefited from your absence."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;No, they were not.&lt;/em&gt;" The names of the other deities that had tried to usurp control of the System were still in Aperio's mind, the memory just as clear as when she had first seen it. "&lt;em&gt;I do not intend to leave her alone, however. At least, not for a while yet.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh? What do you want to do now, mother?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I want to find more dungeons; remember who I was,&lt;/em&gt;" she replied. "&lt;em&gt;But I also want to live. I have never had the freedom to do what I wanted, to go somewhere simply because I felt like it. Even now I do not have that luxury. Not really. I do not know how many more souls have been marred by Vigil; do not know if he was the only one doing it. Simply knowing that there might be others capable of such a thing is making me sick.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio directed her gaze downwards at the words. "I wish I could help you there, but souls are something I do not wish to tamper with."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Nor do I wish you to,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, gently lifting her daughter's head. "&lt;em&gt;You are already helping me enough.&lt;/em&gt;" Just talking to her daughter was helping more than Aperio had expected, and all she could ask for. &lt;em&gt;Now, if only the others could treat me like a normal person as well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a slight shake of her head, she gave Ferio a brief hug before stepping through the thin veil of magic that had kept their conversation silent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 65: Souls and Solutions</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/115549/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio watched with interest as Laelia rose to her feet, testing the weight of the bow in her hands. As her Scion didn't seem quite able to carry it with the same ease, it seemed that the weapon was heavier than expected. &lt;em&gt;Or does she think it could break?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;that the weapon could take a bit of punishment from herself, and Aperio was very certain her strength vastly eclipsed that of her Scion. "&lt;em&gt;It will not break. Feel free to handle it as such.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia directed her eyes towards the winged Goddess, an awkward smile on her face. "I know it won't break, it's just a lot heavier than I thought a bow would ever be. I don't think I will be able to use this anytime soon."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Oh… Can I make the weapon lighter? &lt;/em&gt;She probably could, she just did not know how. &lt;em&gt;How did I make them, anyway? &lt;/em&gt;From observation, she knew that they were made of a material that could withstand her strength, to a degree. She was certain that, if she wanted to, she could break her weapon, but she would much prefer to keep it intact. Unlike any normal weapon, hers would allow her to fight &lt;em&gt;properly&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A thought was all that was required for Aperio's swordstaff to appear in her hand — free of the traitor's blood, of course. She spun the weapon, a motion that came frighteningly easy to her. Using a bit more force to grip the weapon did not bend it, just as she had thought. Still, she could feel that there was a limit to the material's resilience, one that she knew she would hit far sooner than the limits of her own strength. &lt;em&gt;If there even is a limit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was something she wasn't quite so sure about yet. There had to be one for her physical self, but whatever her body could not do on its own, a touch of her magic should solve. &lt;em&gt;Do I even need a body? &lt;/em&gt;It was an interesting thought, but Aperio had no current desire to do any testing of the theory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Are you ready to return?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, resting the butt of her staff on the invisible ground. That she could stand on the nothing in her Void still felt surreal, but considering that her home would reflect any change she wanted to, it was most likely not the most outlandish thing she could do here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes," Laelia replied. She slung the bow over her, an action that garnered a raised eyebrow from the winged Goddess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Do you not have a storage skill?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I do, but I would rather carry the weapon with me. It feels wrong not to."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;She does that because I gave it to her, doesn't she? &lt;/em&gt;"&lt;em&gt;You do not have to treat it with reverence simply because it was me who gave it to you. It is a weapon; use it as such.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then I shall keep it at the ready," Laelia said, a small smile gracing her features. "Just in case I need it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio shook her head at the reply. &lt;em&gt;Does she have a skill that lets her make arrows? &lt;/em&gt;The answer to that was most likely yes; making an arrow from mana should not be that much harder than making a fireball. &lt;em&gt;They won't be as good as what Inanis used, though. &lt;/em&gt;The now-dead Goddess had to have used arrows that Aperio herself had made once upon a time, seeing how they managed to evade even her grasp for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With another thought, reality rearranged itself and the two of them reappeared just outside of the house of healing, where they had been just moments ago. The first to react was Laelia's adoptive daughter. Brenia ran towards her foster mother, hugging her as soon as she was able to. Aperio noted with mild amusement that the girl was wearing the feather she had given her, fastened to her head with a matching black strip of cloth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;It would seem your daughter missed you quite dearly,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, a warm smile on her face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes," Laelia replied, shifting the girl in her arms to better hold her. "It would seem so."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think congratulations are in order," Ferio said as she stepped closer to the newly minted Scion, interrupting further talk. "It has been quite a while since I saw someone with that title."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head at the statement. &lt;em&gt;I had Scions before? What happened to them? &lt;/em&gt;It was hopefully something she could find an answer to sooner rather than later. &lt;em&gt;Then again, do I even want to know? &lt;/em&gt;What she had learned about her previous self did not exactly inspire confidence in what else she might uncover. &lt;em&gt;I wasn't really nice, was I?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a shake of her head, Aperio focused on the surroundings, leaving her daughter and her Scion alone for the moment. She still needed to deal with a mass of people that no longer had a place to call home. &lt;em&gt;Or a purpose in life. &lt;/em&gt;She also had to check how many of them had been marred by Vigil. Aperio was certain that at least a few of his moon-based followers would bear similar runic soul scarring to that of Laelia. &lt;em&gt;All his paladins have it, according to her.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a step towards the group caused a few of them to shuffle backwards, trying to keep their distance from the winged Goddess. Aperio tried her best to ignore them. That they were scared was to be expected. &lt;em&gt;I &lt;/em&gt;did &lt;em&gt;kill their God. &lt;/em&gt;It did not matter how easy the deed had been for her, it still resulted in a fundamental change in these people's lives. &lt;em&gt;And for some, perhaps, freedom.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Who here was a paladin of Vigil?&lt;/em&gt;" Her voice echoed through the street, easily reaching everyone in the crowd before her. &lt;em&gt;And I did not even raise my voice.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody answered her question. In fact, most of the people cowered instead, some of them even attempting to hide behind her daughter's followers. "&lt;em&gt;I have not come to judge what you may have done; may have been forced to do. I merely wish to make sure that everyone here is free from the traitor's influence.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a moment of silence following her statement, but soon a man wearing a white robe with intricate gold ornaments stepped forward. "Who, exactly, are you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head at the question. &lt;em&gt;Natio's fanatic knew who I was, but they don't? &lt;/em&gt;Despite knowing that Vigil and Inanis had tried to erase all memory of her from existence, she had expected their followers to know how she looked. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps not what I am, exactly, but at least a name and an image. Something that would at least imply that I am a danger so that they would know if I was found again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of an immediate reply caused the robed man to take a step back, seemingly taking the silence as a threat. His actions had also caused the last stragglers of the group that had not paid attention to Aperio to cease their intermittent talks and focus on the winged Goddess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Aperio,&lt;/em&gt;" she finally said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reveal of her name did not garner much of a reaction from the crowds — only a few sporadic murmurs and confused looks. &lt;em&gt;They have no idea, do they? &lt;/em&gt;Shifting the swordstaff she still held in her hand got more of a reaction, most trying to further distance themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a sigh, Aperio shook her head and let her weapon return to her Void. "&lt;em&gt;This will only take a moment.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wave of mana followed her words, tearing innumerable tiny holes in the fabric of reality. She had no desire to bring the entire group into her Void, but bringing a fraction of her Dominion into the mortal realm? That she could do. &lt;em&gt;It only requires a thought, after all.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio ignored the panicked yells of the people as they were cast in darkness, the homely feeling she got from even the tiny bit of her Void obviously not spreading to the mortals in front of her. The tendrils of mana that spread from her to each individual in the group garnered no reaction, the mortals either unable to see them or too concerned about the darkness of her Void to notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it was somewhat cruel on her part, but Aperio found she cared little for the people in front of her. She was certain most of these mortals were following Vigil of their own free will, and as such were undeserving of the level of care she had given in healing Laelia. She expected to only find the soul-marring marks on a few.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weaving the countless threads of her mana through tiny passageways to the soul of each mortal was a surprisingly easy task. It still required a far greater amount of her concentration than most anything so far had done, but concentration was something she had plenty of. All in all, it was still a surprisingly negligible strain on her abilities. &lt;em&gt;What have I become?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing what she could do and actually taking advantage of her abilities were vastly different things. She &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;she could check on every single one of them, but actually doing it — with what felt like too little effort — was something else. Aperio might not have cared much for them, but she still did not want to kill them. It would only take a slight mishap on her part for a mortal to perish. &lt;em&gt;Shockingly easy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It only took a moment longer for Aperio to realise that, out of the group of over a hundred, only four other people had markings on their soul. Having found what she was looking for, she brought the four that had been marred to her Void, letting her Dominion fade from the mortal realm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While she most likely could have done what she needed to do while they were standing out in the open, Aperio felt a lot safer doing it in her Void. She tried to ignore the shaky breath and darting eyes of the four people she had brought with her, but could not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Calm… I brought you here so I can help you.&lt;/em&gt;" No-one replied to her, all of them simply continuing to peer off into different regions of empty blackness, clearly trying to look for a way out of her Void.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a silent sigh, Aperio focused on the souls of the people in front of her. Each person seemed to have a different assortment of runes carved onto the core of their very being, most of which she could not yet decipher. The only ones present on every one of them were Servitude and Obedience. &lt;em&gt;Disgusting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if she herself was currently acting against the will of the mortals, Aperio would not stop until their souls were whole again. &lt;em&gt;But how do I do that without blessing them? &lt;/em&gt;It wasn't like healing a body where she could just let her mana be guided by the person's own. Their soul saw no reason to repair itself, seemingly thinking the runes engraved upon it were supposed to be there. There was only one thing she could think of that would heal a soul and not imbue it with her power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A thought later, Aperio and the four marred mortals were floating above the river of souls that flowed through her Dominion. Wanting to avoid another potential fiasco similar to the one she had set in motion when she had carelessly approached the river upon her first remembered arrival in the Void, she had chosen a section that had far fewer orbs flowing through it. Another small flex of her mental muscles provided a large bath house made of marble, into which a part of the soul river was diverted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as the invisible flow touched the marble, a silvery liquid became visible. Its radiance coiled and shimmered beneath the surface as it quickly filled the bath Aperio had made. She &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;that the river returned a soul to its original state; to how she had first made it. &lt;em&gt;Now I just have to stop them from forgetting who they are.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio did not know exactly how she would do so, but a warm, reassuring feeling at the back of her mind spurred her onwards. "&lt;em&gt;Please, step inside.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mortals simply stared at her, not moving a single step towards the silvery liquid. Seeing that her words would do little to persuade them, Aperio herself stepped into the shallow liquid. She spread her wings and gently let herself fall backwards, landing surprisingly softly on the soul-water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tingle ran up her spine as she drifted on the surface, whatever it was that flowed through her Dominion clearly reacting to her. &lt;em&gt;Why didn't it do that when I touched the souls? &lt;/em&gt;She pushed the thought from her mind for the moment, righting herself and gesturing towards the mortals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing happened for a long moment. Then, after exchanging glances with the others, an older man tentatively stepped forwards. First to try his luck, he very slowly stepped into the liquid, then stopped briefly to stare at his reflection. When nothing dire seemed to happen, he continued onwards, further immersing himself in the liquid that still contained surges and shimmers of silver. He stood there for a moment, staring at nothing in particular before he slowly lowered himself into the river's water and said something that Aperio did not understand. The other three people then reacted, moving to join the old man in the pool. &lt;em&gt;Did they not understand a thing I said? ...They probably didn't.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio still kept watch over their souls, waiting to see how the river's water would heal them. It was not as obvious or fast as her more direct intervention, but she could see the marks on their souls fade. That was, however, the only change she could see. Nothing inside the soul changed, the lightly glowing and swirling mist within remained untouched by the river's water. &lt;em&gt;Does it only heal them because I want it to, or because they have a body?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watching their souls slowly heal brought a calm and happiness to Aperio's mind that she had not expected. A large part of her felt she should not be happy that people who had worshipped the God that had killed her were getting healed. &lt;em&gt;But, did they have a choice? &lt;/em&gt;It was a question she would likely never get an answer to, but neither did she truly care. Knowing that she could remove the filth Vigil had brought into the world was good enough for now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time seemed to pass slowly. How long they floated in the silvery waters of the soul river, waiting for the last vestiges of the runes to vanish, Aperio did not know. At last, when all four of the people received the [Sovereignty of the Self] title, it was time for them to leave her Void. Aperio stood up, and the movement seemed to startle the mortals. Perhaps they had forgotten that she had been there, floating on the shimmering liquid next to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her dress was not wet, a fact that went ignored as she brought them back to the house of healing with a thought. &lt;em&gt;Now I just have to find a way to do this without bringing people into my Void.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 64: Forced Ascension</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/115547/</link><description>&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
Stay Safe.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia gritted her teeth as she felt the white-hot mana of her Goddess flow through her. She could feel her bones breaking and her muscles tearing, but she could also feel a comforting warmth spread through her as Aperio did something to her soul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was almost the exact opposite of the induction ceremony she had partaken in to become a true paladin of Vigil. That one had only been filled with pain. Not from her body or mind as she felt now, but from the unseen part of her that held her mana. She could feel her reserves deepening, more and more mana becoming available to her. Laelia could also feel the comforting touch of warmth starting to soothe her from without as well as within. It slowly spread from her mana reserves to encompass her entire being, pushing away the pain of her changing form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By now, she was certain that whatever her Goddess was doing had gone far beyond an inspection. &lt;em&gt;But what &lt;/em&gt;is&lt;em&gt; she doing? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio had been apologetic after she had stripped Vigil's blessing and replaced it with her own. That the winged Goddess also always seemed to emphasize that Laelia was free to choose had led her to believe that she would not do anything too drastic without warning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet, here she was, feeling every part of her body being broken and reforged; feeling her well of mana deepen to levels she had not thought possible. What was most confusing for Laelia, however, was the feeling of wholeness the changes brought. In the beginning it had felt strange. Foreign, as though someone had been trying to graft parts of someone else onto her person. Now, all she could conclude was that when she had been inducted into Vigil's order, they had taken something from her. Taken something that she had never known she had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A small, familiar pull on her mind caught Laelia's attention. The pain she had felt in the beginning had, without her notice, already dwindled to nothingness. Replacing it was a feeling of serenity, one which allowed her mind to focus with a sharpness she had never previously known.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #ecf0f1;background-color: #00436e"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;You have been awarded the [Demigod] title!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;[Demigod]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;You had already taken the first steps on your path to divinity. Now, with the help of the All-Mother herself, you have shed your mortal flesh and purged the last vestiges of a fallen God from your soul.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #ecf0f1;background-color: #00436e"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;Your title [Sovereignty of the Mind] has been changed to [Sovereignty of the Self]!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;[Sovereignty of the Self]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;Not only has your mind been freed from foreign influence, but your very soul. Such violations of the self will no longer be permitted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Demigod? Already took the first steps? &lt;/em&gt;She had not taken any conscious steps towards divinity; she had simply found a new Goddess. One far more worthy of her devotion. The last part of the title's description made a lot more sense to her. The pain she had gone through had to have been the 'shedding of her mortal flesh', as the System had put it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the claims it made, Laelia herself did not feel any more like a Goddess than she had before. Aperio's presence was still as overwhelming as it had ever been. The only difference Laelia could notice was the strange web. Where before there had been nothing to see in the spaces between people and things, now there were tiny threads present, crisscrossing through everything. The more she observed these things, the more she realized that they were made of mana, and they connected everything and everyone to her Goddess. The fact that she could see the world around her while her eyes were closed took a moment longer to sink in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like every other paladin, Laelia had learned to use every skill at her disposal. This included an active development of her awareness, until she had learned how to sense the world around her through her aura alone. Actually being able to &lt;em&gt;see &lt;/em&gt;with her aura, though, was a feat she had thought reserved for accomplished mages.&lt;em&gt; Or Gods.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her mind was ripped from her reverie as a new wave of pain and warmth spread through her. The conflicting feelings caused Laelia to open her eyes, searching for something to keep her mind distracted as she was unable — and unwilling — to stop the change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio's hand brushing over her cheek and the pained expression on her face brought the distraction Laelia had desired, even if they did that in a way she would rather not see. Her Goddess did not need to speak for Laelia to know the reason for her sadness. Aperio had made it quite clear that she did not like to force her will on people. Something she had just done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I am sorry, Laelia,&lt;/em&gt;" the winged Goddess said, her eyes darting around as if they were looking for something only she could see. "&lt;em&gt;I could not leave the mark on your soul; it had to be purged.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia wanted to reply but found herself unable to as her body convulsed, bending in ways she would have thought impossible. Her sudden motion caused Aperio to quickly retract her hand, a gentle warmth spreading around her instead. It only took the Human a moment to recognise the gentle touch of her Goddess' magic as it held her aloft and slowly eased the pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The way she could feel her flesh writhing beneath her skin, how she was able to perceive the threads of her Goddess' magic wash over her caused Laelia to shiver involuntarily. She had not known — or would have believed — that she was able to notice such things. How had she been so blind all her life? Mana had always surrounded her, how could she never have noticed it before?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia took a deep breath as her muscles relaxed. Whatever Aperio had done was finished, that she knew. Taking mental stock of herself and her new state, she was surprised to find that she didn't feel all that different. The only thing that was immediately obvious was the frankly ridiculous amount of mana she now had access to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was about to draw from her well to cast a simple spell when another notification surfaced at the edge of her mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #ecf0f1;background-color: #00436e"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;You have been awarded the [Scion of the All-Mother] title!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;[Scion of the All-Mother]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;The All-Mother has given you a fraction of her might; beyond what others of your kind may carry. Beware your power.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The System's message was accompanied by yet another wave of mana. While this one did not cause pain, it still managed to elicit a yelp from the Human woman as the world around her suddenly took on a sharpness that caused her to squint her eyes. &lt;em&gt;What?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She blinked a few times, and the sharpness of the world seemed to resolve into something she could tolerate looking at. Everything seemed so much more detailed than before, but some details in particular seemed odd enough for prolonged pondering. Tiny imperfections in Aperio's dress were now visible to her, scattered about the fabric in what seemed to be a random fashion. The bulk of her Goddess' attire was made from something other than cloth — mana woven by Aperio herself, if the Human had to guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second, and more perplexing detail than just the strange inconsistencies of the fabric of her Goddess' dress was the presence of tiny strands of mana reaching out from the Goddess herself. They were not always visible, darting in and out of her enhanced vision in a way that made her truly curious about what they were. They were not the same as the countless strands that moved toward her Goddess, connecting everything to her, but something else. While Laelia could not quite grasp what they were, she instinctively knew that they were important, and that messing with them would be a very good way to head to an early grave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio watched with bemusement as Laelia spun in circles. Her Paladin's eyes darted around, sometimes lingering for a suspicious fraction of a second on the threads that bound reality together. &lt;em&gt;Can she see them?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winged Goddess lightly shook her head, dismissing the notification that Laelia had ascended to become a Demigod. It was not what she had intended, but with how much mana she had used, it would have been strange for nothing to happen. She had been expecting &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; as a result of her actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What surprised Aperio more was that Laelia had &lt;em&gt;not &lt;/em&gt;gotten the [Touched by the All-Mother] title, but a different one. &lt;em&gt;Why Scion? &lt;/em&gt;She wasn't training a replacement for herself. In fact, Aperio was very sure she could not — could never — be replaced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vigil and Inanis &lt;em&gt;had &lt;/em&gt;killed her, but she had still came back. &lt;em&gt;It just took a while. &lt;/em&gt;Her absence also did not appear to have been beneficial to the world. The System was broken, and some of the Gods had seen it fit to use the mortals as pawns for their pleasure. &lt;em&gt;What happened on the other worlds?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likely answer was that what happened on Verenier was not the exception, but the rule. That begged the question of how many worlds — &lt;em&gt;Or Realms? — &lt;/em&gt;there were. How many deities she had made.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a shake of her head, Aperio pushed the line of thought from her mind. She had something much more important to deal with. "&lt;em&gt;Laelia.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mention of her name caused the Human to stop her turning and focus on the winged Goddess. Healing her soul and dumping more mana than was in any way reasonable into her paladin had brought changes that Aperio was fairly sure anyone would notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite physically not having changed much, Laelia now seemed to demand more attention. She had not grown taller or gained more definition as Aperio herself had, rather she seemed to have acquired a certain something that made others take heed of her presence. &lt;em&gt;How does that work? ...Do I do this to people? &lt;/em&gt;It would certainly explain why people always reacted rather decisively to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;You are free to leave if you so choose,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, "&lt;em&gt;but I had to remove the mark on your soul, even if I had not been given your consent to do so. There is not a world in which I would let someone's soul be marred with runes that strip their will. Even if it requires me to force the matter.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;How am I supposed to know if they don't want my help? Whoever made the mark could just command them to deny it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia hesitated for a moment, her brows fluttering in what Aperio guessed was confusion. "Runes on my soul?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Yes. Servitude, Obedience, the same as you would find on a slave collar.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is that why I feel… whole now?" Laelia asked, and Aperio noted with mild surprise that the choppiness of the woman's speech was gone. &lt;em&gt;Did she learn the language from my mana, or was the mark on her soul somehow stopping her from using her full linguistic abilities?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That her paladin did not seem concerned with her blatant violation of everything she wanted to stand for did irk the All-Mother. &lt;em&gt;Does it not matter to her? Or does she think she cannot question me?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Perhaps,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied. "&lt;em&gt;But, do you not mind that I tampered with your soul? Though you might not have been able to stop me, it does not mean that you should simply accept the matter. You are allowed to be angry at me.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia did not reply, simply staring at Aperio. The winged Goddess tilted her head at the lack of an answer. &lt;em&gt;She does hate me, doesn't she? &lt;/em&gt;It was what she had expected; what was supposed to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am angry, but not at you," her paladin said, briefly pausing at her own words. "Why do I know how to speak this language now? I could never remember the right words, no matter how hard I tried."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Perhaps it was the mark, then. Why? &lt;/em&gt;It did not really make sense to Aperio. Preventing someone from learning a language did not accomplish much, especially if they were still able to speak it anyway. &lt;em&gt;Broken as it may have been.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The runes that had been carved into Laelia's soul were still fresh in Aperio's mind but, despite being able to recall all of them perfectly, she did not actually know if any one of them pertained to the use of language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Perhaps Vigil had not wished for you to speak another language properly. Why he would do such a thing I would not know." &lt;/em&gt;Admitting her lack of knowledge had been surprisingly easy, the usual feeling of disgust nowhere to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia simply shook her head, likely dismissing the rather magical acquisition of a language for later thought. "I am not angry at you. Not because I fear you might kill me, but because I trust your judgement to do what is best. Yes, the change hurt, but it was worth it in my mind. Though, declaring me as a Scion of yours might be a burden I am not ready to carry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Do you want me to rescind the title?&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Once I figure out how.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No!" Laelia exclaimed, taking a step towards the winged Goddess. "I will give it my all, I just ask that you are patient as I adjust. Perceiving the world as I do now is something I was not prepared for."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;What do you perceive now?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Details I have never known existed. I can feel your mana brush over my skin, can feel every part of my body with a clarity I had not thought possible. And I can sometimes see tiny strands of mana that run through everything."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So she can see them. &lt;/em&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Do not touch the threads. They are not something one should play with.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I did not intend to, nor do I think I can," Laelia quickly said. "They feel… important, in a way. Beyond my reach."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio nodded at that. It was good her paladin understood their importance. "&lt;em&gt;Are you certain that you are fine as you are? That what I did to you was the right thing?&lt;/em&gt;" It stung a little to ask such questions; a minor annoyance Aperio would gladly bear to be sure her paladin, her Scion, was indeed all right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia looked at her hands at the question, balling them into fists as if to test them. "I feel better — stronger — than ever. I can finally speak the language I spent over a decade learning, and all of that for less pain than the induction as a paladin of Vigil. I think I am fine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She hesitated for a moment, taking a step to what Aperio assumed would be a respectful distance before she continued speaking. "You care for those that follow you, acting in ways most would think unbecoming of &lt;em&gt;the &lt;/em&gt;All-Mother. All because you want to make sure a random mortal will be free again, even if that requires a brief subversion of their will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have not known you for long, but I trust you more than anyone else I know. You saved my children and asked for nothing. You saved me from Vigil, healed my soul, and the first thing you did was ask for forgiveness for not asking my permission first. I cannot think of anything that would make a Goddess more worthy of my devotion."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She took a knee in a graceful movement, holding her hands palm up towards Aperio. "I, Laelia Whytegaard, daughter of nobody, pledge my life and fealty to Aperio, the All-Mother; creator of all there is. I swear that I will be true and faithful, that I will be your sword and shield to bring your word and values to the world below so that they may live free from the reins of tyrants."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her words were accompanied by a wave of mana, the universe itself seemingly welcoming the impromptu pledge Laelia had made. Aperio looked at her paladin's upturned but empty hands and summoned the bow she had retrieved from Inanis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just as she had seen the Emperor do countless times, she gently laid the weapon in the grasp of her paladin and spoke: "&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rise, my Scion.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, if only she could put that powerup into a mushroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 63: Down the Rabbit Hole</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/105582/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio and her group appeared right outside the house of healing, in front of the group she had recently displaced from Vigil's lunar hideaway. Laelia was rubbing the bridge of her nose, trying to keep the sizable group of people calm, as she noticed her Goddess' arrival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The followers of the dead God also noticed, murmurs spreading as they eyed Aperio. Her attempt at venting had seemingly not gone unnoticed. She paid them no mind, however, instead focusing on her paladin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That Laelia now had to look up to meet her eyes was a strange but oddly pleasant experience. Sadly, she could not say the same for the slight step her paladin took as she laid her eyes upon Aperio. It would seem that being taller and wreathed in her own mana also intimidated what she would have thought of as a veteran. Still, Aperio would not stop her continuous draw on her well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it might not calm her as much as being in her Void or blowing up part of a moon, it still did a good job of bringing a measure of tranquillity to her mind. That it also further enhanced her strength was just a nice bonus. &lt;em&gt;The only bad thing is that I now practically scream Goddess at anyone who is looking at me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I hope you did not have too much trouble dealing with them,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, pushing her thoughts away for the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia hesitated for a moment before she spoke, seemingly unsure of what she should say. "Not really, most confused; not know where are or what year it is."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;They do not know what year it is?&lt;/em&gt;" The statement seemed weird to Aperio. How would someone not know the current year? &lt;em&gt;Unless, of course, they spent a few millennia in a Void like I have. &lt;/em&gt;She doubted that they did that, though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes," her paladin replied with a nod. "They know their God fallen, however."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;They have more than just fallen. Both Vigil and Inanis are dead.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio's statement caused the surroundings to quiet down, the last murmurs of the group stopping. &lt;em&gt;Did the System not inform them of their deaths? &lt;/em&gt;Upon further reflection, it made sense. Why would the System provide a notification to everyone when a normal mortal died?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She clenched her fist as realisation set in. Aperio did not regret what she had done, as she still thought that death was perhaps too lenient for taking her memories, but the fact that she could cast down a God on her whim was not something she had truly considered before. &lt;em&gt;That also means I could make one, no?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That Laelia, Caethya, and Maria could become Goddesses in the future was without a doubt. But, Aperio was also fairly certain she could pick any mortal and make them into a deity in a matter of moments, if she so chose. &lt;em&gt;But why even have them? &lt;/em&gt;The purpose of the pantheon was not something that had revealed itself to her just yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He is… dead?" Laelia asked, seemingly not caring that Inanis had also perished. "Really?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Yes,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied. &lt;em&gt;Did she still believe in him? Or is she relieved? &lt;/em&gt;That &lt;em&gt;her &lt;/em&gt;paladin questioned what she had said did anger her to an extent, but it was ignored. Quite easily so, if she considered the usual effort something like that took.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you," Laelia mumbled, her eyes glassy as she started at nothing in particular. "...Thank you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio ignored the chatter springing anew within the group in front of them, asking her daughter to take care of it with a small mental request as she stepped closer to her paladin. That a few people in familiar red clothing and wearing various sun-themed ornaments were already present furthered Aperio's confidence in delegating the task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia flinched as Aperio touched her, relaxing shortly afterwards as the mana of the Goddess spread through her. Aperio could not find anything wrong with the Human. Not that she expected to. Still, probing the mind of someone else was not something she wanted to try until it was absolutely necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Are you well?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked as gently as she could, lowering herself enough to meet the paladin's eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Human just nodded absentmindedly, still staring at nothing. Aperio retracted her hand from Laelia's shoulder and tilted her head as she tried to find what Laelia was looking at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, the winged Goddess did not manage to find anything in the direction the Human was looking in. An idea surfaced in her mind and, with a small mental nudge, her aura flared briefly, drowning everyone in her mana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio ignored the crowd's reaction, and how her daughter's followers tried to stem the rising tide of anger and renewed confusion, instead focusing on the trace of mana she found floating in front of Laelia. Then she found a similar one floating in front of multiple people in the crowd and some others spread around the city itself. She knew it to be mana from the System; from her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In front of Laelia hung what Aperio guessed was her [Status], though it only showed her titles. There was the one she knew of — was responsible for — but there was also one that she did not expect, one that seemed to be the reason for the Human's stare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #ecf0f1;background-color: #00436e"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;[Sovereignty of the Mind]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;The final shackles on your mind have been broken, set free from the influence of others; never to be conquered again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I did not remove all of Vigil's blessings? How? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio was &lt;em&gt;very &lt;/em&gt;sure she had purged all traces of the now-dead God's mana from Laelia. &lt;em&gt;...Unless. &lt;/em&gt;There was something she had not checked, but would explain why his influence would still remain even if his mana was removed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How she was supposed to check the soul of a living being without killing them was something she was not entirely sure about. A part of her wanted to simply act — go with her gut — but another part called for caution. While she had been willing to trust her instincts a lot more recently, she was not quite as ready to do so when it came to matters of the soul. &lt;em&gt;If a simple touch can bring such change… &lt;/em&gt;She had an idea on how she could observe what she wanted without causing undue harm — &lt;em&gt;Or give her even more of my mana — &lt;/em&gt;but she would only do so with Laelia's permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Laelia,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, gently laying her hand on the Humans cheek. A tiny spark of mana jumped over from the Goddess. "&lt;em&gt;May I inspect your soul?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tiny arc of mana and frankly weird request caused Laelia to wake from her stupor and set her eyes on the winged Goddess. "Inspect my …soul?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Yes, your newest title warrants my attention,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said. "&lt;em&gt;Should you not be comfortable with this, however, I will not force you.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Very slowly, Laelia nodded. "Do I need do something?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;No, just stay calm.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With those words, Aperio stood up to her full height again and closed her eyes. A moment later she felt the calming presence of her Void settle around the two of them. After taking an unnecessary but calming breath, she brought forth a tiny thread of mana in the palm of her hand. Ever so slowly, it began to drift towards Laelia; sinking into her skin as soon as it touched her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio pushed aside the influx of information that wanted to tell her everything about the physical health of her paladin's body and, instead, guided her mana towards Laelia's heart to keep it beating, no matter what. A part of the tendril split with a thought, heading towards what Aperio could only describe as a passage of sorts. It was a small opening, carefully framed by the tiny threads of her mana that made up everything surrounding them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winged Goddess &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; that behind this wilful imperfection in the fabric of reality was Laelia's well. She did not truly know if she would be able to find her soul there too, but it was the only place she could think of that would make sense. &lt;em&gt;Or at least give me a clue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guiding her mana through the tiny hole was harder than she was expecting, but, in the end, it only required a fraction more concentration than it had before. Once she passed the threshold, Aperio was presented with a tiny pool of mana that flowed out of a tiny red and white pearl. &lt;em&gt;Nothing like my well… &lt;/em&gt;She had no source of mana, just a bottomless bit of energy that begged for her to use it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;...&lt;em&gt;I don't have a soul?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's what the pearl was: Laelia's soul. &lt;em&gt;Why don't I have one? &lt;/em&gt;It was possible that, given the vastness of her well, she had simply not searched enough to find her own. Or, something Aperio considered more likely, she truly did not have one. Why would she? She did not belong to the normal cycle of life and death; she had created it herself. Still, despite knowing the likely answer — that a soul was something she had made so that others could live — she could not shake the cold dread that slowly spread through her mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a firm shake of her head, Aperio focused on Laelia's soul again, ignoring the gasping breaths of the woman herself. How exactly the Human managed to be short of breath in a space that had no air whatsoever eluded even Aperio, but she didn't take the time to question it. The most recent shocking revelations took much more precedence in her mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As carefully as she could, Aperio guided her mana towards the lightly glowing pearl. Even now she could already sense the small cracks on its surface, and a closer inspection showed them to be tiny markings — &lt;em&gt;Runes —&lt;/em&gt; that had been etched into Laelia's very soul. It only took her a moment to recognize some of her most hated words. Servitude. Obedience. &lt;em&gt;How could he do this?&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;How could he do this?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The anger she had felt on the moon was incomparable to the rage that was starting to form inside her. She wanted nothing more than to find Vigil's soul and tear it apart; remove any trace of its existence. The mere fact that he had dared to mar a single soul was already reason enough, but from what little she had seen of the people that had resided in his temple, Aperio suspected that Laelia was not the only one whose soul the dead God had defiled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She took another breath of the calming nothing that filled her Void as she, very gently, wrapped the red and white pearl in her mana. Aperio no longer cared if Laelia would gain more of her mana in the process; she wanted to fix the damage done to her soul. &lt;em&gt;Something that only happened because I was gone.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was under no illusion that her absence played no part in this — if she had been around, she was certain that neither Vigil nor Inanis would have done such a thing. Someone messing with the souls of mortals was something she &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;to be wrong. &lt;em&gt;And yet, I did it myself; I am doing it now.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much like the time she had healed Laelia's foster children, Aperio let her magic follow the guidance the other provided. She did not truly know what she had to do to heal a soul, something the glowing orb luckily seemed to have an innate knowledge of. All she needed to do was to supply it with enough mana to carry out its repairs. &lt;em&gt;How many people will I have to heal this way?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if only Vigil had done this — something she heavily doubted — there could be millions of victims of soul tampering. &lt;em&gt;Did he have followers on other worlds? ...How many worlds are there? &lt;/em&gt;The questions kept piling up in her mind as she watched the scars on her paladin's soul slowly fade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio could already feel, and &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt;, the change in the Human's soul her mana brought. The dance of red and white turned more and more to a dance of silver and red, the glow radiating from the orb growing stronger with each passing moment. Even the mana that endlessly poured from Laelia's soul into her well took on a silver sheen, one Aperio was intimately familiar with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was no longer a pool of mana for the Human to draw on but a sea, one that only continued to grow as Aperio provided more of her own to heal the damaged soul. In the back of her mind there was a tiny voice, asking if she was doing the right thing; if Laelia even wanted this. Aperio did not know if the Human desired any of this, but once the knowledge of the soul runes was acquired there was no way the Goddess could let Laelia's soul remain as it was. Doing so would be an affront to everything she had ever done, ever created. &lt;em&gt;That, &lt;/em&gt;she knew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Laelia wanted to hate her for what she had done, she would live with it. But Aperio would not — &lt;em&gt;could not — &lt;/em&gt;let her soul remain damaged like that; even if it meant breaking her rule of not forcing her will on people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With grim determination, Aperio urged more of her mana to aid in the soul's reconstruction, ignoring the ever-expanding ocean of mana residing in Laelia's well. Ignoring how Laelia was grinding her teeth as her body broke and rebuilt itself over and over again to accommodate the strength Aperio forced on her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 62: Unhinged</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/105581/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Caethya took a step back as her Goddess emerged from the portal she had created to Vigil's Dominion. The reflected anger she felt was no longer a tiny buzzing at the back of her mind but a palpable aura that seemed to emanate from Aperio. That her Goddess had executed two of what Caethya would have called major deities was already not a good sign, but feeling the seething anger was another thing entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We are leaving,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;" Aperio declared, a wave of mana following her words. "&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;And so is everyone else.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her Goddess' words caused Caethya to turn around, and only now did she notice the people that had entered the central hall. All of them looked confused, some as if they had woken up from some weird dream while others shifted their eyes from Aperio's bloodied weapon to something only they could see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya knew what they were looking at. The System notifications still lingered in her own vision, waiting to be read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #95a5a6;background-color: #ecf0f1"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000"&gt;Vigil, God of Justice and Light, has fallen from grace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000"&gt;All blessings and curses given by this deity will lose their effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #95a5a6;background-color: #ecf0f1"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000"&gt;Inanis, Goddess of Freedom and Darkness, has fallen from grace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000"&gt;All blessings and curses given by this deity will lose their effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither of the notifications came as a surprise to the young Elf. She had watched her Goddess execute the two other deities, after all. From a safe distance. She wanted to know what, after what was likely millennia of peaceful relations, had resulted in them deserving death, but this was nowhere near the right place to do so. Even if it was, she didn't currently have the courage to ask Aperio in the first place. &lt;em&gt;Will she send me away if I ask?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She did not want to be forced to leave. There was so much she could still learn; about magic, about the nature of life, and even about herself. Caethya had started to have an inkling as to why she felt what she did in the presence of her Goddess, and if it was correct then revealing it would probably get her sent away rather quickly. &lt;em&gt;If not executed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was out of the question to talk to Aperio now about any of the things on Caethya's mind as she had little doubt that, in her current state, the winged Goddess would not refrain from the use of excessive force.&lt;em&gt; What made her this angry?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before any more questions could form in her mind, another wave of mana emanated from her Goddess. A moment later she saw the mass of people disappear, replaced by a faint blue mist that intermittently sparkled with a faint silver sheen that Caethya could not quite identify.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What she had no trouble figuring out, however, was that her Goddess had just displaced over a hundred people in the blink of an eye. &lt;em&gt;I should probably expect things like this, shouldn't I? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio was &lt;em&gt;the &lt;/em&gt;All-Mother after all; something like teleporting people was probably trivial for her. &lt;em&gt;...Or did she kill them? &lt;/em&gt;Caethya hoped Aperio wouldn't do that, but she &lt;em&gt;had &lt;/em&gt;just killed two Gods and was still radiating anger from the experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A gentle nudge from Ferio ripped Caethya from her thoughts. The Goddess had offered her hand and, after a moment's hesitation, the young Elf took it. A moment later Caethya found herself above the moon, floating in the black abyss of space next to Ferio. Much like Aperio had done before, her daughter had created a small bubble of air around them, something the Elf was infinitely thankful for. While she might be able to survive without air for a long time, she did not necessarily like it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What is Aperio going to do?" Caethya asked quietly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio sighed in response, rubbing the bridge of her nose. "I honestly don't know. I have not seen her this angry in a long time. She just told me to leave the moon, and to take you with me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before Caethya could ask another question a wave of mana rolled over them, sending a shudder down Caethya's spine. A moment later, she briefly saw a twinkle of blue on the moon's surface before a blinding flash of silver caused her to avert her gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The luminous assault only lasted a moment, and once it was gone the Elf blinked to clear her eyes. Then she blinked a few more times, trying to understand what had just happened. A part of the moon had simply ceased to exist, a giant new crater taking its place. &lt;em&gt;As if someone took a bite of it.&lt;/em&gt; Of course, she knew Aperio was responsible for it; why else would she send her daughter and disciple away?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, mother," Ferio muttered. "Despite all the change, you still don't do things quietly, do you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She has done something like this before?" Caethya asked, not quite believing the notion. So far, her Goddess had only gotten angry at things that the Elf would argue had been justified. A dungeon made from her mana that was taken against her will would make her angry as well, after all. &lt;em&gt;Did Vigil and Inanis make the dungeons?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wasn't sure about that. There was a bit of her mind that was certain she had heard the claim that the ex-deities had created them, but she was also quite sure that they had also explicitly said that they had not made them. &lt;em&gt;I'll have to ask her, won't I?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, she has done things like this before. Though last time someone made her this angry, she simply removed the entire world they called home." Before Caethya could properly react, Ferio smiled in a comforting manner. "You don't have to worry, they lived alone on a moon. Despite what it might appear like at the moment, she does care about most people."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya wasn't questioning that point; if her Goddess had no regard for the mortals that lived in her world, she would have probably killed a lot more people for not showing her the respect she deserves. Though, how people would even fail to pay their respects was not something she understood. Just being in her presence was a joy that few other things could match.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should have really picked someone else to crush on, Caethya. Mother doesn't really care for such things. At least, she never used to."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The words of the Goddess of Life and Light caused Caethya to turn her head and stare at her. She had not really known what was the cause of her tumultuous emotions, but having it spelled out by Ferio caused the gears in the Elf's head to slowly start turning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As realisation set in, Caethya felt her cheeks and ear-tips flush red in embarrassment. &lt;em&gt;Why her? &lt;/em&gt;She had held no real interest in such things for the longest time. Anything more than a night of fun was just a hindrance to her, most people vying for her affection too weak to be a suitable partner. &lt;em&gt;Is that it?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She returned her attention to the newest crater on the moon, trying to make sense of the swirling thoughts that had surfaced in her mind. Whether or not she should pursue her feelings was a decision she would not make lightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio let out a breath, a faint bit of smoke flowing from her lips. Removing what Vigil had built had calmed her down, but it also raised a question. &lt;em&gt;Did I overdo it? &lt;/em&gt;She &lt;em&gt;had&lt;/em&gt; just removed a part of a moon. A feat that had been shockingly easy, all things considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All she had done was focus on her aura and then, with a tiny nudge of her mind, commanded her mana to remove what had offended her. &lt;em&gt;That was almost too easy. &lt;/em&gt;The absence of sound was perhaps a blessing, as something in the back of Aperio's mind told her that what she had done would have been quite loud as well as blinding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A brief check through her aura confirmed that both Ferio and Caethya were fine, though the latter looked a bit red in the face. &lt;em&gt;Did I hurt her? &lt;/em&gt;A thought was all Aperio needed to appear behind her disciple, gently laying her hand on her shoulder and letting some of her mana flow through her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya stiffened at the touch but relaxed as soon as she noticed who it was that had appeared behind her. Teleporting without her Void as an intermediary was an oddly satisfying feeling, something she had also not expected. Testing her theory on unsuspecting followers of Vigil might not have been the best choice, but at the time she had not cared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had informed Laelia that she would dump a few hundred people on her lap before immediately doing so. Aperio had little doubt that her paladin could deal with the group of confused followers of a dead God. &lt;em&gt;Not that she will be alone with them for long.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As she could find nothing wrong with Caethya, the winged Goddess removed her hand from her disciple's shoulder. While she still felt there was something off, Aperio chose to not dig deeper. &lt;em&gt;Already upset the lives of enough people today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Feeling better?" Ferio asked. "Taking out a bit of moon has to lift your spirits, no?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While her daughter's tone was not exactly to Aperio's liking, she was correct. Letting loose a little &lt;em&gt;had &lt;/em&gt;helped with her anger. That blowing up part of a celestial body only constituted 'a little' did show, however, that she would have to find something else to actually help with relaxation. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps making something?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Yes, it did,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied eventually. "&lt;em&gt;What they did was unacceptable, however. Death might have been too lenient.&lt;/em&gt;" The knowledge that their souls would eventually live a new life did not sit well with her, their crime feeling too big to be punished in only one lifetime. The only thing staying her hand from removing their souls completely was that they were, like every other soul, doomed to forget. They would not remember anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What could be worse than death?" Caethya mumbled quietly, more to herself than anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Killing them just sent their souls back to her Dominion," Ferio replied. "She could have annihilated their very soul, removing any trace of their existence. Or she could have tortured them for all eternity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio face twisted into a grimace at the mention of torture: she did not the like that idea one bit. Neither did the complete annihilation of a soul sit right with her, the very idea upsetting something deep within her. &lt;em&gt;Such measures are not to be taken lightly. &lt;/em&gt;The only thing that had managed to incite a bigger reaction from her was the discovery that both Vigil and Inanis had taken a part of her memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For what purpose they had done so, Aperio had yet to find out, but she doubted it would be anything good. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps it gave them more strength? &lt;/em&gt;She shook her head at the thought. Much like herself, the deities &lt;em&gt;should &lt;/em&gt;be able to grow stronger by simply existing, or at least through proper training. There was no reason why they could not. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps they got lazy?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was something she would have to investigate, now that the two biggest nuisances were removed. The others — the ones that had appeared on the System restoration notification — were still alive, of course, but none of them were deities she knew or particularly cared about at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I did what I thought adequate at the time,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio finally said. "&lt;em&gt;What I think of that decision now matters little. Our stay here has also come to an end, as I would hate for the ex-followers of Vigil to be left alone much longer.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Who knows what Laelia might do with them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, Aperio knew full well, as she had been keeping a proverbial eye on her paladin through her aura. A feat that should, perhaps, garner more of a reaction from her than it did. &lt;em&gt;But this is normal for me, isn't it? &lt;/em&gt;Magic had become second nature to her. In some respects it had become even easier than remembering to breathe. &lt;em&gt;Ridiculous.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lady Aperio?" Caethya asked, turning around to face her Goddess. "What will happen to the people that lived here?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winged Goddess shrugged in response, her wings mirroring the motion. "&lt;em&gt;I have nothing planned for them. They are free to live their life how they see fit.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't you fear that they will turn against you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Turn?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, tiling her head slightly to the side. "&lt;em&gt;They served a God that wanted to kill me; I would say that they have always been against me. Even if they attempt to do something; what exactly are they supposed to achieve if their God has already failed?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya did not reply, instead averting her gaze to look at her feet. Perhaps she thought that her question was a stupid one yet again. The embarrassment was, at least to Aperio, clear in her behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I think it is time we find out,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, offering a hand each to Caethya and Ferio. She might not need to physically touch someone to teleport them, but it felt like the proper thing to do. Once her disciple and daughter had taken the offered hands, Aperio twisted reality apart and brought them to the house of healing where they had left Laelia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blowing up a bit of moon is sure to calm one down, no?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 61: Judgement Day</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/105580/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio took a step towards the man she knew to be Vigil, noting in the back of her mind that neither Ferio nor Caethya had followed her into the traitor's Dominion. It was perhaps for the best, as neither of them would be able to fight a God in their own realm. Aperio herself was not burdened by such frivolous limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She watched the traitorous God in front of her, her smile growing larger as she saw him stagger back a few more steps. A small flex of her mental muscles caused the man to freeze, held in place by the invisible hands of her mana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He paled further as he found himself unable to move, his feeble attempt at breaking free fruitless in the face of Aperio's might. The winged Goddess took another step towards the downed man, a web of cracks spreading through the polished marble floor. With a wave of her hand she caused him to float in the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;You have proven yourself a traitor,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;" Aperio said, her voice echoing through his Dominion. "&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;You have spread lies — tried to erase all memory of me. But, you failed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a thought, she brought the man in front of her. "&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;You sent me into a lifetime of slavery, expecting me to never return. You were wrong.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You have nobody but yourself to blame for that," Vigil said, his voice raspy. "If you hadn't hidden yourself we would have reached our goal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;And what would that be?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;" Aperio asked, shifting her weapon in her hand to point square at his chest. A part of her wanted to end the man right now, kill him for what he had done to her. Get her revenge. But another part wanted to know what they had wanted to accomplish in the first place, why they would make the literal creator of everything they knew their enemy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As if I would tell you that." His words were accompanied by a sliver of mana that tried to pierce the fabric of reality but failed to push past Aperio's aura. &lt;em&gt;Is he trying to call for help? &lt;/em&gt;For the briefest of moments she considered letting him do so, but quickly decided against it. She did not know how they had managed to kill her before, and was not eager to find out if they could do so again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Then I have nothing left for you but your punishment.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;" Though she was still curious about what had caused him to turn against her, she was not keen on the idea of torturing him for information. Neither did she truly want to kill him, though a part of her hungered for the act. Aperio did not want to simply execute what was likely the God of millions of people. &lt;em&gt;Though, their God will die either way. Vigil won't leave with his divinity intact. But why is he putting up less of a fight than Natio?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious answer would be that Vigil actually knew who she was and therefore knew that a fight would be useless, but that did not seem right to Aperio. &lt;em&gt;They have killed me before, so they know it can be done.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As if to answer her question, Aperio felt something shift in her aura that caused her to whip her head around. Coming out of a portal of her own was an Elven woman in a midnight blue dress that Aperio immediately knew to be Inanis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What was more interesting than the traitorous Goddess was the weapon she held. It was a bow, made from the same silver material as her swordstaff. It, too, had a web of lines running all over the main body of the weapon, but those on the bow held by Inanis were dormant and did not pulse with the wielder's power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same was true for the arrow she nocked; the blue edge of the black tip was there but lacking the sheen her swordstaff had. Aperio did not feel threatened by the weapon, the feeling in the back of her mind not classifying it as any more dangerous than the weapons people had already used against her. The distance between herself and Inanis was also adding to her calm. Should she fail to stop the arrow through other means she could always dodge, or simply return to her Void.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a moment of hesitation as Inanis took aim, seemingly unsure of her actions. Aperio simply drew more mana from her well, using it to further increase the rate of her body's improvement. Just because the tiny voice in her mind told her the weapon would be useless did not mean Aperio would not take precautions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And again your hubris will be your downfall," Vigil managed to croak out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio moved him closer in reply, physically grabbing him by the throat. His face paled further as the blood failed to push past her grip, the man's eyes slowly starting to turn milky white. &lt;em&gt;Why does a God even need blood?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was true that she had it too, but it did not seem to serve any purpose as her mana took care of everything that mattered. Aperio shook her head and focused on Inanis instead. Before the winged Goddess had a chance to address her, she let loose the arrow she had nocked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tried to stop the projectile with a touch of her magic but found it to be strangely slippery. She grappled with it like a wet bar of soap, and though she eventually managed to stop it the arrow still felt like it would fall from her mana's grasp at any moment. &lt;em&gt;How does it do that?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could not see or feel the traitorous Goddess use any magic, she had simply nocked the arrow and let it loose. That Aperio had managed to stop the projectile seemed to surprise her as her eyes widened and she quickly produced another black-tipped arrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much like before, it slipped past Aperio's first few attempts before it simply stopped in the air, held aloft by her magic. When Inanis produced a third arrow Aperio had had enough. She let go of Vigil, causing him to float helplessly in the air again and bent reality so that the single step she took allowed her to appear in front of the other Goddess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as they were face to face the woman tried to leave, an inky black portal starting to form behind her. Unlike the previous attempts to stop the arrows, only a single thought was needed to close the passage Inanis had tried to create.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio let go of her swordstaff, letting it float beside her as she reached out and ripped the bow from Inanis' hands. The Goddess tried to hold on to the weapon, but failed to fight Aperio's overwhelming strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as the bow was firmly in her grasp, the web of lines lit up in a familiar blue as her mana flowed through it. Much like her swordstaff, the bow seemingly hummed with joy as it rested in Aperio's hand; eager to be used.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were no arrows to go with the weapon. Where the other Goddess had gotten hers from, Aperio did not know. Neither did it matter, however. She simply stored the bow in her Void for future inspection and grabbed her swordstaff once more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same touch of her magic that she had used to hold Vigil in place now closed its invisible hand around Inanis, the Goddess' face starting to show the first signs of fear as she realised her escape would not be forthcoming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio could not help but smile. That the other traitor had chosen to show herself so soon was a nice turn of events. She had expected that her search for the other Goddess would have involved going to the other moon and searching for something similar to the thread of mana she had found here. How exactly a Dominion was bound to the mortal realm was something she would have to investigate — after she had taken care of the two traitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unnecessary wave of her hand caused Inanis to lift off of the floor and float next to Vigil. "&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Perhaps you can tell me what you two tried to achieve. Your compatriot was not very forthcoming.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Goddess simply glared at Aperio, struggling against her magic in a futile attempt to break free. Aperio could not help but sigh. She had no desire to torture them, but not knowing what they had tried to accomplish in the first place was starting to nag at her in ways she had not expected. Her desire to simply &lt;em&gt;know &lt;/em&gt;was a lot more pronounced than she had ever thought possible. With another sigh, she flicked her wrist, letting Vigil float next to his accomplice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;And you call yourself Gods,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;" she said, the disappointment evident in her voice. Why exactly she felt so disappointed was something she also did not know. &lt;em&gt;Am I blaming myself for picking these two as God and Goddess? &lt;/em&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Natio put up more of a fight than either of you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With an unneeded breath, Aperio focused on her aura. She followed the tiny bits of mana that flowed through Vigil's body, trying to find something similar to the System's seed she had taken from Natio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio did not quite find what she was expecting. At the core of this traitorous God was not a seed made from the System's mana, but one made from her own. She creased her brows as she reached out to grab hold of it, ignoring the hiss of pain that came through Vigil's clenched teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As she pulled the tiny speck of her mana free from the man, he let out a piercing yell. Threads of mana which still connected him to his source of divinity were methodically severed, one by one. The pain he was experiencing as she removed what she had undoubtedly once given him was pointedly ignored. Not even when Vigil fell unconscious did Aperio's mind stray from the task at hand. He had turned against her and any pain he would feel from her taking back the gifts he had enjoyed were his alone to bear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inanis was muttering curses — some of which Aperio even understood — but none of them would change what she would do. With a flex of her mental muscles, the winged Goddess severed the final threads of mana that bound Vigil to his divinity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as the tiny bit of her mana became unbound, it returned to her. That was what she had expected. What she had not expected was the veritable flood of memories that came with it. How she had given Vigil a blessing, setting him on the path of eventual godhood. How, after Inanis had saved Vigil when he was still a mortal, she had done the same for the woman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could remember how they had chosen their new names; had built their fellowship. But she could now also recall how both Vigil and Inanis became more reserved around her, no longer talking with her. At the time, she had not minded. She had been busy with something else, she now remembered, but the specifics of that which had so occupied her still remained out of reach. Taunting her with their presence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite having regained a part of her lost memory, Apero felt nothing but rage bubbling up inside her. How &lt;em&gt;dare&lt;/em&gt; they take her memories? How &lt;em&gt;could &lt;/em&gt;they even do so? Her hand shifted, unbidden, pressing her weapon against Vigil's neck until a sliver of blood began to trickle down. The System's notification that undoubtedly wanted to inform her about the fall of Vigil was ignored as she turned to Inanis, scouring her for the tiny bit of her mana she was sure the Goddess had to have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Severing the seed of divinity from Inanis was as easy as it had been the first time. Another wave of long lost memories flooded her mind, tiny flashes of the life she did not remember. Most were simply a continuation of what she had gotten from Vigil. A few more bits and pieces on the ceremony that had actually made them into a God and Goddess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mortals at the time were happy, bright laughs and smiles resounding through the halls as those invited celebrated the ascension of the people they knew. Aperio herself had been there, hidden from sight through means that did not want to reveal themselves to her now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sucking in a breath, trying to hold back tears that wanted to burst forth for reasons unknown to Aperio's conscious mind, she moved her hand sharply to the left, severing Vigil's head from his body. In a smooth motion that came too easily to her, she shifted the course of her blade and, just as Inanis' expression was starting to show shock and surprise at the decapitation of her partner she, too, was divested of her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;No one steals my memories.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With those words, Aperio turned to leave, dismissing the notification that informed her about the eradication of both Vigil's and Inanis' Dominions. They would never need them again. Now, she would destroy what the defiler had built on her moon. On her creation. Her memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Gods are dead. ˢᵒ ᵉᵈᵍʸ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 60: One Small Step</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/105578/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio slowed down as she got closer to the moon, the celestial rock far larger than she had thought it would be. She knew how big it was as she had observed it through her aura, but seeing it with her own eyes from up close gave her a better understanding of its true scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She turned her head to glance at the planet behind her, but her wings obscured her vision with every beat. Stopping for a moment and letting Caethya down onto a small pane of mana she had created, Aperio fully turned around in order to properly appreciate the view. The young Elf shuffled herself closer to the Goddess, either seeking the warmth she gave off in their cold and unwelcoming surroundings or not fully trusting a thin sheet of mana to carry her despite its origin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio did not give much mind to such matters as she, too, stepped onto the pane of mana, and extended the air-filled bubble to encompass her and Ferio as well. She draped a wing over both her disciple and her daughter. It was perhaps an unneeded motion, but Aperio felt it was the right thing to do, even if only to invoke the idea of a comfortable blanket offering up its warmth. Caethya briefly tensed up at the motion, as whenever the blue-black feathers brushed against her, the tiny wisps of mana darting around them seemed to melt into her skin. Her breath quickened with every bit of mana that joined her, the sensation undoubtedly foreign for the Elf. She let herself fall back, resting her back against her Goddess' wing as she took a couple of deliberate, deep breaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Beautiful, is it not?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, and once her voice reached Caethya's ears the Elf seemed to relax a little, carefully wrapping her arms around the Goddess' waist. Despite still feeling the shift in her aura on the moon's surface, she would take this moment to revel in the sight of her apparent creation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world that hung before them in the nothingness of space was unlike anything Aperio could remember seeing. Seas of blue and green stretched across its surface, intermittently parted by the yellow line of a desert or the grey and white of mountain tops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That she instinctively knew the names of each continent was relegated to the back of her mind. She had probably read them on a map somewhere during her time as a slave; a circumstance of her distressingly sharp memory. &lt;em&gt;Not something I should complain about.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes," Caethya murmured, still holding on tightly to Aperio. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps taking her with me was not the right choice? &lt;/em&gt;If space scared the young Elf, Aperio would not force her to stay there. That her disciple also physically clung to her was another reason to perhaps consider other modes of transportation. &lt;em&gt;Is it frightening to get carried through space?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Aperio might not want to remove her right this instant, the prospect of having someone hug her every hour of the day was not one she enjoyed. &lt;em&gt;Today is an exception. &lt;/em&gt;She had taken Caethya here, and whatever consequences that brought were hers to bear. The question of her suitability for such affection also flashed through her mind. If seemingly very sharp swords did nothing to her, and she could effortlessly punch through a wall, wouldn't she be harder than both? &lt;em&gt;Even my body doesn't make sense anymore.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As nobody else seemed to want to make a comment, Aperio lingered for another moment to look at the marble of life hanging in front of them, then lifted her wings from Ferio and Caethya and turned around; Caethya ending the hug with a start as soon as the Goddess started to move. Whatever was happening on the moon had started to fade again, the shifting of mana she felt in her aura more subdued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither of her two companions had even seemed to notice that something was happening, a fact that Aperio was unsure should make her happy or be a source for concern. &lt;em&gt;If a Goddess doesn't notice it, does that mean it's not worthy of my attention? Or is it something that she could never feel anyway? &lt;/em&gt;That she shared a rather special relationship with all of existence was obvious, but how to interpret the things she felt from the universe around her? Not so much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Are you ready to pay Vigil's temple a visit?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, once again offering her hand to Caethya.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio gave a brief nod, her face unreadable to her mother. &lt;em&gt;Is she concerned? Or does she not like how I treat Caethya? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio discarded the latter thought. Thus far, Ferio had approved of her conduct with her disciple; even if the way in which she had done so struck the winged Goddess as mischievous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The young Elf swallowed slightly before she nodded and took the offered hand. Aperio, again, picked up her disciple and beat her wings to carry her through the nothing. She knew that it was a useless motion, that she could simply push herself along with her mana, but Aperio enjoyed the feeling of her wings propelling her forward; liked going through the physical motions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much like before, the nothingness around her reacted to her passing; tiny shadows chasing after the wisps of mana that danced around her form. Aperio took a breath of the nothing that surrounded her, finding it unable to calm the bubbling feeling of doubt that had started to surface in her mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wasn't sure what she would do if she managed to get into Vigil's Dominion. On the one hand, a part of her was already screaming for his death — wanting to kill him for his insolence, for his insubordination. On the other, however, Aperio wasn't sure if she was even the same person anymore. She knew the memories she had retrieved from the Crystal were hers, but they felt more like distant echoes of childhood than a memory she had consciously taken part in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing she knew for certain was that she would remove Vigil from the pantheon. While she wasn't quite sure why there was a cadre of Gods and Goddesses under her, she did not doubt that they existed for a reason. Having a group sow dissent was not something she wanted. &lt;em&gt;That's how empires fall. &lt;/em&gt;The Inaru Empire had used that tactic more than once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Split your opponent, have them battle each other, then promise to help one side to take over the other and simply take both. Aperio was sure there was more planning to it than that, but the general idea should be pretty close. &lt;em&gt;Divide and conquer. &lt;/em&gt;It did not explain how she had died in the first place, but highlighted the possibility of outside influence. &lt;em&gt;But who?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;she had made all there is, that everything in some way got their strength from her. &lt;em&gt;So who could turn people against me? &lt;/em&gt;The easiest answer was that there was no one, that either Vigil or Inanis had been fed up with the way she had presumably loomed over them, or done whatever she had done at the time, and one — or both — of them had decided a change of leadership was in order. &lt;em&gt;Can they do it again?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not knowing how she had died in the first place was the main reason for the anxiety and doubt in her mind. What if they could do it again? Aperio did not want to die. She liked what she had become. &lt;em&gt;Returned to be? &lt;/em&gt;She wanted to see the worlds she had made, wanted to spend time with her family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wanted to have a life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio closed her eyes as she descended towards the moon's surface and drew more mana from her well. She felt Caethya shift in her arms in response, felt her breath quicken and her muscle tense up ever so slightly. &lt;em&gt;Did I scare her again? &lt;/em&gt;She was fairly certain that drawing on more mana than most mortals could ever dream of commanding with every breath she took would be a frightening experience. It was, however, something she would have to get used to if she wanted to stay at Aperio's side. Restraint was not something the winged Goddess was particularly fond of. &lt;em&gt;Or good at. &lt;/em&gt;Admitting that, of course, brought with it a wave of disgust that she pointedly ignored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coarse, almost sand-like dust that covered the moon's surface scratched against Aperio's bare feet as she set down. Before her was the barrier that kept Vigil's followers alive and breathing, shimmering slightly as it reflected the light of the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio stepped forward, pushing past the slight resistance the barrier offered. A ripple spread from her point of entry, shortly followed by another as her daughter passed behind her. None of the people inside seemed to have noticed their entry, as all of them still went about their business as usual, unperturbed by the presence of two Goddesses who were on less than amicable terms with their God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of reaction was not unwelcome, however. Aperio had no desire to kill people simply because they followed another God. &lt;em&gt;I don't even want followers; I just want to live.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carefully, she set down Caethya, briefly letting her mana flow through her to see if her disciple had incurred any injuries from their move through space. Aperio was unable to find anything wrong besides the rather frantic beat of Caethya's heart, but she chalked that up to being either excited or scared by the vast expanse of nothing. &lt;em&gt;I wish they could see what I do.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having ensured that she was fine, Aperio set off towards the centre of the complex; the familiarity of what resided there having piqued her interest. There was also a tiny voice in the back of her mind that told her that whatever it was that sat there, it would be helpful in her goal of finding Vigil's Dominion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lady Aperio?" Caethya asked quietly. "What exactly are we doing here?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;We are here to find a way into Vigil's Dominion so that I may deliver his punishment.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reply caused the Elf to shift her eyes to Ferio, who simply shrugged in response. "I may be a Goddess, but I do not know how Dominions interact with this realm. Mother has never explained that to me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I am quite certain that the words required for such an explanation do not exist.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Or that I would know them if they do… or could even explain how I know this.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Couldn't you simply transfer the knowledge to someone's mind like you did with me?" Caethya asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head at the question. It should work, she knew as much, but a part of her mind was screaming at her to not do it. That it would end badly for the one she tried it on. "&lt;em&gt;I could do that, yes. It would not end well for whoever received the knowledge, however.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh..." Caethya said, lowering her head slightly. "I am sorry for asking."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;There is no need to be sorry,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied. "&lt;em&gt;You wanted to learn, did you not? You just did. Knowing how the universe works is complex, and can be damaging to a mind of insufficient strength.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Does that even make sense to her?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further conversation was cut short as Aperio felt another shift in her aura, causing her to raise her hand to postpone any potential discussion. The mana in the centre of complex was growing denser, drawing from somewhere she could not see but still recognized on instinct.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio's next step was accompanied by the sound of shattering glass as reality broke in front of her, her stride never faltering as her foot landed on the floor of the central room that held the cloud of mana that had piqued her interest. Her daughter quickly followed, nudging a wide-eyed Caethya along as she did so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as she was in the room, Aperio focused on the mass of mana. She could &lt;em&gt;see &lt;/em&gt;the threads of mana that jutted outwards from it, slowly intertwining with the ones that stitched reality together. A wave of her hand caused the threads to unravel, an action she had done on instinct to investigate something she perceived as &lt;em&gt;wrong&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behind the reality Aperio had known for most of her remembered life, she now saw an ever-changing swirl of colours and energies she instinctively knew but could never hope to name or describe. All the innumerable parts that kept reality alive seemed to pause at her inspection before slowly parting to show her the single thread that ran from the cloud of mana to a place previously unseen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winged Goddess took a step towards the newest tear in her creation, tilting her head as she slowly extended her arm to grab the offending thread of mana. It did not belong here, she &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;that. &lt;em&gt;But why? What&lt;/em&gt; is&lt;em&gt; that?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the source of the shifts she had felt in her aura. An unsanctioned addition to her creation. &lt;em&gt;Did Vigil do this? &lt;/em&gt;Not knowing what the traitor could do infuriated her, but it did not stop her from summoning her weapon to cut the out-of-place thread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as her blade had severed the strand of mana, a shudder ran through the fabric of space, not unlike the one she had felt after she had destroyed the first core. There was no influx of mana or returning memories this time, however. Only a sense of wrongness that slowly faded away, the universe returning to what Aperio deemed natural. &lt;em&gt;What &lt;/em&gt;was &lt;em&gt;that?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She let her senses expand, following the fading thread through the indescribable expanse of shifting colours and noises. Aperio ignored the happy hum that came from her surroundings, focused on following whatever had soiled her creation to its source.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wasn't long before she could feel a presence coming closer, obviously the one who had woven the string. Aperio sent her senses racing ahead, so she could see who had dared to defile her creation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What she saw on the other end of the thread was not what she had expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before her aura's sight, a vast hall expanded. White marble floor with gold inlays covered every bit of the ground and large, gold accented pillars held up a high roof that depicted a man in his prime wearing a tunic made from white and gold fabric as he pulled a world from the blade of a weapon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;My weapon, &lt;/em&gt;Aperio realised a moment later. She spread her senses inside of what she was now sure was Vigil's Dominion, trying to find the traitorous God. It only took her a moment to find the man that was depicted on the ceiling, leaning over a large atlas of what Aperio &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; to be different worlds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His head snapped up, his eyes seemingly meeting hers despite the fact that she was not physically present. Aperio's lips curled into a smile as she saw him stagger backwards, the colour draining from his face. He made a motion with his hand and Aperio felt something futilely push against her aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her smile spread further as she extended her hand and, with a grinding screech, tore reality apart like an discarded piece of paper. She took a deep breath of the warm air that flowed from Vigil's Dominion, and drew more mana from her well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The weapon in her hand thrummed in anticipation as her mana flowed through it, the floor beneath her feet breaking as it struggled against her might. With slightly flared wings, Aperio stepped into the traitor's realm, ignoring the arcs of mana that danced across her feathers and skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The time for Judgement has come.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wild Vigil has apperead!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 59: A Most Peculiar Journey</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/105577/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio knew where she wanted to go, and a thought was all she needed to bend reality to her will. She spread her wings as she felt Ferio's Dominion shift around her, saw how her mana separated the threads that held reality together and wove them back together in new ways to bring her where she wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A moment later, she appeared above the ruined city she had first returned to. Neither her daughter nor Caethya fell, as both were being held aloft by a touch of Aperio's magic. The young Elf averted her gaze before making use of her own flying skill while Ferio seemed content to rely on her mother's magic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio took a deep breath of the cold air, letting it fill her lungs. She &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;that she did not need to breathe, but found the familiar sensation to be soothing to her mind. Visiting the moons was never something she thought she would do, much less on her own power. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps it is an insane idea after all?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a small bit of doubt in her mind, one that said she could not simply fly to her destination. She was certain that she could, however. The small part of her mind that claimed otherwise? Just a remnant that still did not accept what she had become. &lt;em&gt;What do I have to fear from space? My Void is filled with nothing as well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could feel what was beyond the clouds; a vast expanse of emptiness that was wholly devoid of air and warmth. Aperio tilted her head the sensation, not quite knowing what to make of it. That her aura's reach encompassed the vast nothing that existed outside the world did not surprise her, a part of her having already known that it was without bounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The countless lights that filled the night sky twinkled playfully, almost as if they were vying for Aperio's attention; as if they were alive. They reminded her of the souls drifting through her void. Two sets of lights, linked. One was comprised of the seeds from which life could sprout; the other, the givers of warmth that would sustain them once they had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Beautiful, is it not?" Ferio asked, ripping her mother out of her reverie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Yes,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio replied. "&lt;em&gt;It is.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;How did I make all of this? &lt;/em&gt;Besides the glimpses of the universe coming into existence and the feeling of her mana spreading through it all, Aperio did not know &lt;em&gt;how &lt;/em&gt;she had done so. There was no planning she could see in her memories, just a rapid explosion of her mana that set in motion machination she could not remember. &lt;em&gt;Only that it created all of this.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Caethya, can you traverse the nothingness beyond on your own, or do you require my aid?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio could feel that the space beyond the planet was filled with a myriad of things that made no sense to her. Calling it a 'nothingness' was technically wrong, but for most people it would undoubtedly appear as empty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Elf directed her gaze at the sky, a sliver of her mana reaching out past the reaches of the planet's atmosphere. "I could survive for a while, but not long enough to reach either of the moons. I fear that I will require your help if you wish me to accompany you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio waved her off. "&lt;em&gt;Helping you will not be a problem. Having you come against your will, however, would be. You do not have to come if you do not want to.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya focused on her feet at the words. "I want to come, but I also do not want to be a burden. I have spent my entire adult life searching for you. On my own terms, through my own strength. Despite all my years of effort, despite all that I have learned, this is something I cannot overcome on my own. Asking for help – especially from you, my Goddess – does not sit well with me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I understand that asking for help can be hard,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, glancing at her daughter. "&lt;em&gt;But know that you are not a burden to me. You wanted to learn from me, did you not?&lt;/em&gt;" After the winged Goddess had received a hesitant nod in reply she continued, ignoring the vile taste at the back of her throat. "&lt;em&gt;Then see this as your first lesson. Asking for help is not a bad thing. If someone has offered to help you, they will not see you as a burden if you choose to accept.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Something you should take to heart yourself, mother," Ferio mumbled, looking at Aperio with what she assumed to be concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Yes, I should.&lt;/em&gt;" The reply took more effort to push past her lips than most other things she had said since she had returned. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps having a disciple will help with this?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a spark of joy that surfaced whenever she thought about teaching Caethya, bringing her closer to godhood. It felt similar to what she now remembered from Ferio's official ascension. Her daughter might have come into the world a Goddess, but neither the pantheon nor the System had recognised her as such until she had proven herself. It had been an event that had filled Aperio with a joy and happiness that she had only felt once before. &lt;em&gt;At least that I can remember.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only the creation of everything there was had given her a similar feeling, the fact that she would no longer be alone a relief that she had not known before. For Aperio, the seeming similarity in the current situation simply meant that it was something important. She would do her damnedest to ensure that it would work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She took another breath of the cool night air and closed her eyes, focusing on the rhythmic beat of her wings that kept her aloft. A thought was all she needed to send her senses racing towards the bright white moon that hung above them. Aperio had no intention to teleport her group to their destination like she had done in the dungeon — something about the nothingness intrigued her, as though it were calling to her. She wanted to experience it for herself, as well as to slowly approach what the traitorous God had built to see it for herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It did not take her long to spot the large dome of mana that separated lush green fields and flower beds from the grey and white rock of the moon. Pushing past the barrier caused Aperio to briefly pause, the mana comprising it feeling somehow familiar. She creased her brows as she extended her senses deeper into the sprawling complex Vigil had built.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people inside paid no attention to her mana brushing past them, most of them busy with other things. Some were on their knees in front of altars or statues, obviously praying to their God; while others were out in the open, sparring against one another. There were more people in a building to the side, but Aperio had no desire to see more than the passive trickle of information her aura had already provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio's voice reached her ears, a most peculiar experience when Aperio felt like she was standing on the moon already. She ignored the words, however, as they were directed at Caethya and not herself. Instead, she focused her attention towards a collection of mana that floated in the centre of the complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was clear that it was the source of the barrier that allowed the mortals to live on the hostile moon. What intrigued Aperio was the fact that it felt familiar to her; not like the dungeon cores — this was not made from her mana — but still from something she felt she should know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It felt …important.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The finely-woven golden lattice that surrounded the cloud of mana only furthered her belief that it was important, as did the fact that everything in the complex pointed towards it. Underneath the cloud, a giant circle spread out which, in turn, was inside a star with sixteen points, each one pointing to a tower at the outside of the complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio could feel mana running along unseen lines from the cloud towards each tower, all clearly part of what kept the barrier alive. And yet, she knew that the mana was doing more than simply powering the protective dome. The familiarity she felt from it told her that there was so much more it could do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She opened her eyes and drew a bit more mana from her well. The action caused both Ferio and Caethya to quiet down, the latter also moving a little further away. It hurt a little to see her disciple retreat, but she probably saw the amount of mana she could so casually draw from her well as something extraordinary. &lt;em&gt;Something to be feared.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Are both of you ready?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio inquired, extending her hand to Caethya.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio responded with a nod as fiery wings sprouted from her back, propelling her towards the stars with a single beat. Caethya, on the other hand, very slowly took the offered hand, letting her own magic fade as Aperio's mana spread around her. For a brief moment, Aperio considered the simpler solution of putting Caethya in her Void for the journey and retrieving her once she and Ferio had reached the moon. Then she discarded the thought, gently pulling Caethya closer in order to very carefully pick the young Elf up in her arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could have simply used a touch of her magic to have Caethya float behind her, but doing so felt wrong to Aperio. &lt;em&gt;She is not a thing. &lt;/em&gt;Carrying her disciple like a groom would their bride might not be the most appropriate, but Caethya did not seem to mind. With a beat of her wings, Aperio shot upwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A small stream of mana constantly flowed from Goddess to Elf, keeping her alive and healthy. For her comfort, Aperio also wrapped Caethya in a thin cocoon of mana which provided air for her to breathe. She had a feeling that her mana coursing through the Elf would, in itself, be sufficient to keep her alive, but felt that it might be distressing to suddenly lack the ability to breathe. The fact that she herself sometimes forgot to breathe since her return was relegated to the back of her mind. &lt;em&gt;Most people don't simply forget to do that, do they?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another beat of her wings sent her flying past Ferio and into the nothingness that surrounded Verenier. She soared through the inky black, not a sound reaching her ears. There was no resistance to her flight, nothing her wings should be able to find purchase on to propel her forwards — and yet, they did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It did not give her the same feeling of home as her Void did, but neither did it feel as cold and unwelcoming as she had imagined it to be. There was something beneath the endless expanse of nothing that thrummed with joy at her passing, the threads of reality shining ever so slightly brighter. Aperio could feel something move with her; not her daughter who was swaying from side to side as she flew behind her, but something else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was like a shadow that hid itself in the dark spots between the bright stars that filled the nothing — somehow unfathomably big and yet inconsequential to her. A presence that felt no shame to show its joy at her presence but could not give voice to its desires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It played with the tiny wisps of her mana that danced around her being, cloaking them in shadows to try and hide them from her; chasing them as they drifted around her form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio spoke, but not a sound left her lips. A giggle from her daughter entered her mind, telling her that there was no speaking in space, nothing to carry the sound. The winged Goddess only tilted her head and asked the question that floated in her mind. &lt;em&gt;What is this thing?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly, Ferio could not supply an answer. She could not feel the liveliness around them, only the cold nothing of an empty void. The reply caused Aperio to crease her brows. What she felt was real. She knew it to be. &lt;em&gt;What is it, then?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She focused on her aura as she beat her wings again, trying to spot something her eyes could not see. The only thing she could perceive, however, was a weave of mana that seemed to flow through every bit of the nothingness. It was so minuscule in her aura that Aperio would have missed it had she not been looking so closely for anything out of the ordinary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was easy for her to identify the weave of mana to be responsible for what she had felt, Aperio just failed to see who it belonged to. &lt;em&gt;Or is it like the threads binding everything? &lt;/em&gt;It felt similar – not a thin thread that held reality together, but a broader patch that had been sewn on to fix a hole. &lt;em&gt;Is the universe… happy?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The notion felt weird to her. How could the universe itself feel emotions?&lt;em&gt; It's not alive, is it? What did I do? &lt;/em&gt;She shook her head as she beat her wings again, shooting towards the moon with even more speed and causing Caethya to wrap her arms tightly around her. It was something she would investigate once she had dealt with Vigil and his ilk. &lt;em&gt;Once I have more time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was another reason for her to discard the thought of investigation for now. She had felt something shift within the complex Vigil had supposedly built. She could not find any obvious changes, just a feeling at the back of her mind that something had been altered. With another strong beat of her wings, Aperio shot towards what she knew to be an inevitable confrontation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space... the final frontier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 58: Over the Moon</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/105575/</link><description>&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
It's time for another round of emotions are hard™.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya bowed her head slightly as her Goddess entered the Void — a name she was not sure she had heard before or simply &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;because of her connection to Aperio — and closed the portal behind her. There were a great many things she wanted to ask, but her voice was currently struggling to make itself known. Ever since Aperio had revealed what Caethya assumed to be something closer to her true form, she had felt oddly calm. However, it had also reminded her just who — and &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; — her Goddess actually was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her presence alone demanded respect, something that made speaking all the harder for the young Elf. That she towered over everyone present and had wreathed herself in mana also did not help. Finally, being able to feel and &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt; her Goddess growing stronger with each passing moment had removed the last bit of confidence she had with which to ask what was on her mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throughout all of this, the most surprising thing for Caethya — the thing that lingered most in her thoughts — was that her Goddess did not seem to care that her dress was no longer quite as modest as it once had been. &lt;em&gt;Couldn't she just make it fit perfectly again? &lt;/em&gt;She couldn't claim to understand the mind of a Goddess, but in this case Caethya somehow doubted there was much to think about. &lt;em&gt;Not if one wants to continue living, at least. &lt;/em&gt;She was certain that unprompted advances would not go over well with Aperio. &lt;em&gt;How do I even know that?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An ethereal sigh that somehow shook her very soul ripped Caethya out of her thoughts and caused her to look at her Goddess. She had summoned her weapon again, absentmindedly twirling it with one hand. As it whirled through the Void on its revolving path, the blade itself somehow cut through the nothingness that was equivalent to air in this place. The slices it left healed almost instantly, but in that fraction of a second the young Elf glimpsed something she did not understand, and which gave her a headache when she tried to focus on it further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Are you certain that you do not know &lt;/em&gt;where &lt;em&gt;your Dominion is, Ferio?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am sorry mother, but I truly don't know," Ferio replied. "...I could bring us there? Maybe that would help? But, why does it matter &lt;em&gt;where &lt;/em&gt;exactly my Dominion is, anyway?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That the Goddess of Life and Light was the daughter of the All-Mother was not something Caethya had known. Neither had she known the physical appearance of the Goddess, despite having grown up on Spicor and having attended more than one service performed by her church. &lt;em&gt;A statue really doesn't properly convey her presence.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I wish to test a theory, one that — if proven successful — would make our search for Vigil much easier.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Test?" The word had slipped unbidden from Caethya's lips. The idea that &lt;em&gt;the &lt;/em&gt;All-Mother had to test anything seemed somehow wrong to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response to her question, Aperio's eyes settled onto the young Elf. The way the gaze seemed to pierce straight to her core caused Caethya to shrink a little. The tiny wisps of mana that danced around the All-Mother seemed to shine a bit brighter, ready to burn anything they touched. A tiny voice in the back of her mind insisted that her life was now forfeit, to be snuffed out by her Goddess for doubting her abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Yes...test,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said slowly. "&lt;em&gt;There are a few deities that have done something I cannot tolerate; now they are hiding and I do not know where. I have my suspicions, but I will not know for certain without testing it.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya tore her eyes from her Goddess and directed them at the nothing below her feet. &lt;em&gt;Why did I ask? &lt;/em&gt;Having the attention of the All-Mother on her felt good in a way, but did things to her that she did not like. Under the Goddess' gaze, she found she couldn't manage to concentrate on any one thing, and even now that she wasn't under such intense scrutiny there was still a strange feeling lingering within her stomach. It distracted her in ways she had never before experienced, pointing out the way muscles slid around under the skin of her Goddess with every move, or the subtle curves when she took on contrapposto poses. It all culminated in a very foreign feeling, one that brought a joy to her mind but still slipped past her understanding to cause confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Already the load on her mind was heavy, but adding to it was the way she also somehow &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; her Goddess, knew the way she felt. It was affecting her emotions greatly, and she was about to try to grapple with its meaning again when a warm sensation spread across her cheek, ripping her out of her thoughts. Directly in front of her was her Goddess. With no weapon in sight, her gentle, warm hand pulled away from Caethya's cheek to very carefully brush aside a few strands of her hair. The angle of the elbow, the bends in the nimble fingers, all augmented with mana that flowed to her from the Goddess at every touch; it caused shivers to run down her spine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caethya stiffened as she met the eyes of the All-Mother. The pair of irises drew in her attention, seeming to be comprised of flecks of color that slowly danced and revolved around one another and refused to stay still. They were silver, and blue, and all possible shades between, and each time the Goddess blinked they seemed to resolve into a new, fascinating arrangement of color.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Is something wrong?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a softness to Aperio's voice that Caethya had not heard before. With every word she spoke, a wave of calm spread through her entire being, something that had not happened before. There was also a note of concern present that she had not expected. &lt;em&gt;Why would she care? &lt;/em&gt;Of course, she knew that &lt;em&gt;the &lt;/em&gt;All-Mother wouldn't just bless anyone, but neither did Caethya understand why she would be concerned for her. She had always assumed Aperio did not care for the lives of mortals, a belief she would have to rectify.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I-I'm fine," she managed to stammer out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The All-Mother removed her hand at the comment, causing the trickle of mana that flowed from her hand to cease. Caethya let out a small, shaky breath at the disappearance of the feeling that had raced down her spine. &lt;em&gt;What was that?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head slightly as she stood up to her full height again; she had found nothing truly wrong with Caethya's body. The mana that she &lt;em&gt;knew &lt;/em&gt;came from her blessing had been calmer than before, more focused on its endless task of improvement. Still, she doubted that that was the reason for the Elf's reaction. As soon as she had focused on Caethya the woman had locked up, and her cheeks had flushed in embarrassment after she had asked a rather innocent question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Are you sure?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio inquired, ignoring the light giggle from her daughter. "&lt;em&gt;I do not think that is a normal reaction.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think you underestimate the effect you have on people, mother. Especially in your current form."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio frowned and looked down at herself; she could still not see much of a difference besides having gained a bit of height. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps it's the mana and the glow? &lt;/em&gt;A slight, almost imperceptible light &lt;em&gt;did &lt;/em&gt;shine from her skin, but she doubted anyone aside from herself, and perhaps Ferio, would be able to even notice. &lt;em&gt;It's certainly not like what happened when I first drew on my well. &lt;/em&gt;Back then, the light had had a true radiance to it, looking almost otherworldly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a slight rustling, her wings flared out slightly behind her back. They had gained a faint sheen ever since she started drawing on her well again, but not to an extent that Aperio thought would provoke a reaction outside of surprise at the fact that she even had wings to begin with. "&lt;em&gt;What effect do I have on people?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Caethya can probably explain that best herself," Ferio said, with what Aperio would describe as a soft tone of mischief in her voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Elven woman took a slight step back as a bit of redness spread to the tips of her ears. &lt;em&gt;She is easily embarrassed, isn't she? &lt;/em&gt;Luckily, Aperio herself had long gotten rid of her own feelings of embarrassment. &lt;em&gt;Even if the reasons for that are not pleasant. &lt;/em&gt;While she had done so out of necessity before, now she saw no reason to hide herself or be embarrassed about any part of her. &lt;em&gt;But then, not everyone will think like that, will they?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She might have begun to accept what she was and how she would look for the rest of eternity, but the same was likely true for anyone else. &lt;em&gt;I should know that the mind plays tricks on itself. &lt;/em&gt;She might have stayed sane through ordeals that would have broken other people, but that had only served to defer the pain that brought until later. Even if nothing in her past could ever occur again, she still had to come to terms with it like anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Do I scare you?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked. "&lt;em&gt;Or do you simply do not perform well under stress?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, my Goddess," Caethya said, vigorously shaking her head in reply. "I-it's just that whenever I look at you, or you focus your attention on me, I can't think straight. I… I don't know why. It's not panic that hinders me, but a twisting feeling in my stomach. My thoughts run wild, trying to to predict outcomes I somehow &lt;em&gt;know &lt;/em&gt;won't happen. I can also feel what you feel, somehow. Right now, you are like a beacon in the dark that guides me to calm waters through the storming thoughts in my head."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She paused and took a deep breath, seemingly steeling herself for what she was about to say. "I do not know where any of this comes from and yes, it scares me. I &lt;em&gt;know &lt;/em&gt;it's not something you do on purpose, and yet you are the cause. Your presence alone brings me joy. It also fills me with worries I know are not true but that I still cannot banish from my mind."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio cocked her head to the other side. She had not really experienced any emotion that was in any way similar to what her blessed had described. The only thing she could think of was the inexplicable joy she had felt when her memories of Ferio's youth had returned. There was a feeling lingering at the back of her mind, however, one that told her she knew what this was and how she should respond, but it remained out of reach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a sigh, she lowered her head. "&lt;em&gt;You are free to leave if you believe it to be best for you. There is nothing you owe me and I will not force you to follow me.&lt;/em&gt;" She did not like the idea of sending Caethya away, but neither did she want to be the source of her discomfort. Aperio had hoped she could find a friend in the Elf, someone of her kind. &lt;em&gt;At least, what I used to be. &lt;/em&gt;And, perhaps, someone who would treat her like a person instead of worshipping her as the Creator of all they knew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Her leaving won't solve this problem," Ferio said, her mouth turning upwards in a smirk. "And no, I will not tell you what I think is causing it. That's something you have to work out yourself."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outright refusal of answers accompanied by a smirk caused a wave of rage to sweep through Aperio, her Void cloaking everything in darkness for a breath in response. "&lt;em&gt;Fine. The decision is yours Caethya, just know that you are welcome at my side should you choose to stay.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't want to leave," Caethya mumbled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Then you stay,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, startling the Elf. &lt;em&gt;Did she think I did not hear her?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, I will stay. I want to learn from you, grow stronger. Who could be a better teacher than the one who made everything?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio gave a wry smile and a brief nod at Caethya's response. &lt;em&gt;I can think of a few. I hope she can figure out why my presence does that to her. &lt;/em&gt;The winged Goddess herself could only think of a handful of things that could be the cause, most of which she would rather not like to be true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;May we enter your Dominion then, Ferio? I still would like to see it before I waste my time on an experiment that is doomed to fail.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course!" Her daughter's words were accompanied by a notification that invited her to Ferio's Dominion. She promptly accepted. Once she had, she saw the same message she had gotten before entering Natio's Dominion. &lt;em&gt;Am I that far beyond the other Gods and Goddesses? &lt;/em&gt;The obvious answer was yes, a fact she knew to be true but still was not sure she fully liked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a few more moments, Aperio heard Caethya gasp and found herself standing on a red carpet in a brightly lit plaza. What she noticed right after the unnatural softness of the carpet below her bare feet was the warm summer breeze that flowed through her daughter's Dominion, and the fact that the sky was an ever-shifting mirage of yellow, orange, and red. &lt;em&gt;Almost like the sun,&lt;/em&gt; she mused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was what she had hoped would be the case. If her daughter's Dominion was somehow bound to the place the mortals associated her with, Aperio had little doubt that she could find a way from that location into the Dominion. &lt;em&gt;Never thought I would visit the moons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She felt no hesitation or trepidation at the thought of leaving the planet to fly to a celestial body, her instincts instead rejoicing at the idea. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps what is beyond will be similar to my Void? &lt;/em&gt;Looking at the night's sky certainly revealed a similar image.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Thank you, Ferio. This is most insightful.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio raised an eyebrow at her statement. "Already done? What were you looking to find anyway?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;I wanted to know if your Dominion is somehow bound to what the mortals associate you with,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said, gesturing at the sky. "&lt;em&gt;You are known to some as the Goddess of the Sun, are you not?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio gave a light nod. "Yes; it is a source of light and life, both of my Domains." There was a moment of silence before her daughter's eyes widened a little. "Are you sure my Dominion is somehow bound to this sun? I am known in more worlds than just one."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Perhaps not,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio admitted, ignoring the disgusting feeling rising up in her throat. "&lt;em&gt;But to me it &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;feels&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; like the correct solution. Or at least an idea worth investigating.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You want to go to the moons?" Caethya asked. "I have heard that Vigil and Inanis built temples for their most devout followers there. I never believed those rumours, though."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio held out her hands to both Ferio and Caethya. "&lt;em&gt;Why do we not go and see for ourselves?&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 57: Law of The First</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/105574/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head.&lt;em&gt; How strong is the strongest monster here? &lt;/em&gt;Then she dismissed the notification that lingered in front of her. That the System was following rules she had set possibly aeons ago &lt;em&gt;did &lt;/em&gt;bother her, but not as much as she had thought it would. In the end, it was just a reminder that she did not understand her creation. With a silent sigh, she directed her attention at the two mortals who had accepted her offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both of them had fallen to the floor, twisting and turning as more and more mana entered their bodies. Aperio could see the tiny, System-created tears in the fabric of reality that had been made to facilitate the rapid advancement of the two mortals before her, could feel the mana drain from her well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What surprised her most — even though it should not have — was that despite the amounts that flowed from her well to both herself and now the two mortals, the amount residing within barely changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dragon-maid let out a scream that Aperio could not solidly identify as pain or pleasure as the mana guided by the System's hand started to tear into every fibre of their being. It was a process Aperio was intimately familiar with. Not only had she felt it for what had seemed to be eons after her sacrifice, but just moments before she had gone through the same sensations as she destroyed the crystal core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A cracking sound caused Aperio to shift her attention to the horned butler. He had struck at the floor, hitting and breaking one of the few patches uncovered by the grass she had inadvertently created. Much like his Dragon-Elf companion, the mana ravaged through his body; tearing him apart to rebuild him anew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The seams that had come undone to allow the mana from her well into this realm closed silently, and the mortals slowly rolled onto their backs; ending the ordeal as suddenly as it had begun. Neither of them spoke a word, instead taking deep breaths to calm themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #ecf0f1;background-color: #00436e"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;A'ryein | [Dungeon Master] | Level: 2389&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #ecf0f1;background-color: #00436e"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;Den'kelter | [Dungeon Master] | Level: 2389&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I guess that is strong? &lt;/em&gt;It was the highest level she had seen on a mortal, but the monsters she had killed on her way down to the fiftieth floor had reached levels higher than that when they fought her. &lt;em&gt;How does that even work?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She shook her head, dismissing the thought as well as the tiny voice at the back of her mind that wanted her to challenge the newly elevated [Dungeon Masters]. Both of them were on their knees, panting in exhaustion; neither seemed ready to fight. &lt;em&gt;Is levelling up that exhausting? Or is it because they jumped so many at once?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first to get her bearings again was the Dragon-Elf. She righted herself, grabbing her spear for support only for the metal haft of the weapon to break under her grip. Aperio couldn't help but stifle a laugh at the rather astounded expression of the woman. For a brief moment she considered finding a way to make a suitable weapon to give as a gift, but decided against it. The dungeon should be able to make what they needed, after all. &lt;em&gt;If the System did not lie… Can it even lie? &lt;/em&gt;Aperio did not think it could, but then, she also did not know how to check.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite not wanting to spoil what had to have been a rather important moment of their lives, Aperio felt that she had to issue them a warning. "&lt;em&gt;Should I find that you are abusing what you have been given, there &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;will &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;be punishment.&lt;/em&gt;" Replacing the core with two people that would just enslave people again was not what she wanted to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both of them turned to look at her and then each other, the glances seemingly a form of communication that only the two of them understood. Aperio had half expected them to attack her, drunk on the power she inadvertently had given them, but they did not. Instead, both clasped their hands together in front of their chest and bowed deeply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did not speak a word. &lt;em&gt;Do I have to &lt;/em&gt;tell &lt;em&gt;them that they don't have to bow?&lt;/em&gt; As the seconds ticked by, they simply remained in their bowed position, and Aperio decided that it was, once again, up to her to act. "&lt;em&gt;Rise. You do not need to bow.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While they did cease to bow, neither of them looked particularly happy at the idea of not paying their respects. &lt;em&gt;Is that a cultural thing? &lt;/em&gt;It was a definite possibility, as neither she nor Ferio knew what species either of the two belonged to. Aperio also doubted that Caethya would know; according to the woman herself, she had spent most of her life searching for Aperio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Do you feel obligated to bow?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked. "&lt;em&gt;If you have to pay respects to me, do so by not bowing.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think you will have to get used to people paying their respects in some form, mother," Ferio said. "Once they truly know who you are, they will inevitably react with reverence."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone but Aperio herself seemed to agree with the statement as they nodded their assent. The winged Goddess' gaze slid from her daughter to the tiny wisps of mana that still danced around her own body. &lt;em&gt;Those probably don't help… Why is everything I enjoy bound to make my life harder? &lt;/em&gt;Her wings, her voice, even just her presence alone seemed to somehow inform people that she was more than one would assume. Towering over most people and having mana dancing around her physical form was certainly only going to compound the effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet, Aperio did not want to hide what she was or what she could do. &lt;em&gt;Complaining about this is also a bit weird, isn't it? &lt;/em&gt;Most people would probably give everything they had to be in her position. She would too, and in a way, she already had. &lt;em&gt;I &lt;/em&gt;did &lt;em&gt;die for this. Twice, apparently.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How exactly she ended up as a slave was still a mystery to her; the only God she had fought so far had been laughably weak. Her daughter had, in her own words, mentioned that she had been able to fight Vigil and Inanis herself. She had also said that Aperio was now beyond her in terms of raw power. &lt;em&gt;So how did they do it? ...Or did I do it myself? &lt;/em&gt;She &lt;em&gt;had&lt;/em&gt; looked forward to her death, but so far Aperio had always seen it as a way to escape a life of slavery. &lt;em&gt;Why would I choose to die before, then?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it stood, she could not find a reason. She had no desire to leave Ferio alone with deities that despised her simply because they did not like her mother. Nor did she want to give up what she had finally gotten back, even if it filled her life with minor annoyances. With a sigh, she relegated the thoughts to the back of her mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Perhaps you are right. I will still endeavour to make them not do it as, in the end, I am just another person.&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio paused and gestured around the grass-filled room. "&lt;em&gt;I may have made all of this, but that does not mean I want people to stop living their lives to thank me for doing so. As long as I can have my peace, I am happy.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Now I just have to figure out what I need to &lt;/em&gt;do &lt;em&gt;to be at peace. &lt;/em&gt;Removing Vigil, Inanis, and the rest of the uppity deities was certainly a step in the right direction, but Aperio felt like there was most certainly more to it. &lt;em&gt;Like finding something worth fighting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is it so wrong that we want to show our gratitude, Lady Aperio?" Caethya inquired, her voice a lot less steady than her appearance suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio tilted her head at the question. "&lt;em&gt;No, I simply wish to get rid of the notion that it is required.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Is it that important to her?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We do not bow simply because you are stronger than we are, my Goddess," the horned butler — Den'kelter — said. "We bow because we want to show our sincere gratitude. It is the way our ancestors have done it for generations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Where did you two come from, anyway?&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio asked, pressing the feeling of disgust deep down where it belonged. She had a suspicion, but did not want to say it aloud before they had made their own claim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Valley of Everlasting Fire," A'ryein replied. "We served under Fel'Erreyth. He is the strongest Dragon on Verenier. Or, was." Her last words were spoken with a sly smile on her face that caused Aperio to raise an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My deepest apologies, my Goddess. We have failed to make proper introductions." Den'kelter spoke a bit louder than necessary, an obvious attempt to detract attention from the Dragon-maid, who was quickly looking like she might devolve into giggles at any moment. "I am Den'kelter, formerly the head butler of his majesty Fel'Erreyth, [Regent of Procul]. Now I serve The First." His words were accompanied by a deep bow, a motion A'ryein quickly followed before speaking herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My name is A'ryein. I, too, have served his majesty Fel'Erreyth, first as a Lady in Waiting for one of his wives and later as his personal maid under Den'kelter. But now, under the Laws of The First, I serve you; my Lady."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Laws of The First? Did someone make a set of laws around me? &lt;/em&gt;She narrowed her eyes at the thought. &lt;em&gt;So people do remember me, or am I misunderstanding this? &lt;/em&gt;It also led to another question, one that she could potentially even get an answer to. "&lt;em&gt;Why are you so ready to discard your old liege? And what does this 'Regent of Procul' have to do with dungeons?&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Since when does an entire continent have a Regent, anyway?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The set of questions seemed to confuse everyone but Ferio. Instead of being surprised that her mother did not know everything, she too seemed eager for an answer. &lt;em&gt;Well, she did not know what they were either. Are they Dragons that changed their form? Can they even do that? ...If not, what exactly would a Dragon need a butler or maid for? Scale polishing?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Laws of The First, simply put, state that we are to follow The First. The Strongest. The one who, through the very might of their being, brought forth life from nothing. You have declared yourself the Origin of all Creation, and your very words resonated within my soul. I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt;, without a doubt, that they are true. Even if they were not, you bestowed upon us strength — strength that rivals even that of our old liege — in a gesture that seemed effortless. Like it was nothing. That, alone, makes you more deserving of our devotion." Den'kelter's voice was bordering on reverent, and it was only now that he truly looked at Aperio. "I may not be a Dragon myself, and A'ryein may only carry a portion of her mother's heritage, but we have, since time immemorial, followed the same laws as our ancestors."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The notion that she might not have spoken the truth about her nature caused a bit of anger to boil up in the winged Goddess. She pushed it down of course, but it was still there at the back of her mind, demanding she punish the mortal in front of her. &lt;em&gt;Annoying. &lt;/em&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Following someone just because they are strong is not always a good idea. I am also not looking to found a new religion.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am sorry, my Lady, but I don't think even you could prevent that by simply asking," A'ryein said. "If you do not directly prohibit what people do, they will start to worship you. It is simply a matter of time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She is right, mother," Ferio agreed. "And you have made it quite clear that you dislike anything that takes away the freedom of others."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Perhaps you are correct. However, that does not mean I have to like it.&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio sighed, ignoring how the breeze flowing through the room had gotten colder at her exasperated gesture. "&lt;em&gt;That also does not answer why you have been summoned here, though.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fel'Erreyth rules from the Heart of Fire, a dungeon of his own," A'ryein said. "Why or how it has chosen him, I do not know. Much like the The Laws of the First, it is a tradition that has been at the core of the culture of Procul. Though it was not always a dungeon that chose the next Regent, it was always something that has been touched by the mana of Origin. Touched by you, my Lady."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;So, the dungeon called for help? Why?&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;How?&lt;/em&gt; She had not noticed anything akin to a call for help. Especially one to another continent. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps I just don't know where to look?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, Fel'Erreyth orded us to verify a claim made by the Heart of Fire. We were simply the closest reliable members of his court he could send. That we would meet The First was not something we anticipated."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;It seems I will have to pay this Fel'Erreyth a visit sometime soon,&lt;/em&gt;" Aperio said with a shake of her head. "&lt;em&gt;When I do so, I would be delighted to have you as my guides. For now, however, I have done what I came here to do. You may do with this dungeon what you wish as long as you abstain from slavery and other vile acts. I will not tolerate such abuse of my gifts.&lt;/em&gt;" &lt;em&gt;Even if I did not mean to give some of them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had tried to give her voice a bit of finality, make it clear she would not accept her gifts being abused. Judging by how the two newly appointed [Dungeon Masters] bowed, she seemed to have made her point clear. &lt;em&gt;Towering over them and being wreathed in my own mana probably helps, too.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Aperio had no mirror handy with which to take a look at herself, she had taken a moment to inspect the physical changes drawing on her well brought through her aura. Besides being taller and having wisps of her mana float around her, Aperio could not really see a difference. &lt;em&gt;Perhaps a mortal sees it differently?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a shake of her head, she turned her attention towards Caethya and her daughter. For a moment she considered reaching out with her mind to convey her idea, but decided against it. Ferio might be able to take her continued barrage of thoughts, but she was not so sure about Caethya. She had been stronger than most anyone Aperio had seen thus far, but the reaction she had had to her few attempts at mental communication had not been promising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a private talk via thoughts was out of the question for the moment, Aperio simply opened a portal to her Void with a wave of her hand. Den'kelter and A'ryein might have said they were devoted to her, but that did not mean she trusted them. &lt;em&gt;Trust requires action, not words.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither of her companions needed further encouragement to step into her Void, Caethya even looking eager to go back to her Goddess' Dominion. Aperio gave her two newest followers a last look before stepping through the portal as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Das some old laws, my dudes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Forgotten: Crusade – Chapter 56: Decisions Overseen</title><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/read/28882-forgotten/chapter/100284/</link><description>&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
Welcome to Arc 3: Crusade. Same as last time, it's still part of 'Book 1' and thefore continues the chapter count.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio dismissed the notifications with a thought before she set her eyes upon Caethya. Her first choice for someone to look over the dungeon was either her or Laelia, but she somehow doubted either of them would want to do so. &lt;i&gt;Perhaps they shouldn't. &lt;/i&gt;She still liked the idea of watching them ascend to Godhood, something an appointment as Overseer for a dungeon would probably slow down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, she sent a small thought to the one she had blessed. Aperio had hoped that, perhaps, the most recent change would have lessened the pain Caethya would feel upon her mental query, but the slight stagger and twisted face spoke of the opposite. After taking a moment to get her bearings again, Caethya gently shook her head and denied the offer as Aperio had already expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had also briefly considered Maria for the position of Overseer, but that thought, too, had been quickly discarded. &lt;i&gt;She is too young. And she has not reached out since I left their estate. &lt;/i&gt;The girl knew her name, could have prayed to Aperio to talk or make a request, but there had been only silence. &lt;i&gt;Perhaps she is mad at me after all? &lt;/i&gt;She put visiting the Terenyk estate back on her mental to-do list. &lt;i&gt;After I've sorted this. &lt;/i&gt;If she couldn't find a willing mortal, she could still simply assume the role herself. &lt;i&gt;Now how to ask Laelia...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that thought, Aperio focused on her aura, letting her senses fly upwards through the dungeon. She briefly noted that the monsters all seemed to be frozen in place, something the adventurers she saw gleefully took advantage of. The village on the fiftieth floor was filled with a flurry of activity, people preparing for something that would never come. Their frantic actions made Aperio question how they had perceived the death of the dungeon. For her it was a like a shudder had run through reality itself, but something in the back of her mind told her that the mortals would not perceive it like she did. &lt;i&gt;How could they? &lt;/i&gt;Her connection to the universe was vastly different from theirs, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She let her senses expand past the village and the rest of the dungeon, finding the [Grandmaster] in the office of the local guildmaster. Focusing on the pair caused her to hear their voices, a faint whisper that Aperio &lt;i&gt;knew&lt;/i&gt; she could pull on to find out more. It was something she would have considered if the [Grandmaster] hadn't whipped her head around and stared in her direction. There was a brief moment of confusion before she turned back to the guildmaster to continue their talk, seemingly unconcerned that Aperio could be listening in. &lt;i&gt;Does she even know it was me?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a shake of her head, the winged Goddess directed her attention towards the house of healing her paladin resided in. She knew she could stretch her senses even further, that her aura's reach was not limited to the town or even the continent, and yet she did not want to see all there was through her mana's touch. She might have begun to truly accept what she was, but that did not mean she would immediately become Magistrate of all that there was. Aperio wanted to discover what she had made, see it with her own eyes. &lt;i&gt;Perhaps find something that offers a challenge.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finding Laelia was a simple task. Her paladin was a proverbial beacon of mana when compared to those surrounding her. Aperio was certain that there was more mana than before in the Human's body. Even if the increase wasn't that much, it was still there. Very carefully, she nudged her mana towards the woman, trying to convey her thoughts as gently as she could.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laelia tensed up as soon as the mana touched her, reaching for the sword at her hip before she realised who was invading her mind. Instead of drawing her weapon, she lowered herself to her knees and directed her gaze towards the ceiling, a motion Aperio found highly amusing and wholly unnecessary. She told Laelia as much, the words of her Goddess causing the paladin to jump to her feet and start a flurry of mental apologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio dismissed her concern, instead offering her the position as Overseer over the newly re-created dungeon and, perhaps more importantly, asking why she was not showing any signs of pain. Laelia was quick to deny the offer, stating that she would rather follow her Goddess more closely, but only replied with the mental equivalent of a shrug to the question of feeling pain. According to Laelia, getting a headache was a small price to pay to talk to her Goddess, a mentality Aperio was not quite sure she shared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having eliminated her paladin from the list of Overseer candidates, Aperio turned to face the two people the now-dead core had summoned. As no-one else was accepting the opportunity, she wanted to extend the offer to them. &lt;i&gt;As a test, perhaps. &lt;/i&gt;Neither of them had behaved improperly, simply doing what they were asked — or possibly forced — to do. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They shrunk under her gaze, seemingly intimidated by her imposing stature and the wisps of silver and blue that still floated around her. &lt;i&gt;And probably because I killed the thing that summoned them. &lt;/i&gt;She felt no remorse for her actions, however; the core had withheld something it had no right to. It had also forced hapless Souls into its service, something that would change once she had appointed a replacement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or, perhaps, they could feel the massive amounts of mana that she had drawn from her well and that still coursed through her body. She did not want to stop at the moment, the feeling of power flowing through her a sensation she had not really known she had missed. Neither did she need to, as Ferio was not asking her to cease her actions, nor was she drawing from her well in anger. Right now she did so simply because she enjoyed it, much like some people would perhaps enjoy a fine wine. &lt;i&gt;Just that this is actually useful. &lt;/i&gt;Drinking wine would probably not make one stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She took a step towards the pair, the fissures that formed under her feet glowing and crackling with her mana. Both of them tried to make themselves even smaller at her approach, tried to hide from the being that had destroyed a dungeon core for good. Aperio stopped just out of arm's reach of the scared duo. &lt;i&gt;Not that I have to be close to reach anything.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;i&gt;I have an offer for you,&lt;/i&gt;" Aperio said, her voice sounding more ethereal than ever. &lt;i&gt;Soon it sounds like I will whisper directly into their brain… Maybe they will stop wincing when I speak, then? Or will my voice go back to normal as soon as I stop drawing from my well? &lt;/i&gt;She doubted that would be the case. The changes brought by the mana she drew were permanent, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was no reply, at least not a verbal one. The two of them just looked at her before quickly averting their gaze again. &lt;i&gt;Do I look scary to them? &lt;/i&gt;Aperio did not think that would be the case, she wasn't angry and the tiny wisps and arcs of mana that darted around her looked more otherworldly than scary. &lt;i&gt;Or do they think they are not worthy to lay their eyes upon a Goddess?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To her that was a silly notion but then, she also &lt;i&gt;was &lt;/i&gt;a Goddess. &lt;i&gt;The Goddess. &lt;/i&gt;With a shake of her head, she continued her one-sided conversation. "&lt;i&gt;If you wish to oversee this dungeon, I am willing to offer you two a chance to prove that you are more than the mouthpiece of an abomination.&lt;/i&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both of their heads turned ever so slowly in her direction, this time maintaining their gaze after a moment had passed. Neither of them seemed to really believe what she had said, their suspicion clear on their face as well as practically flowing off of them. Aperio tilted her head at the sensation. She did not share a bond with them like she did with Caethya or Maria and had not expected to gain the same insight into someone's feelings. &lt;i&gt;Is it because of the influx of mana, or because I retrieved some of my memories? &lt;/i&gt;With every moment that passed, what she had reclaimed from the core became clearer in her head, new — &lt;i&gt;Old? —&lt;/i&gt; information surfacing in her mind. That some of those memories would influence her subconscious and her perception of the world and its people was only to be expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Y-You are offering us control over this dungeon?" the horned butler asked, seemingly not quite believing his ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;i&gt;Yes.&lt;/i&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How?" Aperio had not expected the Dragon-Elf to speak, as she had not made any move to do so before. In response to her question, Aperio focused on the feeling at the back of her mind she knew to be the System. Its request for her to designate an Overseer for the dungeon was still there and, with a thought, Aperio directed it at the pair in front of her. She could see the notifications form in front of them, how the threads of reality changed ever so slightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both of them looked at the window that had appeared before them, reading through the rather extensive list that had presented itself. Aperio, too, took a look at it through her aura but quickly lost interest. It was simply a collection of the functions they would have access to if they accepted the title of 'Dungeon Master', none of which was of much interest to the winged Goddess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had no desire to create a new monster or change how the dungeon looked, neither did she care about what the reward for beating it would be. The only things of note to her were a pair of warnings. One informed them that they could still die and that whoever killed them could assume their role or destroy the dungeon, while the other stated that Aperio may change whatever she wished at any time. &lt;i&gt;Why is that even in there? Isn't that true for all that exists?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was no answer to her unspoken question, neither her memory or the System providing anything that would hint as to why this disclaimer was there. With a slight sigh, Aperio turned around and approached her daughter again, letting the Dragon-Elf and horned butler decide their future in peace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio looked at her mother with a slight smile on her face, obviously happy that she had regained at least a part of her memories. Aperio herself was not quite sure what she actually wanted to do now. She still had to take care of the other deities that had dared to go against her but, right now, all the All-Mother wanted to do was spend time with her daughter. &lt;i&gt;But, what should we do?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio couldn't claim to know what families were supposed to do. The Emperor's family spent most of their time scheming against one another, something she would hope Ferio would not do. The winged Goddess herself wanted to explore the world she had made and had spent most of her life on. &lt;i&gt;Perhaps even other worlds. &lt;/i&gt;But she did not know if Ferio could so simply leave this plane of existence, or even if she had any desire to do so. &lt;i&gt;Are the other worlds even on another plane?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a slight shake of her head, she pushed the thoughts to the back of her mind. For now she would have to find a way to deal with Vigil, Inanis, and whoever they had managed to turn against her. She had an idea where she might find an inspirational hint towards infiltrating the Dominions of Vigil and Inanis. It was perhaps a silly idea, but in Aperio's mind there had to be a reason why the two deities were connected to the moons. To know if her initial idea was useless, all she needed was to pose a simple question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;i&gt;Do you know &lt;/i&gt;where&lt;i&gt; your Dominion is, Ferio?&lt;/i&gt;" The mention of her daughter's name caused the maybe-overseers to jerk their heads away from the System-provided window to look at the pair of Goddesses. Aperio chose to ignore them, focusing on Ferio instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter seemed surprised at the question, tilting her head slightly to the side. &lt;i&gt;Did she get that from me? &lt;/i&gt;"I don't really know? I never really thought about &lt;i&gt;where &lt;/i&gt;it would be because I had always assumed it would be in another realm like your Void. Or are you telling me that that is not the case?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;i&gt;I simply had an idea that would perhaps help with finding a way into Vigil's Dominion," &lt;/i&gt;Aperio replied. "&lt;i&gt;I had hoped you could provide a bit more insight, but it would appear I will have to go myself to see if it will work.&lt;/i&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry," Ferio mumbled, lowering her head slightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;i&gt;For what? You do not have to know everything.&lt;/i&gt;" &lt;i&gt;I have to.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just want to be able to help you; be useful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aperio cocked her head to the side at the statement. "&lt;i&gt;You have already done more for me than anyone else, it is not your duty to solve my problems.&lt;/i&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only reply the winged Goddess got was an incoherent mumble as Ferio continued to stare at her feet. &lt;i&gt;Did I do something wrong? &lt;/i&gt;She stretched out her arm and gently brushed her hand over her daughter's hair, a motion she hoped would soothe Ferio. Aperio did not know if it would, but it simply felt like the right thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through her aura she saw Caethya's eyes darting between herself and Ferio and the two summoned people, a confused look on her face. It was clear that she wanted to say something, perhaps ask why Aperio was talking about rather private matters in front of strangers. Aperio chose to ignore her much like she did the other two in the room. Her attention's current focus was on figuring out what exactly was wrong with her daughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferio had not behaved like this since their reunion and neither could she find anything in her newly reacquired memory that would help. Then, a new notification materialized in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="tbl_of"&gt;
&lt;table style="width: 100%;border-style: solid;border-color: #ecf0f1;background-color: #00436e"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;A'ryein and Den'kelter have accepted the position of 'Overseer' over the dungeon designated 'Principle of Creation'.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff"&gt;In accordance with established rules as set forth by the Creator, the assigned Overseers will be elevated to match the current strongest monster residing in the designated area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wi_authornotes"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class="p-avatar-wrap"&gt;&lt;a class="avatar has-link" href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;&lt;img alt="" id="acc_ava_change profile" src="https://cdn.scribblehub.com/avatar/s/1/ava_4221_1563028868.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="an_username"&gt;&lt;a href="/profile/4221/gamingwolf/"&gt;GamingWolf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="wi_authornotes_body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like the story, do leave a rating. If you really like it, please write a review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to chat? Join the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/ZAZN84P" rel="nofollow"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Want to read ahead? Check out the &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/GamingWolfie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false" /><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel><link>https://www.scribblehub.com/favicon.ico</link><description>Forgotten</description></rss>