<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>He Who Fights With Monsters</title><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 240: The Boss Comes to Town</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/503180</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Humphrey swung his arms inward, brutally clapping his hands into either side of the cultist vampire's head. It relinquished its bite on Neil's neck, rearing back to let out an alien screech from its inhuman mouth. His jaw unhinged in macabre mockery of the formerly human anatomy. The mouth no longer had teeth, just bare gums and a pair of hairy barbs, growing awkwardly out from the roof of the mouth. They bristled, wet with saliva and Neil's blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey, gripped the vampire by the hair and smashed its head into the stone platform until the body stopped squirming. It was the last of the bizarrely warped adventurers turned inhuman minion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think I got a big dose of that blood curse," Neil said, sounding woozy. He cast a spell on himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Imbue with life."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clear green light glow around his hand, then shot into his neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Life Bolt] (Renewal)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (healing)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (11%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Delivers life energy though a projectile, giving a small burst of instantaneous healing. Damages certain targets that are inimical to life force, such as most forms of undead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Bestows a mild, ongoing healing effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Neil's bread and butter healing spell, which could also be used as a weapon against most forms of undead. He had never actually used it for that, with undead being rare in Greenstone because of the life energy flowing down the Mistrun River. Vampires were no better, with the blood magic flooding their bodies that produced a warped facsimile of life. They were the one form of undead for whom, healing magic was fully effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Give me a second and I'll clear that curse, Neil," Jason said. "I'm a little tied up, right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was stuck to the platform by a blanket of sticky webbing. Gordon was cutting him loose with his four force beams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My new armour is definitely a step up," Jason said as he waited. "That resistance to adhesive effects on the old one would have been handy, though."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was," Sophie said. She was still using iron-rank armour made primarily, as Jason's had been, of trap weaver leather. "They were spraying that webbing everywhere, like giant nets. I couldn't dodge it all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Clive," Belinda said. "You told us they would be easier to fight after being turned into vampires."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And he was right," Humphrey said. "A few strange spider powers are no compensation for a full suite of bronze-rank abilities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Their transformation was more extreme than I anticipated," Clive acknowledged. "From what I've read about blood weavers, they almost always leave intelligent victims largely intact. They recognise that a high-intelligence minion is worth more than another physically powerful blood puppet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not sure high-intelligence was an issue," Neil said. "They joined a cult and agreed to come here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; "Fair point," Clive conceded. "Blood weavers can put essence users through a stronger transformation, as we saw here, but it destroys the mind. You saw the animalistic way they fought."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After creepily staring at them from the jungle line, the vampire cultists had recklessly hurled themselves into the team. Their reckless attacks led to the team putting them down in short order, although not before they penetrated the team's backline. Clive had displayed some unexpectedly solid staff fighting, combining strikes and blocks with blasts of magic. Belinda had used an escape ability but Neil had been latched onto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gordon finished cutting Jason free and he immediately started purging the team of afflictions, starting with Neil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; "That was some good work with the staff," Sophie told Clive. "You've been practising with Humphrey?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have," Clive said. "He told me that I needed to train for the fight I don't want, along with the one I do. It would appear he was right."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is it just me," Jason asked, "or was that a bit anti-climactic, after all this time. We came here after the cultists and they turn out to be just more monsters. I mean, after the whole vampire monster army thing, they were just a few more vampires."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They seemed more than threatening enough to me," Neil said, then hit himself with another life bolt spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry they got past me," Sophie apologised to Neil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As am I," Humphrey said. "I don't think anyone expected that suicide rush. Jason was right, I think. After all the build up, the cultists didn't amount to much."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; "We need to find where they were staying," Clive said. "My guess would be somewhere in the centre of the city, past the thickest jungle. That's probably where the blood weaver found them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So that's where we'll probably find it," Belinda said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It could be," Clive said. "I think it might have run, though. I suspect it realised that we're strong enough to kill it and threw minions at us to buy time. It probably chose a handful that were strong and mobile and abandoned the area with them while we were chewing through the fodder."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We'll take a break," Humphrey said. "Then we'll loot the monsters, burn the cultists and get on to the middle of the city. We'll find where the cultists were staying before the blood weaver came along and then, what they were up to."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That was a huge haul," Neil said. "Three blood essences and a dark essence. If we find a mouth essence somewhere, we can recreate Jason's combination."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were discussing the loot as they made their way through the still-deserted jungle. Every monster for a wide area had either been taken over by the blood weaver and killed by the team or fled to avoid that fate. They were doubling up on Shade's three mantis beetle forms, which excelled at cutting a path through the thick scrub. Humphrey with Jason, Neil with Clive and Sophie with Belinda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's not very mature, Neil," Jason said. "You shouldn't make fun of people like that. It's why people like me more than you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, that's because you always bring sandwiches," Sophie said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sandwiches," Jason said haughtily, "are the garnish on a prime slab of perfectly pan-seared rakish charm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Getting that myriad essence was the big winner," Clive said. "A legendary essence, and one of the better ones. We could buy the materials to rank every familiar on the team to silver and still have money left over."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll be happy to get mine to bronze," Belinda said. "I'd also like to get closer to them. How do you do it, Jason? You get along so well with your familiars, but mine are so alien."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Colin and Gordon aren't exactly everyday folk, either," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then what's the secret?" Belinda asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They're just people," Jason said. "Treat them that way. Yes, they're a little odd to our sensibilities, but if it can think, it's a person. That's the same, whether you're talking about a familiar or a god. Even a monster, although that's a tragic one. Imagine coming into being knowing that you have a terminal condition, and your options are get killed by an adventurer or go insane, kill a bunch of people yourself and die."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gods aren't people," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's a bit rude," Jason said. "You'll have to atone for that one."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gods are above people," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is no above people, Humphrey. There's just people. Give them enough power and they get a bit weird, but still people."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You seem very confident for someone who didn't believe in gods a year ago," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But I believed in people. It just turns out that some of them are magic. Like us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You do realise that people have different stations in life, right?" Neil asked. "A king is not the same as a pauper."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course not," Jason said. "The king inherits a hat and a chair, where the pauper's lucky to get the hat. Better hat, though. What kind of idiot thinks a metal hat with no top is a great idea. The same guy who thinks monarchy makes sense, I guess."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How can you possibly think that gods are just people?" Neil asked. "You think you can just stand before a god and start mouthing off? I've been in the presence of gods. Just being near them was like standing under a waterfall."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"From what I've heard, he did exactly that," Clive said. "I talked to a lot of people after the last excursion into this astral space. A lot of them were talking about the gods showing up and the lunatic talking to them like they were random people off the street."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They are random people," Jason said. "A bit showy, but nice enough. They like to make something of a spectacle of themselves, though."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group all turned to stare at Jason. Humphrey had to crane his neck from where he was sitting in front of Jason on the mantis beetle to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What?" Jason asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They passed through the rest of the thick jungle without being accosted by monsters. If any were around, they were apparently smart enough to stay well clear of the ones responsible for getting rid of the rest. The shattered and scattered ruins, buried in jungle, gave way to fully intact buildings in startlingly short order. The line of demarcation was so stark that it reminded Jason of the Vane estate, where the lush gardens met the desert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team made a direct path for the very centre of the city and the large square containing the Order of the Reaper's trial tower. As they moved through the buildings, they started to notice fragments of unusual magic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everyone else is sensing that, right?" Belinda asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yep."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yeah."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gods damned magic," Sophie muttered. "No."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team arrested their progress to investigate. The magic was weak enough that it was a curiosity, rather than a threat. It was chaotic, patchy and feeble. They found a fragment of sheared steel, jammed into a brick wall by some tremendous force. Clive took out some tools and began examining it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I should look at more," he said as he finished up. At his direction, the team sought out locations from which the strange, scattered magic was emanating. One was a cushion that had somehow buried itself in a wall as forcefully as the metal shard had. Another was a round indentation containing a dark, crystalline powder. After examining the powder for some time, Clive rubbed some between his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a ground-down awakening stone," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I didn't realise you could do that," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can't," Clive said. "Every attempt to alter the form an awakening stone has either done nothing or triggered it into returning to a raw magic state. Rainbow smoke."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is the result of the Reaper's power," Shade said. "I can sense it because it is the same as my own power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You know what happened here?" Clive asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I suspect these fragments are the remnants of the tower's treasure stores. I have previously postulated that the dimensional spaces in which those stores were kept would collapse once the trials came to an end and the power controlling them was withdrawn. My guess would be a mana implosion affected by the protective measures put in place by the order triggered an unexpectedly destructive reaction. There is likely less treasure to find that I originally intimated."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think he's right," Clive said. "The traces of astral magic on everything I've looked at are chaotic and unengineered. These fragments don't do anything except throw off some residual magic. It speaks more to un uncontrolled phenomena, like a dimensional explosion."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is this residual magic a threat to us?" Humphrey asked. "It's weak here, but will there be more dangerous patches?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a conglomeration of random dimensional energies," Clive said, "blasted into a chaotic mess and mixed with the power of a being who could, if it wanted, use that power to assassinate the universe. So… maybe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think we should give Clive some space," Jason said. "Leave him to figure things out without having to answer any questions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive flashed Jason a grateful look as Jason waved the rest of the team away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This will be the final ascension ceremony," Zato told Dougall. "The last of your essence abilities will be gone, but you will cross the threshold of silver-rank today. You can anticipate being filled with something new and far greater."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you, Master Zato," Dougall said. "I know I came to the cult under slightly different circumstances than most, but I am profoundly grateful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were walking through the grounds of the ruined Vane estate, entering what had once been a small wood but now was nothing but dead and withered trees. They reached a space where five equidistant trees stood at the points of a pentagram, part of a magical diagram laid out between them with bricks. The trees could barely be called that anymore, stripped of their branches and bark and sculpted into wooden obelisks. Runes ran down their sides, alternately made from hammered-in steel or engraved directly into of the wood and stained the rusty colour of dried blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is the place," Zato said. Timos had been waiting for them, head hidden within a voluminous ritual robe. He held out robes for Zato and Dougall. Zato gave Dougall an encouraging smile as they slipped them on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ritual took place with Dougall in the middle of the circle, Zato and Timos on opposite sides. On the robes of all three men, magical sigils lit up with power. There was a gathering of energy as the pair conducted an extended chant. Soon, Dougall felt a power rising up from within. The power surged through him, cleansing and changing. He crossed the threshold into silver and impurities started seeping through his pores, leaving him covered in filth. He was panting and tired, but grinning fiercely as he revelled in the sense of power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timos stepped forward with a bottle of crystal wash, ignoring the smell. Dougall stripped off the robes and ruined clothes before cleaning himself off, the filth on his skin and the fallen-out hair sloughing away. Afterwards, Timos lead him to where he had fresh clothes folded neatly in a bag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Dougall changed, he revelled in the sensation of his new power. He could no longer sense his essences, but compared to the power he could feel it was no loss. He could even feel more potential power, hidden deep within his soul. It was laying untapped, right next to the… star seed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was gripped by a sudden sense of dread; the realisation that the power inside him did not belong to him a all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As if it were germinating, he felt power swell out from the star seed. It kept coming and coming; an alien might flooding out of his own soul to fill the channels of power that months of ritual treatments had installed in his body. He went cold with fear and an absolute certainty that his soul was no longer his own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dougall's last free thought was rage at Zato for his betrayal. He opened his mouth to yell but was choked off as the new power initiated a new, sweeping change. Flesh rippled, but not with organic fluidity. It was like his flesh was comprised of tiny, tiny blocks, undergoing some kind of shift. The strange rippling swept his whole body before settling again,  leave no lingering indication of a body anything but organic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His body went limp, standing like a puppet hanging loose from a string. Dougall stood up straight, his expression was blank, his eyes plain, grey orbs. He looked at the clothes half put-on and finished dressing. Zato and Timos kneeled to the ground, heads bowed, as Dougall finished and looked over his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lord Builder," Zato greeted, not looking up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This vessel is adequate," the Builder, now occupying Dougall's body said. "If I use more than silver-rank power it will break down immediately, but the vessel was prepared efficiently. With care, it will last some time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The next vessel is already at a late stage of preparation, Lord Builder," Zato said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I know," the Builder said. "I am in your soul. There is nothing you can hide from me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, Lord Builder."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Builder walked over to where Zato was kneeling, head down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There have been a cavalcade of failures here," the builder said. "You made the correct choice in continuing the work, but you made it out of fear. Fear of the consequences of failure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We did, Lord Builder," Zato admitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Builder was silent for a long time. Zato could see from his feet that he hadn't moved. Timos couldn't see him at all, not daring to raise his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your motivations are acceptable," the Builder said finally. "The consequences of failure are there to spur desirable behaviour, after all, which is what they have done. Stand, both of you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cultists stood, but kept their eyes lowered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I know all that has transpired," the Builder said. "I am impressed with how the pair of you have handled dire circumstances placed upon you by the failures of others. Continuing the work instead of drawing back and regrouping was the right choice. Preparing a vessel that I might direct you now, instead of waiting for a success to buffer the failures here was likewise a correct choice. The intrusion of this astral space is more crucial than you realise."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lord Builder?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You had not yet been made privy to the true purpose of the astral space we are about to claim. It is one of a small number on this world that are more important than the others. The original intention was for a clockwork king to lead this expedition. In the wake of the failed summoning, the leadership here made a sequence of costly mistakes. This included raising our profile to the point that I was no longer able to move significant resources here without alerting the natives to the importance of the task now ahead of you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will do what we can with what we have, Lord Builder," Zato said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As you have been doing. I am satisfied that you have both risen to the stations thrust upon you by the inadequacies of those the led before you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you, Lord Builder," both men said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This astral space was something taken from me in the past," the builder said. "The time has come to reclaim it. There are tools within that will greatly assist our work on this world."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What would you have us do, Lord Builder?" Zato asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For now, continue as you have been. First, we enter the astral space. Then we prepare to bring my world engineers here. Your remaining ritualists are mediocre, but under my direction they will be sufficient. Opening those gates will be wildly destructive, but you knew this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, Lord Builder," Zato said. "I was told that claiming the astral space would be unusually destructive, but not why."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is hard to interrogate our people, but not impossible," the Builder said. "For this reason, the secret was restricted to the leadership. You will understand the full purpose soon enough."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you, Lord Builder. As you obviously know, the Rejector is already in the astral space. Once we are there, I will see to it that the Rejector is found and killed, should he still be alive on our arrival."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No," the Builder said. "The Rejector and I have unfinished business. You will bring him to me alive."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">503180</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 23:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 239: The Most Dangerous Thing in the Dark</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/502704</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Behind his front-line team members, Jason injuries swiftly started healing over. The recovery power he gained from devouring vampiric curses combined with the healing Colin provided to close his wounds without requiring intervention from Neil. In most cases, his armour had mitigated the bulk of the damage, so here were no individual injuries that were egregious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason did not immediately turn his attention to the team. First, he looked out at the amassing monsters, picking out the sturdier bronze-rank one. His eyes sought out those who were affected by his afflictions but tough enough that they were still far from being overcome. He cast inexorable doom on them, one after the other, to start churning out the automatic afflictions that would stack his amulet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Inexorable Doom] (Doom)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (curse)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Moderate mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (09%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Periodically applies an additional instance of each stacking curse, disease, poison or unholy affliction the target is suffering from. This is a curse effect. This effect cannot be cleansed while any other curse or any disease, poison or unholy affliction is in effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Inflicts or refreshes the [Inescapable] affliction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Inescapable] (affliction, magic): Subject cannot be affected by teleport or non-damaging dimension effects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;With his afflictions ticking up, Jason turned his attention to the team. Sophie was relatively undamaged, the advantage of being an evasive-type defender. Holding out against numbers was not her strong suit, however, and her own armour was marked with the rents of bite and claw. Jason used his feast of absolution power to absorb the vampiric blood curse from her and stack his own healing in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others holding the line were Humphrey, Neil's golem and Stash, guarding their rear from behind the platform at the back. He was still in the shape of the massive hydra from which Jason had looted his whip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The golem was immune to the vampire's curse and didn't require Jason's attention. It had suffered enough damage to be forced into its chrysalis state, but that was not enough to let the enemy past the now bronze-rank summon. The crystalline cocoon was no longer the inert mass it had been in the past. It was now a rune-covered obelisk of crystal, rapid-firing crystal spikes into the crowd. Anything that got close was struck by crystal spears, that shot out to strike a target, then remained bristling from the obelisk like diamond pikes. Given the mass of monsters trying to push past, it had swiftly transitioned from obelisk to tall, diamond echidna, covered in bloody spines. The chrysalis stage, as it turned out, was proving a better blocker than the golem had before entering it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey was standing strong against the horde, his strength and fortitude an impassable bulwark as his sword threshed the monsters before him like an apocalyptic farming implement. His armour was much stronger than Sophie's but he had, nonetheless, suffered injuries as he put himself fearless forward. Neil's healing was on top of the injuries, but he had left the afflictions for Jason to drink up, which he did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That left Stash, who was faring the worst of all, being off the platform and essentially holding the rear alone. Neil had been helping, but the lack of the hydra's regenerative powers was obvious, and the large size of the hydra form made it easy to swarm. Jason drained the afflictions from Stash, then called out to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm coming in, Stash!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stash stilled his body for a moment, not that the hydra form was agile. Jason jumped directly onto his back, behind the five, long hydra necks, and slapped a hand onto one of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have bestowed all instances of [Guardian's Blessing] to a party member's familiar, [Velitraxistaasch].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason made use of his bronze rank agility, the equal of any circus acrobat, and back-flipped off stash and back to the platform. His cloak didn't entangle him as he could make it incorporeal at will and have it drift right through his body to settle, shrouding his flipping form in shadow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; "Is anyone recording this fight?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We're a little busy, Jason," Clive admonished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Right, yep."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason cast a gaze over the situation around Stash. The multi-headed hydra form was good at picking off the weaker monsters quickly and Humphrey's familiars were also working that rear side of the battle. They likewise went for the weaker ones, flying in and snatching them in their talons before carrying them into the air. While their griffin forms were powerful and their dragon-bone bodies not subject to vampiric powers, they did not risk alighting amongst the massing horde. They would peck the monster to death in the air, or carry them high enough that the subsequent drop did the job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, there was a growing percentage of bronze-rank and tougher iron-rank monsters surrounding Stash, increasingly putting him under pressure. Jason began his intervention, throwing out quick spells at the monsters that presented the biggest threats. He didn't have a lot of afflictions on them yet, but he started with inexorable doom in preparation and followed up with a blood spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Haemorrhage] (Blood)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (wounding, unholy, blood)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Moderate mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (06%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Inflicts or refreshes the [Bleeding] and [Sacrificial Victim] afflictions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Inflicts the [Necrotoxin] affliction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Bleeding] (affliction, wounding, blood): Deals ongoing damage by causing or increasing blood loss. As a wounding effect, this condition absorbs and negates an amount of incoming healing, after which this affliction immediately ends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Sacrificial Victim] (affliction, unholy): Any drain attacks or blood afflictions suffered have increased effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Necrotoxin] (affliction, poison, stacking): Inflicts ongoing necrotic damage until poison is cleansed. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;He went through the strongest enemies, dropping the two-spell combination on each. When he was happy with his coverage, he leapt into the fray once more, wading though the monsters to support Stash. He went after the monsters he had thrown spells on, one to the next. He would hit each of them just once, laying on afflictions with his dagger before moving on. His whip he continued to thrash in the direction of the weaker enemies, using it to make space as best he could in the press of monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time he was done, so many afflictions were ticking over that his amulet accrued blessings faster than the hits he was taking could consume them. On his way back to the platform, he once again bestowed them on Stash. They would only last so long, but is was a respite for Neil's healing that was welcome in the endurance battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back on the platform, Jason turned back to look at the monsters held back by Stash's massive hydra body and five snapping heads. He looked for one of the tougher, now heavy afflicted monsters and cast a spell. Instead of his usual finishers, punition or verdict, he hit it with something different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Feast of Blood] (Blood)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (drain, blood)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Base Cost: Moderate mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 30 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (03%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Drain health and stamina. Only affects targets with bleeding wounds or who are suffering from the [Bleeding] affliction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Drains additional health and stamina for each instance of poison on the target.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of all Jason's abilities, bar one, feast of blood had proven the most powerful against vampires, feeding on the blood magic coursing through them. After ranking up it grew stronger from every stance of poison on the target and Jason could layer quite a number of poisons. Necrotoxin, leech toxin, the ruination of the blood from his dagger and the umbral snake venom from his new armour, all stackable and piling up under the effects of inexorable doom. The result, amplified by the vampiric vulnerability to blood magic, made the first monster wither and die, its empty husk falling to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even his transcendent damage finisher was not as strong against the vampiric monsters. While he waited for the cooldown, he threw out more spells, turning his attention to Sophie's side of the platform. Still an iron-ranker, she was fearlessly punching above her weight, but while she had not been in as much danger as Stash, hers was the side closest to being pushed in. Jason continued throwing out spells on her side, in between using feast of blood as a finisher on Stash's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason glanced over the rest of the field. Humphrey was holding the most steady. Neil's growth spell had worn off, but Humphrey remained a powerhouse, stronger and tougher than any other member of the team. Jason asked Neil about Humphrey's mana consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He's doing great," Neil said. "Very controlled; we've barely had to top him off."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the deadly, blood-soaked porcupine, monsters were starting to accumulate on the golem's side. Jason was about to intervene when the golem erupted from its chrysalis. This time, it had taken the form of three plain, crystal blocks, each seeming comical and harmless as they stood on three legs apiece. It became less funny as they waddled into place to form a wall, each proving to possess the same spike power as the chrysalis form. Soon, all three were bristling with bloody spines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason turned his attention back to Stash, firing off another feast of blood spell before bestowing a third stack of blessings on the familiar. Many of the toughest enemies were now cleared off and Stash and the griffins could handle the rest for the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason returned to Sophie's side, where she fought, uncomplaining, even as her injuries and the pressure upon her mounted. Jason stepped forward and held up his hand to unleash his strongest trump card, the power that was unequivocally his strongest against the vampire monsters. Blood seeped out of his palm and then leeches started erupting from his hand. He swept his arm like a water cannon at a riot, scattering his swarm familiar over the crowd of monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colin was a vampire-devouring machine and that whole side of the battle collapsed like wilting flowers. Jason had considered unleashing Colin from the start, but had decided that holding him for when he was needed most would be the most effective use. The monsters had largely recovered from the team's initial big hits and were ramping up the pressure, so it seemed like the moment was right to deploy his strongest weapon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll cover you," Jason said after draining Sophie's afflictions again. "Take a rest."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the front-liners had been bearing the brunt of the attacks, Clive and Belinda had been dishing out the damage, like Jason. Using her specious sorcerer power, Belinda gained the ability to use wands and staves like Clive. Even though she could take advantage of his battle platform ritual and he had also put enhancement rituals on her weapons, she was still a pale comparison. He was a rank higher, as were his legendary items.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both Belinda and Clive had been using their rune trap powers on cooldown. It was a little costly on mana, but so long as they otherwise stuck to their weapons it was sustainable. The value of the spells, even Belinda's iron-rank version, was incredible. The monsters were too packed together to move out of the way, pushing each other into maximising the effectiveness of the small explosive area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophie resumed her position and Jason once again dove into the mess of monsters, roaming about, laying afflictions. Through the voice chat, Clive warned them of a new threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Flying monsters," he announced. "I think they're night shrikes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team looked up the approaching creatures, winging their way over the jungle canopy and into their air above their clearing. Night shrikes were another monster they had encountered before. Their bodies were the size of a small, slender person, something between a bat and a hook-billed bird. They were bronze-rank, but very much on the weak side, physically. Their advantages lay in their flight and their special power, which they combined to make hit and run attacks with their sharp beaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Floating above the team, Onslow turned his head to the new enemy, but Clive directed him to stay focused on the ground monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Jason will handle them," Clive told his familiar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As monster ranks increased, so did the likelihood of monsters with exotic powers. In the case of the night shrike, they had the ability to plunge an area into magical darkness that even drained the magic from glow stones, although none were out for this daylight battle. The shrikes would then strike using the darkness as their weapon, as their own senses were unimpeded by it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As anticipated, the shrikes blanketed the platform in complete darkness, turning bright day into deeper than night. What the flying monsters would quickly discover, as had those of their kind who came before, was that they were not the most dangerous thing in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason was no more impeded by the absence of light than the shrikes. Stars lit up on his cloak, shedding light that penetrated the magical power of the shrikes. The motes of light floated off his cloak, leaving it void black, as they floated up and around the platform. They concentrated on the platform itself, giving the team all the light they needed to keep fighting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around the platform, the motes of light were softer and spread out, giving just enough illumination to turn the black void of darkness into shadowy gloom. By turning the monsters' realm of absolute darkness into a realm of shadows, Jason made their kingdom his own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a zone of ubiquitous shadow, Jason could teleport around as he wished. He shadow-jumped behind one of the shrikes, wrapping his legs around its, under its wings, and one arm around its neck. The weight reducing power of his cloak stopped them from immediately plunging out of the sky, but the creature's flight was drastically impeded and they started arcing sharply down. Jason ignored their predicament, ramming his dagger into the monster multiple times before jumping again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason proved a horrifying nemesis to the shrikes, jumping from one to the other and sending them crashing into their monster brethren below. Some were already dead when they hit the ground, the rest soon after from the hard landing and Jason's afflictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shrikes scattered, wings beating heavily as they climbed skyward. It didn't matter. The cover of darkness was vanishing in patches as the shrikes died in rapid succession, restoring the bright sunlight to dominance. When the final shrike died in the air, Jason found himself floating alone in the sky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using the new gliding power of his cloak, Jason drifted his way over the team. Cloak fluttering around him, he alighted gently amongst them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Alright," Neil acknowledged. "You might kind of make this look good."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you think?" Humphrey asked Neil, refocusing his attention. "Is it time?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's a lot of Jason's sin affliction around now," Neil said. "Yeah, I think it's time. Everyone dump your mana."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team started unleashing every high cost ability they had, rapidly draining their mana pools much as they had at the beginning of the battle. Colin gathered up during that time, strips of bloody cloth snaking through the battlefield to collect leeches like fly paper and drag them into a central mass that wrapped up into its humanoid form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Here we go," Neil said, and activated his power, sending the team, plus their summons and familiars into a dimensional space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Reaper's Redoubt] (Shield)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special ability (dimension, recovery, disease).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Extreme mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 6 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (01%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Take allies into a dimensional space briefly while flooding the area with death energy, dealing disruptive-force damage, necrotic damage and inflicting [Creeping Death] on everything in the area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Allies undergo extreme mana replenishment while in the dimensional space.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Creeping Death] (damage-over-time, disease, stacking): Inflicts ongoing necrotic damage until the disease is cleansed. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team emerged from the dimensional space with their mana replenished. The jungle around them had been withered by Neil's power and most of the monsters were dead. Only a handful lingered past what was now the jungle line, having been outside the power's range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were about to move on them when eight figures emerged from the jungle. Unlike the monsters, these were all human. They stepped forward slowly, with none of the rush that the monsters had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's them," Humphrey said, face turned steely. "Time to do what we came here for."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">502704</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 23:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 238: Sin Eater</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/502234</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sophie and Humphrey were waiting for the monsters to get closer, while Neil cast a spell, conjuring two sets of three stone reels above his head. There were pictures of the various monsters present on the reels, like a giant, archaic slot machine. There were also images of the team, although massively out numbered by those of the monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Reels of Fortune] (Prosperity)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (this ability has variable subtypes, contingent on effect).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 10 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Conjures three immaterial reels. Channel mana into the reels to generate random effects on random individuals within the area. If an individual is affected more than once by the same use of the reels, the effect is increased for each reel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Conjures a second set of reels. Each reel is more likely to match sets for additional effect when large numbers of a creature type are present.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reels wheeled around before slowing and locking into place, one after another. Due to the bronze rank effect and preponderance of monsters, it was all but a given that each reel would produce a matching set. The first turned up three matching images of a snake monster and send a stroke of electricity into the cloud. The team could only see flashes of the lightning through the dirt and dust of the cloud that Clive had thrown up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second orb showed a three-set of a gorilla-like monster and sent a huge ball of fire sailing into the air. At the peak of its arc, it broke into numerous, smaller fireballs, plunging into the cloud as the reels above Neil faded. By this point, the monsters were almost upon them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey turned his gaze to the sky and teleported high into the air, before initiating his dive bomb and unstoppable force attacks, descending through the air like the sword of judgement. He carved a heavily armoured beetle-type creature clean in half and sent out a shockwave that scattered the surrounding monsters, dispersing the momentum they rebuilt after Clive's attack. Humphrey's wings appeared on his back and with a heavy flap they pushed his back onto the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first monsters had reached the platform and Sophie used her massive acceleration power, eternal moment. Time seemed to freeze as she rapidly produced wind blades that shot off as the power faded, so many that even the iron-rank attack eliminated a bronze-rank monster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With everyone having fired off their big openers, Neil cast a spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Cornucopia] (Prosperity)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (boon, recovery).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 1 hour.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (01%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Bestow a very strong mana and stamina recovery effects on all nearby allies, with a moderate duration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Provide boons that adapt to the needs of each ally. These effects have a long duration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team's mana started rapidly replenishing, and the team received various bonuses. Clive received an increase to wand and staff damage, as did Belinda, who had used her spurious sorcerer power to also gain the power to use magic weapons. Humphrey received a cost reduction for special attacks, while Sophie had her passive damage abilities strengthened. As for Neil, he had his cooldown times reduced. Even the familiars received bonuses, Only Jason missing out by being out of range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything was turning to chaos as monsters piled up around the platform. After Clive's blast gutted the centre mass of the monster wave, it was the flanks that pushed in hardest, with Humphrey and Sophie each holding a side while Neil's golem took the less hectic front. It was higher rank than Sophie, but the tenacious adventurer was still better able to hold the line than the summon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The monsters were primarily a mix of high-end iron and low-end bronze, with a few powerful standouts among them. The horde spread to the rear of the platform faster than expected after being pushed around the sides. There, they ran into hydra-form Stash, Humphrey directing the griffins to move in and support him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The monsters started piling up around the platform, held off by Stash, Sophie, Humphrey and the golem. Humphrey was swinging his sword back and forth in workmanlike fashion, his normal blows enough to put paid to the iron-rankers. His special attacks he saved for the bronzes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophie was moving so fast she looked like a flipbook animation, like a series of still images leading one into the other. She made the most of her increased damage buff and battering her foes with a dazzling series of hits that looked more like the speed of a bronze ranker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her wind blade power was of limited effect against the strength and number of the enemy. Instead, she relied on her wind wave power that could blast powerful gusts of air and send enemies flying. Usable every six seconds, it was an effective tool for disrupting the enemy and buying time. With the teams mana regeneration and her own efficiency, it was a pattern she could keep up indefinitely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others poured out damage from behind, Belinda and Clive with staves, Gordon and Belinda's lantern familiar with beams and bolts of force. Onslow floated above them blasting out powers from his shell. The magically saturated astral space was kind to the rune tortoise, allowing its powers to recharge more swiftly than normal and making it less reliant on Clive's mana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ranged attackers mostly focused on Sophie's side and the golem at the front, as Humphrey brought strength and resilience enough to hold a side largely on his own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unstable détente was formed, the monsters blindly attacking, but unable to make it past the teams defences for the moment. The initially impassive monsters were increasingly entering a state of blood frenzy, their vampiric natures revealed in a clamouring thirst for the blood of the team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The powers Clive had placed on the team, the rings of runes and the retributive damage, were proving a highly efficient use of his mana. Their effects weren't great, but they were ongoing and cheaply reapplied. The mantle of retribution inflicted damage back onto enemies, not in huge amounts, but it accumulated as the monsters threw themselves at Humphrey, the golem and Stash, all of whom were taking regular hits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each attack also triggered one of the runes from the rune mantle, to wildly varied effect. Some gave the ally a heal over time, an instant burst of mana recovery or bestowed boons like damage reduction, enhanced strength or even more retributive damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the runes affected the attacking enemy they usually blasted out damage that could be of any type. Elemental damage was the most common, but also varieties of force, from the powerful resonating and disruptive types to sonic shockwaves. At other times, the runes applied afflictions, from a weakening poison to flames that wouldn't seem to go out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One more effect was impinging upon the enemies with every attack they made. It was one that had little immediate effect, but threatened to ultimately determine the fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Hegemony] (Sin)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Aura (holy, unholy).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Base cost: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (09%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Allies within the aura have increased resistance to afflictions, while enemies within the aura have their resistance to afflictions reduced. Enemy resistances are further reduced for each instance of [Sin] they are suffering from.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Inflicts an instance of [Sin] on enemies that make physical or magical attacks against allies within the aura. Instances applied in this way cannot be resisted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Sin] (affliction, curse, stacking): All necrotic damage taken is increased. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's initial plans had been literally blasted into dust by Clive, forcing him to reorient himself. He and Shade's bodies were shadowy figures moving amongst the monsters, elusive and fleeting presences that monsters had no more than a swipe or two at before they were gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His aura was blanketing the area without giving away his position, akin to hiding a tree in the forest. It was one of the first aura techniques Farrah had ever shown him and now it was second nature. He might not be able to hide his aura from a well-trained silver ranker, but even they would have trouble pinpointing his location when he used this technique.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was staying relatively close to the platform, where his aura could blanket the monsters attacking his team. Every attack earned the monsters an instance of the necrosis-enhancing sin affliction, setting them up for a later fall. Every enemy that struck out against his allies was slowly shovelling earth from their own grave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason himself also took damage. Even without his aura revealing his presence, simply weaving through the monsters meant that many were taking swipes at him as he passed. They were a small price to pay for the havoc he was wreaking in return.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the bronze rankers he was lashing out with his dagger, piling on afflictions with every sweeping slice. In his other hand was a bronze rank weapon he had stowed away in his inventory since looting it from the marsh hydra he had fought with Humphrey and Clive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Item: [Flail of the Hydra] (bronze rank, rare)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A whip imbued with the life-force of a hydra&lt;/em&gt; (weapon, whip).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: The whip does not function like a normal whip. When swung, the heads of the whip will seek out enemies to attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: Poison inflicted using the whip as a medium is more potent.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The whip had five thick, thick, brown, leathery tails that ended in bulbs, within which were mouths filled with wickedly sharp teeth. They flailed uncontrollably, springing eagerly at any flesh that wasn't attached to the arm holding it. As Jason could use two shadow arms now, he had one for flexibility with the dagger and one to add reach to the whip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disadvantage of the whip was that it didn't inflict the trio of afflictions the conjured dagger produced, which is why Jason used that for the tougher monsters. It still applied the disease added by his shadow arm power and the effect of any special attack he used.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, those effects were delivered by each of the five heads. That meant a single target special attack could now affect five at a time, albeit randomly in whatever vague direction the whip was swung. In a thick crowd of monsters, it was an excellent tool for thinning out the weaker ones. The whip's bites might have not dealt a lot of damage, but as an affliction delivery system it was amazing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason was unconcerned about the damage being inflicted on him, in spite of being amidst a sea of monsters. Pain was an old friend to any adventurer that truly threw themselves into the work, and his powers gave him powerful advantages over the vampiric enemy. His blood abilities were especially potent against the vampiric creatures and the blood magic that fuelled them. As he lay into them with his dagger, that made his choice of special attack obvious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Leech Bite] (Blood)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special attack (melee, wounding, blood, drain, poison).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Base cost: Low stamina.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (07%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Inflicts or refreshes the [Bleeding] condition. Drains a small amount of health and stamina when refreshing the [Bleeding] condition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Inflicts an instance of [Leech Toxin].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Bleeding] (affliction, wounding, blood): Deals ongoing damage by causing or increasing blood loss. As a wounding effect, this condition absorbs and negates an amount of incoming healing, after which this affliction immediately ends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Leech Toxin] (affliction, poison, blood, stacking): When [Bleeding] is negated, an instance of [Leech Toxin] on the target is consumed to reapply [Bleeding]. Additional instances can be accumulated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Against the vampiric monsters both the bleeding effect and the health drain were operating more powerfully than normal, even accounting for the increase to bronze rank. The health drain helped keep him going, although alone, it was not enough to outpace the regular swipes and bites that he suffered. Fortunately, he was able to devour the very means the vampires sought to bring him down with. Every bite he suffered only made him stronger as his sin eater ability devoured the curses they carried.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have been afflicted with [Vampiric Blood Curse].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Vampiric Blood Curse] (affliction, poison, blood, stacking): Has a slight disorienting effect that increases with stacks. Beyond a certain threshold, dying under this effect will cause you to rise as a vampiric ghoul.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have resisted [Vampiric Blood Curse].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have gained an instance of [Resistant].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have gained an instance of [Integrity].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Jason, the vampiric powers of their enemies were not an issue. He had some concerns about his team, but they were holding it off to a degree. Sophie and Jason's auras protected them, and Neil was on hand to cleanse if necessary. The plan was to leave that to Jason, though, who not only didn't spend mana to cleanse, but got it back in return.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's sin eater ability already increased his resistances, and increased them even further for each effect he resisted. At bronze rank, each effect resisted also bestowed a new boon, alongside each instance of the resistance boon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Integrity] (heal-over-time, mana-over-time, stamina-over-time, holy, stacking): Periodically recover a small amount of health, stamina and mana. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effect of a single instance was very mild, but with every bite he suffered, the healing continued to stack up. On top of this, he also had his protective amulet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Item: [Amulet of the Dark Guardian] (growth, bronze rank, legendary)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: For each instance of an affliction applied to an enemy, gain an instance of [Guardian's Blessing]. You may bestow all instances of [Guardian's Blessing] upon another person by touch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Guardian's Blessing] (boon, holy): Instances are consumed to absorb damage from any source. Additional instances have a cumulative effect. For each instance consumed, gain an instance of [Blessing's Bounty].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Blessing's Bounty] (heal-over-time, holy, stacking): Heal over time. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he laid out afflictions, he gained stacks of protection that were consumed as fast as they were laid on, leaving a heal effect in their wake. Between the two healing effects and the drain, Jason was healing much of the damage monsters landed on him with their opportunistic strikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He constantly flickered around using Shade's bodies to stay on the move. He never stopped long enough in any particular location for the monsters around him to stop and make concerted attacks. That kind of focus when surrounded would easily be enough to overwhelm him in short order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even staying on the move, he was taking damage faster than he was healing it. That, and the slowly accruing vampiric curse affecting the team made it time for a return to the platform. He sent one of Shade's bodies ahead, allowing him to step through another and right into the middle of his team.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">502234</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 23:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 237: It's Not About Killing Monsters</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/501772</link><description>&lt;p&gt;They heard the monsters before they saw them. It began with the sound of something moving loudly through the thick jungle, pushing its way roughly through the undergrowth. Humphrey had them turn around and go back the way they came, making for one of the defensible points he had been looking out for as they travelled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had picked out a construction that had held up better than most, due to being a solid, flat, stone platform. It was only around chest high, far from enough to stop monsters, but was at least an impediment they could work with. It was also sized fairly well for the team, giving Sophie and Humphrey the chance to move about while staying close to the more vulnerable party members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shade returned to his normal form, gently depositing his riders on the ground. The others took a moment to begin calling up their summons and familiars while Stash turned from a riding lizard into a giant marsh hydra. At bronze rank he could take the physical form of bronze-rank monsters but could only use the full magical powers of iron-rank monsters. He could use some minor magical abilities of bronze-rank monsters, but certainly nothing as powerful as the hydra's potent rapid healing. What he did get was the hydra's strength, toughness and multiple, teeth-laden heads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason directed Gordon to stay with the main group as the familiar's direct damage would be more useful to the team than it would for Jason in the fight to come. He was about to leave when Humphrey held him up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Jason," Humphrey said. "We're going to lean on you heavily for this, but I know you can do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Humphrey," he said, shaking his head, "you still don't really understand adventuring. It's not about killing monsters."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason tugged casually at his new, bronze-rank battle robe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's about how you look while you're killing monsters. And you have to admit…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's shadow cloak manifested around him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I make this look good."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dear gods, you're insufferable," Neil called out from where he was setting up a summoning circle. "Also, good luck and please don't die."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason slipped the hood of his magical cloak back, giving Humphrey a rare smile completely devoid of smirk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't go getting it into your head that you have to do all the work," Jason warned him. "Don't go thinking that you're the one who has to save everyone, to make the big sacrifice. Remember when I got it into my head to go of and kill all those bandits alone? I was wrong to do that. Be the beneficiary of my mistakes. It's not just about you. Or me, which I need to be reminded of, from time to time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Happy to help!" Neil called out, still pouring the salt for his summoning circle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you, Neil," Jason said flatly, then turned his attention back to Humphrey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Trust the team, Humphrey. Rely on the team. We're pretty good. Well, Neil's okay. But the rest of us…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason slipped his hood back up and lightly ran off, vanishing into the jungle. He was stronger when he was free to run rampant, but would remain in contact with the team through the voice chat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were ropey vines all over the platform and Clive handed Sophie and Belinda vials they used to rapidly wither the plants and give themselves clear footing. It was a concoction of Jory's that Clive had acquired a supply of before returning to the jungle-covered city. They didn't have enough for it to waste on pathfinding through jungle scrub, but to give them some much-needed solid footing in a crucial moment it was perfect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the two women cleared off the plants, Clive started drawing out ritual circles. He started with a large one in the centre of the platform, his battle platform ritual that would enhance the wand and staff attacks, as well as any damage spells of the group. Then he moved on to circles attached to the end of his weapons. The glowing lines moved with the weapons as he waved them about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advantage of staff and wand weapons was that they were highly mana efficient, compared to combat magic. The disadvantage was that they were also weaker, but Clive's ritual circles would help remedy that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The circles he was using would refine the ambient magic of the area and feed it into the weapons, providing additional power without requiring additional mana from Clive's own pool. The impact this would have on the ambient magic once he started using his weapons meant that any further rituals in the area would be tricky to use for a while, but that was hardly a concern with what was about to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive decided to get in before then and try something he had been working on. It wasn't related to his essence abilities, instead being a work of pure ritual magic. Ritual magic designed for combat some exceptionally rare, and it was something Clive had developed himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He started drawing ritual circles in the air, one after another in a line, like a tube. He poured large amount of his own mana into each one, largely depleting his mana pool by the time he was done. It ran from the centre of the battle platform circle directly toward the jungle where the sound of rushing monsters was growing louder by the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey and Neil, in the meantime, were calling up their summons. Neil's chrysalis golem looked different at bronze rank. It was just as tall but the formerly chunky, ogrish form was now more refined, like a powerfully muscled giant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For his own summon, Humphrey hesitated before throwing the summoner's die. He ultimately decided to use it, knowing that it could provide a crucial advantage in what would be a punishing battle. Hopefully, even a bad role would be mitigated by the new ability it had gained on reaching bronze rank. At first, Humphrey had thought there was no change to the function of the die, as there was little change to the description.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Item: [Summoner's Die: Form] (bronze rank [growth], legendary)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;&lt;em&gt;An eldritch tool for altering the nature of summoned creatures&lt;/em&gt; (tool, die).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Requirements: Summoning power.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: Rolling this die while enacting a bronze-rank or lower summoning power will randomly alter the form the summon takes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Can be used in conjunction with [Summoner's Die: Element] and [Summoner's Die: power]. Using more than one die of the same kind will negate the effects of all dice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;What he had only later realised was that three of the faces on the die had changed. It had only been the day before when he used the die and one of the new faces rolled up. After stopping, the symbol that lit up was not that of an animal, but one that Clive quickly translated as meaning 'power.' The die had then rolled again, on its own, landing on the symbol for wolf. The result had been Humphrey's summons turning into werewolf like creatures, larger, more powerful and standing on two legs. They were still made of dragon bone and had the conjured equipment generated by Humphrey's storage power, in this case, bronze-rank armour perfectly tailored to fit their unusual body shape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey hoped for a similar result as he rolled again. When it stopped, a glowing symbol rose up from the die; another of the new symbols. Humphrey had gone over them with Clive after finding out about the new sides and knew this one meant double. He had been hoping that meant it doubled the number of summons it called up. Even unenhanced by the die, ten of his bone soldiers would be of critical value against the numbers they were expecting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After falling to a stop, the die rolled itself again, the symbol for bird rising up to float next to the one for double. Then the die rolled for a third time, stopping on cat. The three symbols merged to form a new symbol, one that Humphrey didn't know. Then his summons began to appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were five, the normal number for his summoning power at bronze rank. They had the hind legs and body of oversized lions, and the wings and head of a giant eagle. Their front legs were also those of an eagle, ending in powerful talons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Griffins," Humphrey said in a half-whisper. He had seen them as a child, while travelling with his mother. Sailing on a ship near the coast, they had spotted the griffins come soaring majestically off the top of a cliff. They had swooped down, snatching sharks right out of the water before winging away with them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It had been young Humphrey's first encounter with a magical beast that was natural, rather than a monster. Such creatures were rare in the low-magic Greenstone region where he was born and raised. It had left griffins with a special place in his heart and he was entranced as his summons took their form. These were all white, the colour of dragon bone, and wearing armoured barding suited to their forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Humphrey," Sophie called out. "Eyes up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey stirred from his unexpected, nostalgic reverie and realised that the sounds of the approaching monsters had grown from a few individuals crashing through the jungle into what sounded like a wave. Like water crashing onto a rocky shore, the violent sounds of monsters tearing through the undergrowth came washing over them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey touched one of the griffins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Swoop, grab and drop," he instructed them and they took to the air. He then leapt lightly onto the platform, where Neil and his golem had already clambered up. Most of the team were gathered with their familiars and summons, the exception being Humphrey and Jason. Jason had taken Colin and Shade with him, leaving Gordon behind. Humphrey was present, but his griffon's were winging overhead as Clive's floating tortoise watched their majestic swooping forlornly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey had sent Stash, in his domineering hydra form, back behind the platform. The monsters would largely try and swarm them from the front, which is where their main defensive strength was positioned. It was inevitable, though, that the platform would become surrounded. Stash would be their main line of defence from that approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive and Neil both started casting spells on their teammates. Humphrey grew half his height again from Neil's first offering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Giant's Might] (Growth)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (boon).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 10 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (04%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Target ally and their equipment grow larger, gaining an enhanced [Power] attribute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Ally also gains resistance to physical damage and high-momentum effects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive's first spell affected the whole team on the platform, including their summons and familiars. Jason, Shade, Colin and the Griffons who were out of range were not so blessed. The ability created rings of glowing runes that floated around everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Rune Mantle] (Rune)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (boon, this ability has variable subtypes, contingent on effect).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 10 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (02%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Bestow a ring of random runes around an ally. Each rune is associated with a specific effect that affects the ally or an enemy. Attacks against the ally trigger the destruction of a random rune, causing its effect to occur.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Increasing the cost to moderate mana allows the rune mantle to be bestowed on all nearby allies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive's second spell likewise affected the whole team, making them glow gold-red for a moment before fading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Mantle of Retribution] (Karmic)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (boon, retributive).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 10 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (01%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Inflicts retributive impact damage on anyone who attacks the target ally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Increasing the cost to moderate mana allows the mantle of retribution to be bestowed on all nearby allies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the spells were being cast, the monsters grew louder and louder, yet there were no roars or shrieks. They were silent, save for the commotion of their passage through the jungle as they flattened everything in their path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally they appeared in front of the team, erupting out of the jungle. As unnerving as the fact that they weren't issuing any noises was the way the disparate group moved as one. Normally, such a wild collection of monsters would be more eager to fight each other than they would adventurers..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the creatures reached the platform, they finally started to make noise, all in harmony. It was an alien, sonorous cry, filled with hunger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Throw your heaviest attacks to blunt the first wave, then conserve mana," Humphrey called out, as if the team hadn't gone over and over the plans for the battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive had already made his big mana expenditure on his row of ritual circles. They were lined up like the barrel of a gun and he fired a bolt from his staff through the first. The bolt froze, as if caught in an invisible hand, and the mana Clive had put into the circle was fed into the bolt until the circle collapsed. The bolt shot forward again, stopping and draining mana from each circle until it was a huge globe of force that made the air around the team vibrate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the bolt was going through its stop-start passage, the rest of the team opened up. Belinda used her force tether power to gather a large cluster of the shoulder-to shoulder monsters and then open her reaper pit power underneath. The tether exploded and the rest of their health would be eaten away by the pit. Only a few of the tough bronze-rankers would eventually escape when the pit's duration came to an end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive's bolt finished its passage, having consumed all the ritual circles. It landed amongst the monsters like military ordinance, throwing up a huge cloud of dirt and dust, along with a low boom that rammed into their eardrums. The cloud obscured most of the monsters from their sight, while gobbets of wet jungle earth and wet former monster rained down on the team. They didn't have time to pay it any mind, as what they could see of the monsters showed that they hadn't slowed down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell was that?" Jason asked through voice chat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sorry," Clive said. "I didn't realise the effect would be that big."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just watch where you're aiming that thing!"&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">501772</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 23:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 236: A Series of Familiar Powers</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/501334</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Shade was not visibly changed in his new, bronze rank vessel; he remained a shadowy figure in a cloak of darkness. The only visible difference was an increase in his number of bodies, from three to seven. He had also gained the ability to exert a small amount of physical force, while remaining an incorporeal entity. It wasn't enough to inflict damage but it would allow him to perform tasks in places too dangerous for people who weren't intangible and didn't have six extra bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also meant that it was unlikely that Shade's vessel would be completely eliminated in battle. Barring an unusual fight, such as the one against the elemental tyrant that claimed his original iron-rank vessel, he would remain intact. Any bodies that were destroyed could be remade, so long as at least one remained. The only cost would be time and almost all of Jason's mana, making it something not to be done in the midst of combat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other new ability Shade had acquired was his own dimensional storage space. It wasn't as capacious as that of Jason, Humphrey or Clive, but was accessible from any of Shade's bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's own storage space, his inventory power, had likewise improved as he reached bronze rank. One of it's nuances was the ability to expand the number of slots available through the use of dimensional bags. There were five slots in the corner of the inventory screen interface for placing dimensional bags, but only one had been available and could only be filed with an iron-rank bag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason had filled that slot early in his adventuring career, but he brought two bronze rank bags with him for use once he ranked up. He had to carry them empty, as dimensional bags could only be placed into other dimensional spaces when they themselves contained nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another boost to his inventory was an increase to the maximum volume per item. He could feel the change instinctively, but would need to experiment to find the exact new limit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey and Clive had likewise experienced improvements from their storage abilities reaching bronze. Unlike Jason's power, theirs were essence abilities that gained not just incremental improvements but whole new effects on ranking up. Humphrey's storage space power, magic armoury, now significantly reduced the mana cost of conjuring his weapons and armour. It meant that he no longer had to burn a notable chunk of mana at the start of every fight, of whenever he switched between his two conjured swords.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive's rune gate power had gone through the most impressive change. The original function opened a rune circle portal to his storage space, but was now a full-fledged portal power. Combining dimensional storage and a travel portal in one ability wasn't useful in a fight, but it was easily the most concentrated utility power on the team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increase in utility was another indication of the somewhat unusual makeup of the team. Humphrey and Neil were the only members that would slot easily into conventional team roles, with Jason, Clive, Belinda and Sophie all outside the norm to various degrees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the relatively normal end of the spectrum were Jason and Sophie. Affliction specialists and dodge tanks were less common variations of the common damage-dealer and guardian roles. Clive was a spell-based damage dealer who only had one attack spell. Belinda was the most extreme, simultaneously filling no set roles and most of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A traditional adventuring team used reliable strengths and fixed roles to approach every situation in a similar way, in order to maximise their strengths and minimise their weaknesses. The weakness of Jason's team was the inability to do that. They needed to strategise and adapt to any given circumstance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team, in a way, had become something of a reflection of Jason. There were better power sets for everyday monster hunting, but they thrived in meeting challenges that more conventional teams would struggle against. By not being pinned down to one approach, they would be ready when unusual circumstances were thrown their way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the team's adaptive nature was the inclusion of a lot of utility. Most teams would include at least one storage space power and would count any more as a happy bonus. As for portal or teleportation powers, there was no team that wouldn't jump at the chance. Many teams would take on an otherwise unremarkable, or even downright incompetent member for the simple reason that their repertoire included a portal ability. Jason's team commanded four storage powers and three long-distance travel powers, making them rather enviable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stash had also evolved to bronze rank alongside Humphrey, the bonded familiar not requiring a new body to be summoned in they way Jason's familiars did. While as mischievous as ever, he was more confident about revealing his true form, which only Humphrey had seen before. His true shape was small, with a long, serpentine body covered in rainbow scales that ran along him in waves of colour that shimmered and changed. Belinda became completely enchanted with his draconic true form and Stash became enchanted with the praise she heaped upon him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gordon went through a slight change when his new body was summoned, with a second pair of glowing, blue and orange eyeball orbs joining the first in floating around his body. This gave him four simultaneous attack beams; two of resonating force that was effective against tough opponents and two of disruptive force, effective against magic and incorporeal beings like Gordon himself. Additionally, he could send two orbs of the same type hurtling off, even flying them around corners before coming together and detonating. The resultant explosion was powerful, but the orbs would take a minute to reform, during which they could not be used to make further attacks..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making good on his threat, Humphrey pushed the team to stay on the move, hunting down more of the flesh abominations and whatever ordinary monsters they encountered along the way. Eager to push the limits of their new capabilities, both Humphrey and Jason took on flesh abominations alone for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Jason's case, his bronze-rank powers were enough to overwhelm the monster's recovery powers much faster. He had already been able to bypass the rank-based damage resistance but now his powers were doing bronze-rank damage. That was only part of the change, as his new afflictions also played a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rigor mortis, inflicted by his shadow arm Reaper power, gave a stacking penalty to the speed and recovery attributes of whatever poor soul he inflicted it upon. His inexorable doom power caused the effect to stack up and up, the penalty to speed making the creature more and more sluggish, even when it took swift forms to try and pin down the elusive Jason. Meanwhile, the penalty to recovery left its ability to hold off the afflictions increasingly diminished, even as the afflictions themselves became worse and worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another key affliction came from Jason's special attack, leech bite. Along with inflicting the bleeding effect, it now also inflicted the same leech toxin poison that Colin did. An instance of the stacking toxin would refresh the bleeding effect whenever it was healed through, leaving the adaptive powers of the flesh abominations unable to stave off Jason's malign powers as effectively as they had in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey was likewise able to overcome the ability of the abominations to adapt to him, in his case with raw power. He showed off the advantage of being a human special attack specialist with an array of offensive techniques that could take on any kind of enemy. If it took a solid form, the resonating force of his shield breaker attack would crack it like an egg. A more amorphous form would absorb heavy physical blows but be vulnerable to the disruptive force of his spirit reaper attack. His unstoppable force power had a longer cooldown, but would devastate the abominations in whatever form they took.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey had not taken on any of them himself before Jason and Neil ranked up, as getting them over the line to bronze rank had always been the priority. Now they had, he was happier to let himself loose. Like Jason, he had already been ignoring the rank disparity, but Increasing the power of his attacks from iron to bronze-rank had turned him from a threat to a nemesis. He relentlessly pounded away at an abomination that simply couldn't find a form to withstand the oppressive might.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team were put through their paces as they made a beeline for the centre of the city and the territory of the blood weaver. Of a night they continued to rest in the cloud house, which was now a more secure than ever. The magic of the house was more sophisticated at bronze rank, with stronger defences and a superior ability to hide itself from the senses of wandering monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As they stopped to rest each night, Clive had been taking more precise measurements of the ambient magic, which had been rising at a precipitous rate. He updated the team as they rested for the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Isn't that a barely measurable increase?" Jason asked as Clive gave them the results of his latest analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The fact that the increase is measurable at all is alarming," Clive told him. "That it's occurred over just a matter of weeks is insane. We need to figure out what these cultists have done."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And if we can't question them, because they're mindless blood thralls?" Sophie asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I doubt they'll be mindless," Clive said. "A blood weaver could turn them into witless blood puppets, but more likely it has employed a traditional form of vampirism, where they are subject to the will of the one that turned them, while retaining their own minds."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We take them alive if we can," Humphrey said. "Not at the risk of endangering the team, though. If we have to put them down, we do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If they aren't any help, that's not the end of the road," Clive said. "Whatever is causing this change isn't something you can just knock out a magic ritual for and off you go. What's happening is more involved than that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Any closer to an idea of what that is?" Humphrey asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I've being going through the books Knowledge gave Jason, looking for something that would produce these results. Without more information, though, I'm not even sure what to look for. At this point, more than talking to these cultists, I need to see what tools they brought with them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shade now had enough bodies that he could transform into a mount for each member of the team, and bronze rank had apparently enhanced the nature of the mounts he could transform into. For one thing, he could collect multiple bodies together to replicate the self-propelled magical carriages favoured by the Greenstone elite. That was of little use on streets overgrown with jungle, but not the only new trick he had picked up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than a full vehicle, Shade could also merge fewer bodies to create different individual mounts. By merging his bodies in pairs, he became three creatures that were somewhere between a narrow-bodied beetle and a preying mantis. Each had a glossy black carapace, glowing eyes and huge blade arms with glowing white edges, from which mist softly drifted. They were an intimidating sight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Very nice," Jason said approvingly. "Shade, you're an absolute champion."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These creatures do not appear in this world," Shade said with his remaining body. "They exist in another world I spent time in while serving as a familiar."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hold on," Humphrey said. "Jason, you have no problem with these terrifying blade-armed monstrosities, but heidels disturbing?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They have two heads, Humphrey. Two heads. Can you imagine having two heads? Imagine if you had a great idea for a recipe, then had to explain it to your other head. That's not right."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait, &lt;em&gt;that's&lt;/em&gt; your problem?" Humphrey asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What if you're eating something delicious? Either one head gets left out or each one only gets half as much, because they have to share a stomach. Half as much! What if it's a delicious cake!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That was a nice cake you brought out for the rank-up feast," Neil said. "Did you make that yourself?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I did. The secret is to sweeten the cream before whipping it and really make it the highlight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Was there leftover cake?" Sophie asked, with a suspiciously bushy moustache.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There was not," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Boo," she jeered, before turning into an iridescent blue jungle lizard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"At least he's figured out how to shape shift clothes, now," actual Sophie said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They're still part of his body, so technically he was naked," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey said nothing, pinching the bridge of his nose and shaking his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all of the team rode the mantis beetles. Sophie maintaining her scouting glide-flight over their heads, while Humphrey rode Stash in lizard form. Clive joined Sophie, drifting slowly through the air on Onslow, the flying tortoise. His familiar wasn't very fast at any altitude beyond just above ground height, but as he didn't need to navigate the terrain there was no problem keeping up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That left the three mantis beetles, the most Shade could produce. It was enough for Jason, Neil and Belinda, giving the whole team effective transport. The blade arms of the mounts were ideal for cutting a path through the jungle, while the remaining six beetle legs offered a solid platform that could navigate the uneven ground with ease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shade, how do you think this form would hold up in combat?" Jason asked. Although the mantis beetle looked to have a hard, chitinous exterior, it was actually composed of the same soft, comfortable shadow-stuff Shade's horse form had been. The blade arms were effectively cutting though the undergrowth, however.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That would be unreliable, at best," Shade said. "I strongly suspect that any amount of damage would make me unable to sustain this form. You do not have to tell anyone that, however. I could be used to make an effective bluff."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I like the way you think."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, great," Neil said. "As if Asano wasn't dodgy enough already. Now he's got a partner."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team reached the interior of the city where the buildings were completely shattered and the jungle in complete ascendance. As with their first visit, they were unharassed by monsters as they pushed in. Rather than ride mounts, they made a slogging path on foot through the thick undergrowth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you think the blood weaver took control of all the monsters in this area?" Neil asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There might have been some too strong to take over," Humphrey said. "Other silver rank monsters. They were more likely driven out of the weaver's territory, rather than subjugated. You can expect to encounter vampire versions of everything bronze and below that was here, though."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It kind of worries me that we still aren't seeing any," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It almost certainly knows we're here by now," Clive said. "It's smart enough to try and bait us in, the way it did last time, but not smart enough to realise we'd see through it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yeah, but we're walking into the trap anyway," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Once the fighting starts, it probably won't stop until we reach the blood weaver," Humphrey said. "We're going to be fighting all the monsters from a large area, all in one wave. Let Jason and Sophie do the heavy lifting as much as possible, since they're our endurance players. Obviously do what you have to, but conserve your mana and stamina as much as you can. We have a lot of mana recovery, but expect a lot of fight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey stopped, looking around at the team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Make no mistake," he said. "This will be a battle, not a fight. We are about to experience the single most gruelling combat scenario that any of us have ever encountered. More than the expedition into the desert astral space, more than Jason playing distraction to the silver-rank elemental. We're going to war against an army of vampire monsters and we'll be wading through the bodies of the dead before we're done."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, what I'm hearing is that it will be easy and we shouldn't worry," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey glared at him and Jason put a reassuring hand on Humphrey's arm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mate, it's alright," Jason said. "We know the stakes, we know what we're up against and we know what we'll have to face before we're done. Don't go wasting your energy now on being tense; you'll have intensity enough, once the fighting starts. For now, just trust in your team."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason glanced at the jungle around them, as if waiting for something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Damn," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What?" Humphrey asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That would have been an epic moment for the monsters to appear," Jason. "You'd think vampires would have a more appropriate sense of drama."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">501334</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 23:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 235: Anyone Can Be Useful</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/500123</link><description>&lt;p&gt;"I actually got the materials pretty cheap," Jason said. "Gary made it from local materials in the first place, so I just needed higher-grade versions of the same stuff."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason had drawn out the diagram for the ritual of ascension that would have his sword, like he had himself, advance from iron-rank to bronze. He was now laying out ingots of blood gold and star-fall silver, piles of quintessence gems and neat stacks of bronze-rank spirit coins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rest of the team were lounging about on the porch of the cloud house in hanging chairs. Jason turned to look at Sophie who had been staring at him all day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What?" he asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What?" she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You've been looking at me like that all day."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Like what?" Sophie asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Impassively, I guess," Jason said. "You do everything impassively, so it's hard to differentiate."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your face," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What about my face?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Bronze rank," she said. "It made it less awful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yep," Belinda agreed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I miss the chin," Neil said. "It kind of looked like some weird essence power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It wasn't that bad," Jason said. "Humphrey, tell them it wasn't that bad."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It wasn't that bad," Humphrey said. "I'd even say it was good."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I mean," Humphrey continued, "if I ever ran out of mana and couldn't conjure a sword, it was right there. What do I use for a backup, now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason looked put upon as the team laughed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It really does look good," Belinda said, taking pity on him. "Bronze rank's been good to you. The square-jaw thing you have happening now that is actually not bad. Right, Soph?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Its… not terrible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's Sophie language for 'sexy as all get-out,' which I think is a little excessive, but each to their own," Belinda said. It earning her a glare from Sophie, while Jason shook his head and went back to his ritual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would have been faster for Clive to perform the ritual, as he had with Neil's growth items, but Clive hadn't offered and Jason hadn't asked. They both understood that if you could advance your growth items yourself, you did it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sword was simple and elegant in it's design; silvery blade, a simple, red gold hilt with black binding and a short black tassel. Jason carefully placed it at the centre of the magic circle and performed the ritual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Growth item [Dread Salvation] has advanced from iron rank to bronze rank.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Growth item [Dread Salvation] has reached its maximum potential. It must be reforged by the original craftsperson in order to advance further.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Item [Dread Salvation] has gained new abilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive, Neil and Humphrey had already ranked-up their growth items with no additional effects, and the same had happened for Jason's amulet. His sword was the first of their items to gain new effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Item: [Dread Salvation] (bronze rank [growth], legendary)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A sword crafted with gratitude, in hope it would be of the greatest use in the moment of greatest need. It was forged with passion and expertise to be a reliable companion, bestowing upon it an incredible potential&lt;/em&gt; (weapon, sword).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: If a special attack that applies an affliction is made with this sword, but the subject of the attack has a physical immunity to it, an instance of [Stone Cutter] is applied to the blade and an instance of [Vibrant Echo] is inflicted to the enemy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: If a special attack that applies an affliction is made with this sword, but the subject of the attack has a magical immunity to it, an instance of [Spell Breaker] is applied to the blade and an instance of [Radiant Echo] is inflicted to the enemy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Stone Cutter] (magic, stacking): All attacks deal additional resonating-force damage; highly effective against physical defences. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Vibrant Echo] (damage-over-time, magic, stacking): Deal ongoing, resonating-force damage. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Spell Breaker] (magic, stacking): All attacks deal additional disruptive-force damage; highly effective against magical defences and incorporeal entities. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Radiant Echo] (damage-over-time, magic, stacking): Deal ongoing, disruptive-force damage. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to getting more powerful over time, the sword's new abilities allowed it to leave behind ongoing damage effects, bringing it more in line with Jason's own power set. Magic-type afflictions were easier to dispel than most, but almost nothing was immune to them, unlike Jason's various maledictions. To advance the sword further would require Gary's help, but silver rank was, for the moment, a distant horizon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was saving his familiar upgrades for last, so he moved on to the cloud flask. He shooed everyone off the porch and returned the cloud house to its flask, the house taking several minutes to dissolve into smoke and pour into the bottle like a genie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There must be a big, involved ritual for an item like the cloud flask," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nope," Jason said. "You just have to get to bronze rank, then feed the greedy bugger about a squillion bucks worth of goodies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He shook his head at the bottle as he pulled a funnel from his inventory, placed it in the mouth of flask and then started shoving in fistfuls of quintessence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Twenty-two hundred quintessence," he complained. "Two hundred of it dimension quintessence. Remind me to thank Emir again for supplying the goods for the first rank up. No way could I have afforded this, on top of everything else."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shovelling in all the quintessence gems and then ten thousand spirit coins took longer than the rituals for Jason and Neil's growth weapons put together. Deprived of their comfortable cloud seats, some of the team grew impatient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Could you have just used silver coins?" Neil asked. "Or gold. That would have sent it along nicely."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's not about the value of the coins," Clive said. "It's about the magic inside them. All that power doesn't just fuel the upgrade but balances out all the magic involved in the transformation, so it doesn't go awry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You know," Neil said to Clive, "just once, I'd like something to come up and have you say that you have no idea."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey Clive," Belinda said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How would Neil kill any monsters if we weren't around?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have no idea," Clive said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You two are hilarious," Neil said flatly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Actually, that was pretty good," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shut up and play with your bottle."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cult leader Zato, led Timos and Thadwick across the ruined grounds of the Vane estate. The last remnants of the climate-shifting magic were gone and the desert was rapidly reclaiming the once lush territory. Now it was nothing but withered remnants and piled ruins, only the now-dormant magical pylons marking what had once been a stark line between the estate and the desert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They arrived at what had previously been the manor house, now crumbling stone and dried wood. Zato held out an arm and the limb segmented into pieces, revealing not warm flesh and blood within, but cold iron. The pieces were strung together on a wire, which spooled out as the segments sprung forward, burying themselves in the piled debris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moments later, chunks of that debris started floating into the air, more and more of them, moving into an organised shape. The materials melted, wood and stone flowing like water as they blended together to form a strange hybrid material. The material flowed into lines, creating a ritual circle on the ground and then a dome that covered it, leaving only a hole large enough to crawl through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As you grow stronger," Zato said, "Your meagre essence abilities will be supplanted, one by one, by the superior power of the Builder. You will not be bound by mortal limitations, scrabbling for scraps of might from worthless training or miserable monster cores."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This will make me strong?" Thadwick asked, nodding at the dome as it neared completion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes," Zato said. "So many have passed you over, Thadwick, but I see your true potential. You will prove of supreme value to the Builder, once you are stronger. Enter, and feel the power flow through you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a last, wary look, Thadwick got down and crawled through the hole. When the hole closed behind him and he was plunged into darkness, he panicked for a moment. Then he felt the promised power surging into him. It had only been a matter of moments, but he could feel the strength flowing through him and he started laughing like a madman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outside the dome, Zato and Timos could no more hear Thadwick than he could hear them as they walked away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When you said you would find something for Thadwick, I was not optimistic," Timos said. "I didn't realise that something like this was possible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"More than possible, it is necessary," Zato said. "I was not fully inducted into the leadership, who took their plans with them to the grave fighting on the island. We have need of guidance. Thadwick and the other one…?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dougall," Timos reminded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Right, yes. Thadwick and Dougall are not true believers. They came to us out of desperate, mercenary sensibilities. Half loyalties will be met with half membership. They will pay the rest of their way with sacrifice and will be venerated for their service."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why bother with the ruse?" Timos asked. "Why not just force Thadwick along?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Because even with the soul seed inside it, altering a soul is difficult business unless that soul is willing. Why force the poison down his throat when a spoonful of honey will have him gulping it down?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Honestly? I want to make him choke on the spoon?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zato chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How close to ready is Dougall?" Timos asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He will reach the requisite state shortly before the Church of Purity's people arrive," Zato said. "The timing is fortuitous. For the moment, make sure that neither Dougall nor Thadwick realise that they are receiving the same treatment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not a problem," Timos said. "Dougall is so keen on ingratiating himself that he will do exactly as asked. Thadwick is so self-obsessed that he is oblivious to any of the goings on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zato smiled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"See? Anyone can be useful, if you find the task that best suits their abilities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's big," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It wouldn't let me use the blending-in version," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't think there's a version of this that you can discreetly move through a jungle," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Item: [Cloud Flask] (bronze rank [growth], legendary)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;This item is bound to you and cannot be used by anyone else.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Use the energies within the cloud flask to create buildings and vehicles made of clouds. Available forms are restricted by rank.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Items contained within the cloud construct when it is returned to the flask are stored in a dimensional space and cannot be recovered until another cloud construct is formed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Available forms (iron rank): Cloud house (grand), cloud house (adaptive).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Available forms (bronze rank): Carriage house (grand).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Unavailable forms (bronze rank): Carriage house (adaptive).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A carriage house is meant to be a building that holds carriages," Jason said. "Not a building that trundles about like one."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Jason, the cloud flask's bronze-rank form looked as much as anything like a massive recreational vehicle, one of the stupidly expensive ones with two levels and a roof deck that movie stars lived in on set. It even had a spot for a driver at the front, although it was directed by placing hands on a misty orb, rather than a steering wheel. Other than that, Jason could direct its movements mentally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cloudy white vehicle with its sunset embellishments stood out brightly amongst the dark stone and deep greenery of the overgrown jungle. There were no wheels, making it something of a hovercraft RV. The boulevards of the overgrown streets were wide, but thick with jungle, making them impassable for the huge vehicle. Jason had moved it back and forth a little, but there really wasn't room to drive around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The interior was likewise akin to a luxurious RV, with beds, couches and comfortable chairs. There actually was a roof deck. From the inside, translucent mist made for clear windows, although they could not be seen through from the outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well," Humphrey consoled, "it'll be nice once we're back out of the astral space. "It'll be great for taking long trip so you, me and Clive can visit locations to portal to, later. That's what my mother did all through bronze rank. Travelling the world, having adventures."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Actually, that sounds kind of awesome. Neil doesn't get an opening credit until season two, though, and it'll be an 'also starring' with his face hidden by a melon or something."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can figure it out later," Jason said. "I guess I should turn it back into a house, and then finish up. What do you say, fellas? Saving the best for last?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gordon appeared with a flash of Jason's aura as Shade appeared from his shadow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gordon says that I should be last," Shade said. Gordon orange orb flashed brightly, which was his signal for no.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"See?" Shade asked. "He really doesn't want to go last."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The orange orb started angrily strobing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He's quite vociferous on the topic," Shade continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shade, stop teasing Gordon," Jason said. "Gordon, it's just an expression. Being last doesn't actually mean you're the best."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A small patch of blood seeped from Jason's neck, turning into a leech that crawled along his shoulder. Jason turned to look at it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Colin, you've already ranked up. You can't do it again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disconsolate leech slinked back into Jason's neck.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">500123</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 23:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 234: Crossing the Threshold</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/499701</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The team waited for the sound of grinding stone that would signal another wave of combat, but the room was as silent as Neil, under Jason's baleful glare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think we're clear," Humphrey said, finally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team stopped to rest in the zone of clean air Sophie's power had finishing clearing out, while the poison mist in the rest of the room slowly dispersed. As the haze disappeared, it revealed a horror show of dead creatures piled around the broken remains of the constructs they had destroyed earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil tried looting the enemies, but while the constructs yielded a few crafting materials, the creatures yielded nothing. They also didn't disappear into rainbow smoke, showing them to not be monsters, but real creatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These things have been sealed away for who knows how long," Neil said. "Kind of like those priests that Jason set loose."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My interface called them Tartarian Brutes," Jason said. "The constructs were Tartarian Golems. Does that mean something to anyone?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All eyes turned to Clive, who shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In my world," Jason said, "there's a myth about a realm called Tartarus. It's a prison realm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We do seem to be in a prison," Belinda said. "It makes me curious about what's behind these doors."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Neil had been looting, Clive had been examining the doors. He started drawing magic diagrams on them in golden lines with his ritual power. Jason noted that, unlike the attempts of the adventurers that came before, they were being placed in the middle of the doors, rather than around the locks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're not trying to crack the locks?" he asked Clive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those are a decoy," Clive said. "A key tip for ritual magic – and life, really – is to not do the same thing as the people who died trying. Also, a twin-circle ritual is a very bad idea if you don't know what you're doing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive completed the ritual, the two magical circles lighting up on the door. The red light shining from underneath faded away and there was a pair of audible clicks from the locks. Clive dismissed his glowing ritual circles with a wave of his hands and pushed on the doors, swinging them open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond was a circular chamber with a vaulted ceiling and only one feature. In the middle of the room was a stone plinth, on which was what looked like a solid block of crystal encasing a sword. Around the block of crystal was a sphere of shimmering light, the same gold, silver and blue produced by Jason's transcendent damage powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sword in the block was elaborately crafted into a sinister form. The blade was some kind of black metal, engraved with glowing red runes down its length. The hilt was constructed of some manner of red crystal and black stone, like ruby and onyx. The grip had sharp thorns, meaning that anyone who grasped it would be stabbing their own hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It kind of looks like Jason's dagger," Neil said. Jason conjured his dagger into his hand, holding up for the group to compare. Jason's dagger was likewise an ornate object of black obsidian and red crystal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're not wrong," Jason said. "It has to be coincidence, though right? I mean, if you're making a sweet-looking red and black bladed weapon, they're all going to end up with a certain level of similarity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do those runes on the blade mean anything?" Sophie asked. Jason and Clive both had translation powers, so they looked closer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They don't say anything coherent," Jason said. "They just represent various concepts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not ideal concepts, either," Clive added. "Soul. Power. Hunger. Life. Feast."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That does sound pretty bad," Neil said. "As in, Jason's powers bad."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm more interested in that energy around it," Clive said. "It seems very strange to both aura and magical senses."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It looks like Jason's dissolve people into nothing powers," Sophie said. "I'm not going near it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Agreed," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason turned his attention to the shimmering light, slowly moving closer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Be careful," Humphrey warned, but Jason instead extended a hand toward the light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Jason, you should give me time to examine that before doing anything rash," Clive said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason ignored them, having felt something familiar about the energy. As his fingertips came in contact with it, a bolt of sensation rocketed through his body and he yanked his arm back, like it had been shocked. He stumbled back a couple of steps before righting himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a soul," Jason said, his voice haunted. "This light is a disembodied soul, somehow held here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you sure?" Clive asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Completely."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive scratched his head as he looked at the light in confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That shouldn't even be possible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm increasingly convinced that impossible isn't a thing," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, someone has turned an actual, living soul into a box?" Humphrey asked. "Isn't that a lot to keep people away from a sword?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It isn't trying to keep things out," Jason said. "It's trying to keep something in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you sure?" Clive said. "Even with enhanced aura senses, it's like there's something obscuring it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can touch it, if you like," Jason said. "I wouldn't advise it, though. It's much higher rank than we are. At least gold, and possibly even diamond. Just coming into contact with it had quite the spiritual kick, but its purpose was immediately clear. Everything it is has been directed to a singular intent: keeping this sword exactly where it is."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm going to touch it," Clive said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just be warned," Jason said. "It's going to kick you right in the soul."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Maybe you shouldn't," Humphrey suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have to," Clive said. "Call it a spirit of enquiry. I'd rather go through whatever punch-back it will give me than live my life knowing I had the chance to experience something so rare and unique, but didn't have the courage."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive reached out his hand and, after a brief moment of hesitation, touched the light. The breath shot out of him and he toppled like a tree, falling to the ground, unconscious. Neil quickly dropped to one knee to examine him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He's fine," Neil quickly said. "He just had a jolt to the system, causing some soul-body dysphoria. Best to let it settle than try and forcibly wake him up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That soul-body thing sounds bad," Sophie said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"On a regular person it would be," Neil said as he pulled a pillow from his dimensional satchel and placed it under Clive's head. "For an essence user, it's kind of like holding your breath for too long and passing out. He's going to wake up with a fierce headache, but nothing more than that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team gathered around Clive, looking down at him with concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Really, he'll be fine," Neil said. "It won't take him long to wake up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Alright," Belinda said. "I guess we decide what to do about this sword while we wait."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't so anything," Jason said. "Someone or something went to considerable effort to contain it here. All that stuff we fought in the cell block was little more than a no trespassing sign compared to the power involved with this. If someone went to the trouble of doing this to a person's soul, just to keep this thing locked up, I don't think letting it loose is a good idea. Even assuming we can figure out how."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, after all the fighting we did to get here, you just want to walk away?" Belinda asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes," Jason said. "That's exactly what I want to do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm willing to take Jason's advice on that," Humphrey said. "Sophie, Neil?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, I was happy to leave it there when I saw that fact that the handle stabs you," Neil said. "That's tells you all you need to know about the kind of weapon it is."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's not as if we're even looking for a sword," Sophie said. "You conjure yours, Humphrey, and you're not giving up the one Gary made, right Asano?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Exactly right," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That just leaves you, Lindy," Sophie said. "It might not hurt to have some good equipment for your turn into a warrior power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No thanks," Belinda said. "I'll stick with weapons that only stab the other guy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive groaned loudly as he gained consciousness. He groggily sat up, gripped his head in his hands and let out another coughing groan. Neil dropped back down to examine him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How do you feel?" Neil asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Like someone dropped a sailing ship on me," Clive said, looking past Neil to Jason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How did you avoid that thing hitting your soul like a hammer?" Clive asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I didn't," Jason said. "I did warn you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I wish I had your resilience of soul," Clive said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No," Jason said flatly. "You don't."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We've decided to leave the sword where it is," Humphrey said to Clive. "Unless you're looking to reopen the debate."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No," Clive said, shaking his had and then wincing at the pain it brought. "I felt that soul. What it went through to put that thing there and keep it there. I'm not even sure we could get that sword out, but I am very sure that we shouldn't."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil and Jason were meditating outside where the cloud house had been set up. They were both anticipating an ascension to bronze-rank after the battle in the cell block and didn't want to make a mess inside. The cloud house would be able to clear it up, but doing so would just accelerate the rate at which it would consume the supply of crystal wash Jason had fed into it. It had been a huge amount and should be sufficient for years, but there was no point accelerating the consumption when it wasn't necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil's summoning power was his last remaining iron-rank ability. The golem had fought like a champion in their most recent conflict, so no one was surprised when Neil crossed the threshold into bronze. He wandered out from the secluded bit of ruin where he had finished his advancement, having washed himself down with a bottle of crystal wash after purging all the muck from his body in the transition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had stripped down to his underwear, so his waiting teammates could see that his blocky, weight-lifter physique had clearly changed to one of more sleek, yet still built-up muscle. It had also made his hair fall out and his fingernails grow strangely long. Jason helped remedy those minor issues with grooming scissors and some of Jory's hair growth cream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's change did not come that day, but Humphrey designated a day for rest. It was something they had done around once a week, taking a break from the otherwise unrelenting schedule of training and combat. They had killed more monsters than it was worth bothering to count, although they had been counting the flesh abominations. They had found and destroyed forty-one of the abominations thus far, which Shade's numbers put at around a tenth of the city's total.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shade's familiar power advanced ahead of Gordon's, the shadow Jason's most constant companion. Jason had come to rely on his shadowy presence, available even when an apocalypse monster or an interdimensional reality assassin were socially inappropriate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;All [Dark Essence] abilities have reached [Bronze 0].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Linked attribute [Speed] has increased from [Iron 9] to [Bronze 0].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's power attribute had reached bronze over the course of their time in the astral space, taking his strength officially beyond what any normal human was capable of. It was the transition of his speed attribute that really made his feel like he had truly transformed, however. It affected not just his ability to run fast, but his reflexes, agility, dexterity and proprioception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His newly ascended speed attribute also combined with his power attribute to make him capable of incredible feats. When he really should have gone back to meditation, his team found him doing somersaults on the spot and climbing up ruins by jumping from wall to wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I feel like a video game character!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No one knows what that means," Sophie said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You've been able to move like this for as long as I've known you," Jason told her. "How are you not constantly running around and giggling like an idiot?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should have seen her when she was younger," Belinda confided, getting a glare from Sophie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason finally settled down and resumed his meditation, after which it did not take long before Gordon's power likewise crossed the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;All [Doom Essence] abilities have reached [Bronze 0].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Linked attribute [Spirit] has increased from [Iron 9] to [Bronze 0].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Progress to bronze rank: 100% (4/4 essences complete).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;All your attributes have reached bronze rank.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have reached bronze rank.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have gained resistance to iron-rank and lower damage sources and effects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;The potency of your aura has increased.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Your aura senses have improved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Progress to silver rank: 00%.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's transition from iron to bronze rank was much less violent that from normal to iron. That time, his newly created body had been composed of what Clive called trash magic, while his iron-rank one was closer to an ideal state for his rank. It still purged a large quantity of black, stinking biomass, however, that he washed off with crystal wash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He trimmed his suddenly grown nails and regrew his hair with the cream, leaving his beard to grow back on its own. Humphrey and Clive had both grown beards during their time in the astral space, likewise losing them during their rank-ups. Neil, being an elf, had never grown more than a light scruff that Jason found enviably appealing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason really did feel transformed. He was a new man and he felt it. Just moving around in his bronze-rank body felt different. His spirit attribute reaching bronze also had a big impact as it increased not just the sixth sense that detected auras but took his other five senses beyond the bounds of human potential. The world was suddenly alive with a nuance of colour like nothing he had experienced. He could pick out scents like he was cataloguing them and his hearing could pick out the world around him almost as well as his vision. He could feel the air on his skin, taste it on his tongue. It was as if the world had transformed with him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good, right?" Humphrey asked with a smile as he found Jason looking into the distance with a goofy grin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, yeah."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can handle monsters, or equivalent, of higher rank than us in large numbers, now," Humphrey said. "Remember those teams we saw at the mirage arena in Jayapura? We can stand shoulder to shoulder with any of them, now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some people might think that means we can relax a little," Jason asked. "Something tells me that you think it means we have to train even harder."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can confidently say that we're at an elite level for our rank," Humphrey said. "That's not such a big deal at iron rank, though. If we're going to say the same at bronze and silver, we need to start the work now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You know, Humphrey, the parents of every girlfriend you ever have are going to love you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do they think of you?" Humphrey asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I haven't gotten that far too many times," Jason said. "There was my first girlfriend, whose parents liked my brother more. Which worked out, in the end. Everyone between her and Cassandra was more casual. Thalia Mercer liked me. Her husband, not so much, I think. The thing with Thadwick, you know."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was always uneasy about Gabrielle's parents," Humphrey said. "Religious is good, but some people take it to a point that it gets a little unnerving."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Putting aside the religious being good thing, I know what you mean," Jason said. "You get those really religious people with that weird intensity, you know?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh yeah," Humphrey said. "I mean, the goddess of knowledge. It should be a fairly relaxed group, right? They kept asking me what I was reading. They did not like hearing that I didn't have a lot of time to read with all the training. Speaking of which, we will be getting back to it. A few days to let you and Neil get a feel for your new power level. Then we'll go after the blood weaver and see what we can find from what's left of the cultists."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Alright," Jason said. "I have some stuff to do before that, though. Growth items, familiar summoning. Basically, a bunch of rituals. Neil has his growth items, too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can take tomorrow," Humphrey said. "After that, though, it's back to work."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">499701</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 23:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 233: I'm Sick of Fighting Magic Rocks</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/499149</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The now-familiar sound of grinding stone echoed through the cell block. The first time, it had been small holes in the walls and ceiling. The second, large holes in the floor. The group looked around for the new source of the grating noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's coming from the cells," Humphrey said. "All the cells."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team looked through the rusty bars and spotted apertures that had appeared in the floor behind them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How many cells are there?" Sophie asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Twelve cells to a side, per level; two levels to each side," Belinda said. "Almost fifty, all up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How can stuff rise up from the floors of the upper cells?" Neil asked. "They'd just come from the ones below, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dimensional spaces," Belinda said. "Like the powers you and I got from the Reaper stones, Neil."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In each cell, a large glass box rose up from the floor. All of them were filled with a sickly yellow fog, from which the team could sense the auras within, currently in a dormant state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those are bronze-rank auras," Sophie said. "Are we ready for that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have to be," Humphrey said. "So, yes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood red light shone over their feet and they turned to see it was shining under the large doors they had used to trigger the room's defences in the first place. It seemed to be a trigger for whatever was inside the glass cases as the team felt the auras within them surge into wakefulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Time to even out the numbers a little," Humphrey said, producing a bag of chalk dust and hurriedly pouring out a circle. He took out his summoner's die and rolled it on the floor, the face up rune glowing as it came to a stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh no," Humphrey said as five large fish made of carved bone were summoned into being and started, flopping helplessly on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The fish again?" Jason said. "Maybe you shouldn't be rolling the dice on the important fights. Literally and figuratively."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a one in twelve chance," Humphrey said. Rather than have his helpless summons underfoot he dismissed them and they vanished. Neil's summon was still present, the crystalline golem maintaining its more advanced, post-chrysalis form. Leaner and more agile than its basic shape, it had four arms ending in fists capable of powerful vibration attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do we go smash those glass cases?" Neil asked. "We'd have to kick our way through the bars, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I suspect whatever is in there will come to us," Jason said. "If you want to go into a prison cell where some unknown creature is about to burst out, though, be my guest. Actually, you're the healer. You have to stay here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sound of shattering glass signalled that their thus-far unknown enemies were about to make an appearance. The sickly-looking smoke that had been in the glass boxes came pouring out through the cell bars. The volume of it suggested that either the fog had been incredibly compressed in the glass cases or it was being continually fed through wherever the glass cases had arisen from. It obscured the team's vision of the cell interiors as they heard the bars start to swing open with reluctant, rusty shrieks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The creatures that emerged from the smoke were roughly humanoid; broad, heavy and hairless, with dark, scaly skin. Their arms were longer and more powerful than their legs, ending in thick, three-fingered hands. They had tiny, sunken eyes and nostrils in flat, noiseless faces. Their wide mouths were filled with misshapen teeth, like fragments of shattered, yellow stone. They pushed their way through cell doors barely large enough to fit them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They don't look weak," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The smoke thinned as is moved into the room ahead of the creatures, filling the cell block with an unpleasant haze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Poison cloud had inflicted you with [Breath of Tartarus].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have resisted [Breath of Tartarus].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have gained an instance of [Resistant].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have gained an instance of [Integrity].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason looked to his companions with concern. They were more vulnerable than he was, not sharing the power to grow stronger from afflictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Sin Eater] (Sin)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special ability (recovery, holy).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Increased resistance to afflictions. Gain an instance of [Resistant] each time you resist an affliction or cleanse an affliction using essence abilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Gain an instance of [Integrity] for each affliction you resist or remove using essence abilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Resistant] (boon, holy, stacking): Resistance to afflictions is increased. Additional instances have a cumulative effect. Consumed to negate instances of [Vulnerable] on a 1:1 basis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Integrity] (heal-over-time, mana-over-time, stamina-over-time, holy, stacking): Periodically recover a small amount of health, stamina and mana. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rest of the team were not completely vulnerable, with Sophie and Jason's auras both shielding them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Cleansing Breeze] (Swift)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Aura (holy, cleanse).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Allies within the aura have increased resistance to curses, diseases, magic afflictions, poisons and unholy afflictions. This is a holy effect. Negates poisons in the air; this is a cleanse effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Allies within the aura are periodically cleansed of curses, diseases, magic afflictions, poisons and unholy afflictions. Mana and stamina recovery effects on allies have greater effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleansing breeze was one of the precious few powers that had reached bronze for Sophie, accelerated by a preponderance of poisonous monsters in the city. Thorny plant monsters, spitting frog monsters, snake monsters. The team had a good amount of cleansing between them, which made such creatures easy pickings, as well as helping them accelerate the advancement of those powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the case of Sophie's aura, it would slowly but surely cleanse many types of affliction from her allies. It was already purifying the fog around them and, added to Jason's aura, left the team in relatively good stead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Hegemony] (Sin)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Aura (holy, unholy).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Base cost: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Allies within the aura have increased resistance to afflictions, while enemies within the aura have their resistance to afflictions reduced. Enemy resistances are further reduced for each instance of [Sin] they are suffering from.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Inflicts an instance of [Sin] on enemies that make physical or magical attacks against allies within the aura. Instances applied in this way cannot be resisted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belinda, Sophie and Neil suffered the worst, their iron-rank constitutions struggling against the poison even with the powers bolstering their resistance. Jason clasped a hand on Neil's shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Feed me your sins."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red life force emerged from Neil, tainted by the same colour as the mist. The taint disappeared into Jason's hand, leaving Neil looking relieved as his now-healthy life force returned to his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Feast of Absolution] (Sin)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (recovery, cleanse, holy).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Base cost: Low mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Cleanse all curses, diseases, poisons and unholy afflictions from a single target. Additionally cleanse all holy afflictions if the target is an ally. Recover stamina and mana for each affliction cleansed. This ability ignores any effect that prevents cleansing. Cannot target self.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Enemies suffer an instance each of [Penance] and [Legacy of Sin] for each condition cleansed from them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Penance] (affliction, holy, damage-over-time, stacking): Deals ongoing transcendent damage. Additional instances have a cumulative effect, dropping off as damage is dealt.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Legacy of Sin] (affliction, holy, stacking): You are considered more damaged for the purposes of execute ability damage scaling. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this was going on, some of the monsters had already moved in to the attack. The team had their backs to the large doors, so the monsters wouldn't be able to flank them, although they would be able to drop down from above. While Sophie stepped forward with Neil's golem to hold off the first wave of attackers, Humphrey vaulted up to the mezzanine on their left with a flap of conjured dragon wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey engaged with one of the creatures that had been about to drop down. It's lengthy arms gave it reach, and the knobbly scales running along them made those arms as tough as any weapon. The monster may not have been a match for Humphrey but it was still disconcertingly strong and tough, given how many they knew to be gathering, unseen in the poison haze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason used his magic boots to leap up to the mezzanine on the other side, likewise engaging a monster. He inflicted a rapid series of slashes, the creature's reach no match for that of Jason's shadowy arm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Hand of the Reaper] (Dark)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Conjuration (disease, unholy).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana-per-second.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Conjure a highly flexible, semi-substantial shadow-arm that can extend or shrink. Conjured items can be conjured into the shadow hand. Can be used to make melee special attacks. Special attacks made using the arm inflict [Creeping Death] in addition to other effects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): You can conjure a second arm. Special attacks made using the arms inflict [Rigor Mortis] in addition to other effects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Creeping Death] (damage-over-time, disease, stacking): Inflicts ongoing necrotic damage until the disease is cleansed. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Rigor Mortis] (affliction, unholy, stacking): Penalty to the [Speed] and [Recovery] attributes. Additional instances have a cumulative effect. Each time a new instance is inflicted, deals necrotic damage for each existing instance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason's dagger barely drew blood from the scaly skin, but all Jason needed were shallow cuts. With just a few slashes, more than a dozen afflictions were loaded onto the monster. Jason's conjured dagger was the source of many, but not all of them, such as the special attack he was using.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Punish] (Sin)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special attack (melee, curse, holy).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Inflicts necrotic damage and the [Sin] affliction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Inflicts or refreshes the duration of [Price of Absolution].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Sin] (affliction, curse, stacking): All necrotic damage taken is increased. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Price of Absolution] (affliction, holy): Suffer transcendent damage for each instance of [Sin] cleansed from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither Jason nor the creature were going to wait for the afflictions to slowly devour it. It lunged at Jason, although its relatively short legs and the afflictions it already suffered from made it a little slow. Jason easily stepped into one of Shade's bodies and out from another that had slipped past the creature while it was engaged with Jason, giving him plenty of time to cast a quick spell before the creature turned around to face him again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Suffer the cost of your transgressions."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Punition] (Doom)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Moderate mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 30 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Inflicts necrotic damage for each curse, disease, poison and unholy affliction the target is suffering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Inflicts or refreshes the duration of [Penitence].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Penitence] (affliction, holy): Gain an instance of [Penance] for each curse, disease, poison or unholy effect that is cleansed from you. This is a holy effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Penance] (affliction, holy, damage-over-time, stacking): Deals ongoing transcendent damage. Additional instances have a cumulative effect, dropping off as damage is dealt.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The creature staggered as its muscles withered with necrosis, even as its wounds glowed with the transcendent damage starting to ravage it from the inside out. It lunged at Jason again with no more effect, Jason easily able to move from one of Shade's bodies to the other like a bully playing keep-away. He cast another spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Feed me your sins."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The creatures life force became visible, tainted with the storm of affliction within it. Ugly curses, poisons and other horrors Jason inflicted swirled about with the shining transcendence of holy afflictions until they were drained out, siphoned off into Jason's outstretched hand. Even more of the holy afflictions were left in their place as the creature's life force once again became unseen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;18 afflictions have been cleansed from [Tartarian Brute].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;36 Instances of [Penance] have been inflicted on [Tartarian Brute].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;18 Instances of [Legacy of Sin] have been inflicted on [Tartarian Brute].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Your mana and stamina have been replenished.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Stamina and mana cannot exceed normal maximum values. Excess stamina and mana are lost.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brute stumbled to a halt as the transcendent damage devastated its body, lighting it up from the inside like some divine being, alighted upon the earth. Jason tilted his head as he watched the creature, one of the few he had encountered capable of surviving this far into his ability sequence. He chanted the incantation for the coup de grâce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Mine is the judgement, and the judgement is death."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Verdict] (Doom)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (execute)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Moderate mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 30 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Deals a small amount of transcendent damage. As an execute effect, damage scales exponentially with the enemy's level of injury.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Base damage is increased for each instance of [Penance] on the target.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The penance afflictions on the creature increased the base damage of the execute power, while the legacy of sin affliction made the damage escalation ramp up much faster. The multiplicative affect of the two affliction stacks made for a shower of transcendent light that left behind not so much as a drop of blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason had never killed something that tough that quickly, but of course Humphrey had already finished his first and was making short work of a second. Another brute came lumbering out of the poison fog and Jason just raised his hand. Blood seeped from his palm for a short moment, after which a torrent of leeches came spraying out over the creature. Jason paid it no more attention and leapt from his side of the room over the gap to Humphrey on the opposite mezzanine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can you drop these upper levels at this end, so they can't drop down on the team?" Jason asked as Humphrey kicked a dead brute off his sword.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey gave the brick floor beneath them an assessing glance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yeah. You want to go backs to the wall and let them come to us?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, but we can't have them fall on our heads either," Jason said. "You keep the others safe while Neil and Sophie hold the poison at bay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And what about the room full of monsters and poison gas?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shade emerged from Jason's shadow as Gordon manifested with a surge of his aura. Jason glanced across at Colin, now bound up in his bloody-cloth humanoid shape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sick of fighting magic rocks," Jason said. "You can leave this lot to us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophie's aura was thinning out the gas in the area immediately surrounding the team and would soon have it cleansed entirely. Humphrey had used his shield breaker attack to shatter the mezzanine at their end of the room, so the creatures were only able to come at them at ground level, from one direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophie, Humphrey and Neil's golem beat them back, assisted by Clive and his magical weapons. Neil watched over the whole group but made sure to keep a careful eye on Belinda, who was suffering the most from the gas not yet fully cleared out. Whenever it started to get the best of her, he would purge it from her with a spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Clean Slate] (Prosperity)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (cleanse, heal-over-time, holy).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Moderate mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 30 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Negate boons on a willing subject. Cleanse target of afflictions of all types except wounding. The base strength of the cleanse effect is enhanced for each boon negated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Target gains a heal-over-time effect that had additional effectiveness against wounding afflictions. The strength of the healing effect is increased for each boon negated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the haze of poison fog, the team saw flashes of transcendent light and heard horrifying screams. They could only assume they came from the creatures because it definitely wasn't Jason's voice, although none of the creatures Humphrey and Sophie cut down had made so much as a grunt as they died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first the brutes surged in on them but slowly their numbers petered out. Finally, the last one to appear was in such a miserable state of decomposition that it looked like a zombie, complete with staggering shamble as it emerged from the fog before falling onto what was left of its face. A bloody strip of cloth snaked out of the fog, wrapping around its leg and dragging it back out of sight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next thing to come out of the fog were four cloaked figures; Jason, flanked by his familiars. He looked the team over, nodded as he saw they were fine, and his gaze turned to the large doors behind them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's say we see what's back there?"&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">499149</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 23:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 232: Stalwart</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/498730</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The spider constructs had appeared from holes that had opened in the walls and ceiling. This time, it was the floor that opened up, six large, evenly-spaced but much larger holes, appearing in a straight line down the length of the cell block. The team didn't wait for whatever was within to emerge, springing straight into action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll take the first, you the second," Clive said to Belinda and they both quickly chanted out their rune trap spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Emplace the mark of power."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Runes appeared on the floor, in front of the first and second holes. They glowed brightly for a brief moment before vanishing. As they cast their spells, Humphrey vaulted into the air, a pair of dragon wings appearing on his back and pushing him upwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Dragon Wings] (Wing)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Conjuration (movement).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High mana-per-second.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (01%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Manifest wings that are powerful but lack agility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): The strength and resilience of the wings is increased, allowing them to be used for crude attacks to the sides and rear. The wings have strong damage resistance and very strong fire resistance. Ongoing mana cost is reduced from very high to high.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey alighted on the upper mezzanine level, letting the mana-hungry wings vanish again. Sophie sauntered forward, ready to meet whatever emerged, while Jason vanished into the shadows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil had been hastily pouring salt from a small sack to make a circle. He knelt briefly and touched a finger to the circle when it was done. The salt crystals started sparkling like flecks of diamond in the sun before a dervish of crystal appeared above the circle, swiftly cohering into the shape of Neil's summon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Chrysalis Golem] (Growth)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Summoning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Very high mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 6 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 9 (97%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Summons a chrysalis golem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The golem was a large, humanoid edifice of translucent crystal, half as tall again as its summoner. Neil gestured it forward, where it positioned itself between the team's support contingent and the holes from which the enemy was about to emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From each hole, a single figure rose up from below. Like Neil's golem, they were constructs, ascending on platforms that sealed the holes from which they came. They also shared the golem's intimidating size, but not its humanoid appearance These new constructs had a body that was a vertical cylinder of plain, dark stone. From the base, four legs held it up, obviously build for stability over speed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equidistant at cardinal points around the middle of the cylinder were long, inhuman arms. Each arm was segmented with a pair of elbows that allowed them to move in uncanny gestures. The arms ended in blunted, four-fingered claws. Atop each cylinder, in place of a head, was a stone bowl. As the constructs rose up, spheres of magical force manifested into each bowl, shimmering like a soap bubbles, and the constructs began to move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like all constructs, they didn't have a soul and their auras were the meagre product of the magic animating them. It was enough to let the team know their opponents were somewhere in the mid-range of bronze-rank power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two sides were moving on each other before the platforms bringing the constructs up had even completed their task. Sophie was the quickest, ignoring the first two constructs to go after the third, rapidly hammering attacks into the joints of its arms. The movement of the arms was quick and tricky, but Sophie's reflexes were up to the task. As it continued to rise up, she went after the leg joints as well. The effectiveness of her attacks was limited, but the resonating-force damage of her special ability did succeed in chipping away at the hard stone of the leg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Immortal Fist] (Mystic)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special ability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 8 (21%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Unarmed attacks deal additional resonating-force damage, which is highly effective against physical defences. Suffer no damage from making unarmed strikes against objects and negate all damage from actively intercepted attacks. Not all damage from very powerful or higher-ranked attacks will be negated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two constructs she had passed stepped over the edge of their holes before the platforms they rode reached the level of the floor to seal them. They moved forward towards the main group, only to walk over the now-invisible runes, which detonated as they did so. The explosion was not enough to knock the heavy creatures over but they were successful in causing enough damage to have cracks appear in their legs. This was most true of the closest construct, which had walked over Clive's trap. It suffered the full effect of the bronze-rank power, then the secondary explosion on afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Rune Trap] (Rune)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 1 minute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (03%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Create an explosive rune that will disappear after a short period. The rune can be set to trigger by proximity, caster trigger, or both.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Enemies affected by the rune trap will be the source of a secondary explosion after a brief period.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second construct was not much more than briefly staggered by Belinda's trap, but Humphrey made the most of the immobile target. He plummeted down like a meteor, stacking up powers into a single, potent attack. He started by invoking one of his racial gifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Dragon Blood]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Transfigured from [Human] ability [Essence Gift].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Power] and [Spirit] attributes are enhanced for moderate mana-per-second.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;His dragon wings appeared onne again as he plunged from above, driving him forcefully towards his target below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Dive Bomb] (Wing)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special attack (movement, combination).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High stamina.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 20 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (02%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Accelerate down to attack a target from above; can be combined with normal or special melee attacks. Physical damage from these attacks is increased. No falling damage is suffered when using this ability, even if the attack misses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): A resonating-force shockwave is produced from the impact point.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another of Humphrey's racial gifts further enhanced the power of his attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Wing Raider]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Transfigured from [Human] ability [Essence Gift].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Speed, momentum and damage of movement-type special attacks is increased. Heavy conjured weapons and armour do not increase stamina consumption, regardless of weight, and do not impede movement abilities. Light conjured weapons have increased weight and momentum without being heavier to wield, counting as heavy weapons for the purposes of special attack requirements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dive bomb would do damage alone, but as it was a combination special attack, Humphrey added another power that would be especially effective against the construct.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Shield Breaker] (Might)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana, moderate stamina.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 10 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (04%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Inflicts additional resonating-force damage, highly effective against physical defences. Requires a heavy weapon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Damage to rigid material is significantly increased.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Humphrey plunged through the air, the sphere that had formed in the monster's strange bowl head floated up to intercept him. It grew as it moved into his path, large enough to engulf his whole body. Humphrey passed through the sphere, which popped like the soap bubble it resembled. It had not so much as slowed him down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have been trapped in [Sphere of Incarceration].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Sphere of Incarceration] has triggered ability [Unstoppable].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Sphere of Incarceration] has been destroyed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a team full of unconventional members, it was easy to overlook Humphrey and his powers that were as straightforward as Humphrey himself. What he brought to the team was something that they otherwise lacked: simple, reliable power. When Humphrey Geller wanted to attack you, you were getting attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Unstoppable]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Transfigured from [Human] ability [Essence Gift].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Movement abilities cannot be negated or impaired. Resonating-force damage and disruptive-force damage are imparted to any obstructing object, increased for each movement ability and special attack in effect. This is a movement effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey came down on the construct like the United States military on an oil-rich nation. His assault from above was domineering, overwhelming and inflicted a level of widespread damage that went way beyond his expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The initial strike smashed right through the stone bowl and burying itself deep in the cylindrical body. The construct was riddled with cracks and half destroyed, a job finished by the dive bomb attack's secondary shock wave. It freed Humphrey's sword as the construct was blasted into shrapnel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Humphrey destroyed the second construct Sophie continued to tie up the third. It tried to catch her with its own sphere, but her speed and mobility powers allowed her to nimbly avoid it, even as her attacks continued, unabated. The closest she came to being caught was when she looked back as fragments of the construct behind her explosively showered her with shrapnel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of her construct's legs gave out beneath her unrelenting attacks, but it continued to fight back with the lengthy, multi-jointed arms that tried to slam her into the floor. Some attacks she blocked, others she neatly side-stepped, all the while continuing her own assault. She was able to more than hold her own against her bronze-rank enemy, but it remained a dangerous opponent. She was all too aware that getting caught up fighting just one meant she was not protecting the team from the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophie and Humphrey had left one construct between them and the bulk of the team, which was intercepted by Neil's summon. Although the two constructs were of a similar size, the bronze-rank enemy quickly began to overpower the summon. It started by using two of its four clawed hands to grab the chrysalis golem's arms, holding them out of the way as a third claw hammered away on the golem's crystalline body. With each blow, a new rune appeared on the myriad facets of the chrysalis golem, even as it struggled, ineffectually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this was going on, Neil watched in silence, primed to throw out any necessary shields and healing for his teammates. Belinda was likewise actively prepared to support the team, as needed. Clive in contrast was drawing a ritual circle at the end of his staff, lines of golden light appearing at a wave of his finger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Enact Ritual] (Rune)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special ability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: varies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (09%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Manifest lines of magic to draw out ritual diagrams. Materials required for a ritual may be used directly from a dimensional storage space instead of being placed within the diagram.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Create simple ritual diagrams to alter the parameters of magical items.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quickly completed, the ritual circle floated in the air, affixed by an invisible force to the end of his staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;You have altered the effect of [Spell Lance of the Magister]. Damage has been altered from disruptive-force to resonating-force.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disruptive-force of his staff attacks were highly-effective against magic and adequate for most enemies, but would suffer against the hard and tough bodies of the constructs. The time it cost him to alter his weapons would be made up for in the effectiveness of their new, temporary damage type. He left his wand unchanged, however, as he was wary of the magic spheres the constructs each had. His senses could clearly make out their magical nature, which his wand's original damage would be effective against.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the construct continued to hammer away at the chrysalis golem, its sphere floated out to hover over the golem's head. The construct's final arm rose from behind its main body to touch the sphere, which started to vibrate and grow. Clive immediately directed the beam of his wand to lock onto the sphere, while his staff repeatedly fired bolts into the construct's body. The magical bolts exploded on contact, also affecting the chrysalis golem. The damage caused new runes to form on the golem's body. The sphere above the Golem continued to grow but the disruptive power of the wand slowed that growth to a crawl.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the far end of the cell, the distance from the rest of the team and the glow stones they carried made the shadowy darkness a playground for Jason. He danced among the last three constructs, an elusive, flickering shadow. The disadvantage was that his only viable source of damage was his sword, which would take time to build up enough power to be an effective threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Item: [Dread Salvation] (iron rank [growth], legendary)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A sword crafted with gratitude, in hope it would be of the greatest use in the moment of greatest need. It was forged with passion and expertise to be a reliable companion, bestowing upon it an incredible potential&lt;/em&gt; (weapon, sword).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: If a special attack that applies an affliction is made with this sword, but the subject of the attack has a physical immunity to it, an instance of [Stone Cutter] is applied to the blade.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect: If a special attack that applies an affliction is made with this sword, but the subject of the attack has a magical immunity to it, an instance of [Spell Breaker] is applied to the blade.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Stone Cutter] (magic, stacking): All attacks deal additional resonating-force damage; highly effective against physical defences. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Spell Breaker] (magic, stacking): All attacks deal additional disruptive-force damage; highly effective against magical defences and incorporeal entities. Additional instances have a cumulative effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason moved amongst the constructs like a spirit, doing all he could to hold their attention with his minimal damage. The more he could distract the back half of the enemies, the quicker his allies would deal with the front and move to assist him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special attack [Punish] has inflicted [Sin] and [Price of Absolution] on [Tartarian Golem].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Tartarian Golem] is immune to [Sin].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Sin] does not take effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Affliction immunity has triggered an effect on weapon [Dread Salvation].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Weapon [Dread Salvation] has gained an instance of [Stone Cutter].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Tartarian Golem] is immune to [Price of Absolution].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;[Price of Absolution] does not take effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Affliction immunity has triggered an effect on weapon [Dread Salvation].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Weapon [Dread Salvation] has gained an instance of [Stone Cutter].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until his allies could join move to help, Jason had the assistance of Gordon, whose beam attacks proved more attention-getting than Jason. One beam was disruptive-force, which weakened and eventually broke the magical spheres, forcing the constructs to form new ones. The other beam was resonating force, an effective weapon against the rigid, stone bodies of the constructs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shade had informed Jason that the constructs almost certainly relied on purely magical senses, lacking the sensory organs of a living creature. As Jason had little need of Shade's shadow bodies in the darkened area, Shade posited that he might be able to hide Jason from their senses entirely. For each of Shade's bodies subsumed into Jason's shadow, he could mask an aspect of Jason's presence, such as heat or sound. It apparently also extended to more unusual senses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason declined, however, as he needed to hold the constructs' attention. Their spheres moved around and their arms lashed out, striking nothing but hard floor and empty air. Jason may not have been Sophie's equal, but he had the skills imprinted on him by skill books and consolidate with a year of training and experience. He had become formidable in his own right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three constructs became two as Humphrey moved past Sophie and started hammering on one of them, diverting its attention. He started with the strongest of his special attacks, which rocked the construct back, in spite of its great weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Unstoppable Force] (Might)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High mana, extreme stamina.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 1 minute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (07%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Melee attack with massive momentum, dealing large amounts of additional resonating-force and disruptive-force damage. Requires a heavy weapon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): For each enemy struck the cooldown of this ability and the cost of the next use of this ability are reduced.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;After week after week of almost hourly battles, the team was quick to pick up on one another's rhythms. Belinda was at the ready and immediately reset Humphrey's attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Blessing of Readiness] (Adept)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special ability (recovery).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Base cost: Moderate mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: Varies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 8 (14%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): This spell can only affect an ally and not yourself. The cooldown of the next ability used by the target is reduced by up to one minute. The cooldown of this ability is equal to the time taken from the cooldown of the target ability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using her magical tattoo, she ended the cooldown on her power, allowing it to reset Humphrey's attack a second time. Jason was almost caught in a sphere as he watched, boggle-eyed, as Humphrey pushed around the giant stone monstrosity as if it were a small child. Humphrey finished the construct off with a shield breaker attack, the specialty resonating-force power inflicting even more damage than his unstoppable force attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophie, in the mean time, had neatly disassembled her opponent. Where Humphrey left nothing but ruined chunks, Sophie had taken her golem apart joint by joint and then smashed the bowl, causing the sphere she had been dodging to wink out and not return.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sophie!" Neil called out, and she turned to look. The sphere of the first construct had finally grown large enough to encapsulate Neil's golem, which was suddenly covered in a crystal cocoon within the sphere. Trapped in the sphere and entered into its inert, chrysalis state, the golem was no longer any kind of protector for Belinda, Neil and Clive. Belinda stepped up to buy the time the team needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With her power-resetting abilities expended, Belinda knew it was time to change roles. She starting by summoning a suit of heavy armour, plus a hammer and shield, which blinked into existence on her person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Bag of Tricks] (Magic)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special Ability (dimension).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: None&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 8 (08%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): You have a personal, dimensional storage space. You may equip any item in your storage space directly onto your person or unequip anything on your person directly to your storage space.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;She activated another power that made her grow taller and bulk-out with muscle, her clothes and equipment growing with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Counterfeit Combatant] (Charlatan)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special ability (boon).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 1 minute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 4 (74%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Gain a significant increase to the [Power] attribute and temporary proficiency with armour and melee weaponry. Your physique enlarges, with equipment shifting to match.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;As prepared as she could be, she squared her shoulders and moved to intercept the construct. She was only an iron-rank combatant, however, and a makeshift one at that. This became painfully obvious as she was rapidly pushed back, overwhelmed by the construct's multiple, irregular attacks. Her only saving grace was the construct's sphere was still occupied containing the chrysalis golem. The construct apparently unaware that the golem was in an inert state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophie appeared, moving through the room like a breeze. She took over from a grateful Belinda, who had suffered something of a beating from the many-armed construct. The shields and healing supplied by Neil had been the only thing that let her hold up against the higher-rank enemy even for the short time she had managed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the other end of the cell block, Humphrey moved on one of the now two remaining constructs. They were now ignoring Jason, in spite of the growing power of his sword, rightly recognising the larger threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey could not take the two constructs down as quickly as the first two, needing to wait for his most potent abilities to come off cooldown. His shield breaker attack, fortunately, had a short cooldown, made all the shorter by Belinda's aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Masterful] (Adept)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Aura (recovery).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Base cost: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 7 (55%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Abilities of allies within the aura come off cooldown more quickly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;In between hits with his big-ticket attack, Humphrey fought using another of his special attacks. The human aptitude for special attacks had caused him to awaken an array of them, contributing to his potent offensive capability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Relentless Assault] (Might)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low stamina, increasing with each successive attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (02%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Each use of this attack in quick succession increases the damage of this attack. Damage is of the same type caused by a normal attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): After a threshold of successive attacks is reached, escalating resonating-force damage is dealt with each attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even this back-up attack of Humphrey's started putting paid to the construct he was fighting in relatively short order. He finished it with a shield breaker attack and moved onto the next construct as Jason realised that his contribution to the fight really would be minimal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he and Humphrey engaged the last construct at the back, the remaining one at the front was now squaring off against Sophie. Clive's staff had left it pocked with damage and Sophie was doing the same, but it was the awakening of Neil's golem that signalled the end of that fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The golem explosively emerged from the crystal chrysalis. Shards of razor-sharp crystal shot out wildly, shredding the sphere containing the golem. Revealed in the wake of the detonated cocoon, the golem was leaner than it had been before, now with four arms, like that of its opponent, although more traditionally placed, two to each side of the golem's body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the disappearance of its first glowing sphere the construct created another in it's bowl, which began floating it towards the newly reformed golem. The golem hammered the sphere with a fist and the bubble not only burst, but blasted force back at its creator. As the construct was rocked back on its legs the golem, more agile than before, moved in smoothly to start hammering away with it's fists. The crude, blunt appendages vibrated as they struck, sending shockwaves through the enemy construct.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new and improved chrysalis golem took out its enemy almost as quick as Humphrey, who was finishing the last of the last of the constructs up the back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team regrouped in the middle of the cell block. Clive and Neil enthusiastically told Jason and Humphrey about Belinda's stalwart efforts in buying time for Sophie to come to their aid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Still," Neil said. "Not as bad as we thought, in the end."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Seriously?" Jason asked. "You're doing it again?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The bad thing already came out," Neil said. "What are the odds of there being another…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He trailed off as the cell block filled with the sound of grinding stone.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">498730</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 23:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Who Fights With Monsters - Chapter 231: Trading Safety Today For Death Tomorrow</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/chapter/498242</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The team had been aware going in that there were locations within the city that were more than just empty ruins. A number of trial-goers had reported such locations to the Magic Society and Emir's people, who had undertaken a large-scale debrief of the iron rankers who survived the trials. In addition to monsters unlike those found elsewhere in the city, such locations held unusually valuable treasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive had been one of those who encountered such a place during the trials, where he obtained the legendary set items both he and Neil were wielding. For him it was a staff and wand set that had become a crucial part of his combat potential. For Neil, it was a fist-sized orb that shone with a blue light when held, and a gold circlet with a blue gem set into the forehead. The abilities combined to powerfully enhance his shielding powers, which the team appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the formidable power of the abilities on those items, the team eagerly explored any location that was outside the ordinary. In addition to being as likely as any other place to have monsters to confront, there was always the chance of treasure. With the battles to come, any advantage was a much-needed blessing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most such places were either subterranean complexes or atop unusually tall buildings, much as Clive's had been. The first of these locations the team encountered for themselves was a sprawling complex of underground forges, foundries and furnaces. In addition to having dangerous fire and iron elementals, it was infested with bizarre undead, with metal fused into their bodies like magical cyborgs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason had found it a frustrating place to fight, with most of the enemies highly resistant, if not outright immune to his abilities. He made good use of the sword Gary had given him, but it was a marked step-down in his capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's good for you," Sophie had told him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you only train for when things go right, you die the moment they go wrong," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yeah," Jason acknowledged unhappily. "Rufus used to tell me almost the exact same thing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That place had eventually yielded some impressive treasures, although not so useful as those Clive had found. There was a pair of gloves that enhanced fire and iron-based abilities, and an anvil that enhanced the crafting of weapons. They took them with the intention of delivering them to Gary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The complex had also delivered a solid haul of essences and awakening stones, almost all fire and iron. They were both common, but very popular, meaning they would fetch a good price once they returned to civilisation. They were a welcome addition to the piles of spirit coins and quintessence gems piling up in their storage spaces, courtesy of Jason and Neil's looting powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next similar location they came across was likewise underground. They were uncertain to its nature, at first, as it was very plain, but they could tell it was unusual from how intact it was. Most subterranean spaces in the city were thick with mould and root systems breaking in through the walls and ceiling. This complex was all square tunnels and empty rooms, the brickwork uniform and unblemished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There doesn't seem to be anything here," Belinda said as they looked over another empty room. "No loot, no monsters nesting in here. Not even the dilapidated furniture and such you get in most of the ruins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All these empty rooms remind of the place we found in the delta under the swamp," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's worth remembering," Clive said. "That place seemed empty until we had a face full of marsh hydra."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A good lesson," Humphrey agreed. "This place may well be empty because the one thing in here has scared off the rest."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are we ready to face a silver-rank monster?" Neil asked. "We haven't had to do it yet, but the monsters have been getting stronger and stronger. We hardly see any iron-ranks anymore."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If we caught one in isolation, then maybe," Humphrey said. "The problem is that we still have too many iron-rankers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm so close to bronze I can taste it," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They continued through the complex, finally discovering what it was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A prison," Jason said as he surveyed the latest room they had entered. "That's great. Nothing bad ever happened in a creepy, abandoned, subterranean prison. I'm so glad monsters turned out to be real."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were in a large, long cell block, with a mezzanine level running along each side. The cells, running the length of the room on both levels were barred, giving the team a clear look inside. None of the cells had occupants, being as empty as every other room they had come across. Moving though the large cell block, they found stairs that led down into another, and then a third. It was there that they finally found something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Signs of combat," Clive said. "This really does remind me of that place we found."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is fresher," Humphrey said, examining a scorch mark on the wall. "Most likely, someone found this place during the trials."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's something at the far end of the room," Jason said. His ability to see through darkness extended beyond where the light of the team's glow stones grew dim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team moved forward carefully, finding a handful of corpses scattered about where they had fallen. A violent demise and months in the muggy, underground chamber had not left them is a pleasant state, but as Jason's powers left enemies in much the same condition, they were used to it. Rather than dwell on the state of the bodies, they considered what might have left them that way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No trace of whatever killed them," Jason said. "It seems the fight was either one-sided, or whoever killed them took their own fallen when they left."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hard to determine what killed them from the bodies," Neil said. "They're too far gone to make out much. I am seeing some broken bones, so something physically powerful maybe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We didn't fight anything on the way in here," Sophie said, already eyeing the room around them. "There weren't any signs of combat before this, and I think they would have left some. I'm seeing scorch marks, chunks torn out of the stone floor. I think that whatever killed them didn't show up until they reached this point."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of the team had let up their guard, but for the moment, nothing was making an attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It could have been other adventurers," Jason said. "We know that at least some of us were killing each other."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All we can do is be cautious moving forward," Humphrey said. "That, and collect these poor souls for return to their families."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They went about the grisly task of retrieving Adventure Society badges, for identification and to return to the families. There had been discussion of retrieving remains before they came in, but storage space was at a premium for coffins and any remains were likely to be a mess. A number of families made quiet approaches to try and make specific arrangements for their lost people, but Humphrey flatly refused. He insisted on keeping things even handed and restricting recovery to Adventure Society badges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What about their equipment?" Belinda asked. "It feels ghoulish to loot the dead."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We'll return their gear to the families, along with the remains," Humphrey said. "Once they're identified."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the cell block. Not far past the bodies, was a pair of large doors. They were metal, but unlike the bars of the cells, were unblemished by time and moisture. They were plain and heavy, with a large keyhole on each. There were traces of a ritual circle drawn around each keyhole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Maybe that's what brought out whatever killed them," Jason said. "Trying to break-in triggered some kind of defences, maybe?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The obvious solution, then, would be to not break-in," Neil said. "I mean, treasure is nice, but we just picked up a dead adventuring team. Do we really want to be the next one?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He's not wrong," Jason said. "We have a responsibility, here. We may be the only ones who can stop the cult from tearing this astral space off the side of the world. Or whatever it is they're going to do with those giant golems. We can't go getting ourselves killed over some loot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"On the other hand," Humphrey said, "we need to push ourselves to the limit, and beyond. We don't know what kind of challenges we'll have to face in stopping the cult, but I don't think the cultists being captured by the blood weaver is the end of it. I'm certain there are greater challenges ahead before we can put paid to the cult's intentions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, you're saying we should face whatever killed these people as a training exercise?" Jason asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Since when are you the voice of moderation?" Clive asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not saying we shouldn't do it," Jason said. "I just think that the idea of not doing it is worth exploring. I've been too reckless, too often. I've survived too many times on luck which, sooner or later, is going to run out. This isn't a monster we have some idea about, before we go in. We backed off because we weren't ready for the blood weaver. What if this is worse?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to get you and Neil over the threshold for bronze," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not sure this will do it," Jason said. "If there is a still-active defence system here, then it has to be something that didn't die out in all the years this place has been dormant. My guess would be some kind of construct guardian, or maybe some undead. I won't get to workout my powers like that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your familiars are the last abilities you have to advance," Humphrey said. "If your other abilities are less useful, your familiars become more important."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I say we go for it," Sophie said. "Humphrey's right that we need to have the experience of having something dropped on us that we aren't ready for. Better we experience that now, so we have the experience before the cultists do it to us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you think, Clive?" Humphrey asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clive rubbed his chin, thoughtfully.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The biggest danger is to our iron-rankers," he said. "I think we leave the decision to them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's fair," Humphrey said. "So, what's it going to be?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm still up for it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If Sophie's in, I'm in," Belinda said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm going to say no," Jason said. "If Neil wants to make it three to one, I'm fine with that, but if he wants to play it safe, I'll back him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone turned to Neil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Great," Neil said. "Now it's my fault if everybody dies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're saying go for it?" Jason asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Jason, you weren't there during the expedition," Neil said. "You haven't fought these people. You haven't seen the monstrosities they turned themselves into. The endless sea of constructs at their command. I don't know what they're going to bring to bear against us, but we can't be ready enough. Not taking every chance we have to get stronger is trading safety today for death tomorrow."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And here was I thinking that you were the sensible one," Jason said. "Alright, then. Of course, if we're wrong about the defence mechanisms, this whole conversation was pointless."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision made, Clive turned his attention to the large doors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They messed up their unlocking ritual," Clive said. "Even at a glance I can see how amateurish it was. No wonder they set off any defences."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then do what they did," Jason said. "You can worry about getting it right afterwards."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's not very professional," Clive complained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Being professional isn't the objective, right now," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If the goal isn't to get it right, then you might as well do it," Clive said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's hurtful," Jason said. "But fair enough. Everyone else get ready."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the team gathered in preparation for a fight, Jason examined the doors and the remnant lines of a ritual circle drawn onto each in chalk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You weren't kidding, Clive," Jason said. "Even I can tell this is a dog's breakfast. It looks like someone who barely knew what they were doing just copied this ritual out of a book."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Probably someone who used a ritual magic skill book and never took the time to learn any theory," Clive said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Was that aimed at me?" Jason asked. "I've been hitting the books pretty hard, as you well know."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can you please just get on with it?" Humphrey asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sorry," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason took out a stick of chalk to redraw in the faded lines. He recognised the basic unlocking ritual, which was indeed something that had been in the ritual magic skill book he had used himself. That fortunately meant that he had the ritual incantation memorised, which was somewhat tricky. The chant was one of those that were series a series of sounds rather than words, in and of themselves, meaningless. They simply existed to set up a resonance and begin channelling magic through the ritualist and into the ritual diagram.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason carried out the ritual, but the locks in the middle of the ritual circles glowed red hot. Much of the redrawn circles burst off the doors in a puff of chalk dust. Jason turned and joined the others, drawing his sword in readiness for whatever appeared to meet them. They did not have to wait long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individual bricks in the walls and floor sank drew back into recesses with a grinding of stone. Moments later, small stone and metal spiders came swarming out of the holes all over the room. They immediately started scuttling toward the group, swarming over the walls and across the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The construct creatures had minimal auras, but they were clearly iron-rank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Belinda, Neil." Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yeah," Belinda said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Got it," Neil followed. "On your call, Belinda."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tiny constructs had painted the walls and ceiling as they moved on the team. As the front runners edged closer and closer, some of the team started throwing Belinda glances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Uh, Belinda?" Neil asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wait," she said calmly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Construct spiders started dropping off the ceiling and the upper parts of the walls as they drew excruciatingly close to the team. Clive raised his staff to fire off a blast and Belinda waved him down with a gesture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not yet," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you kidding?" Clive asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have to catch a lot of them," Belinda said. "Alright, Neil. Now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil chanted out a quick spell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Let your power fulminate."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Bolster] (Growth)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Spell (boon).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Bronze 0 (00%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): The next essence ability used by the target ally has increased effect. This can affect parameters including damage, range and number of targets, depending on the affected ability. Cannot be used on self.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (bronze): Mana and stamina costs of the affected ability are reduced. In the case of ongoing mana and stamina costs, only costs initiated with the ability are affected. Costs invoked subsequent to the ability being activated are unaffected.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;As soon as she felt the power of Neil's spell affecting her, Belinda threw out her hand and a crystal rod rose up from the floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Force Tether] (Trap)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Special Ability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: Low mana-per-second.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: None.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 7 (09%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Conjures a crystal rod, from which a tether of shimmering force connects to all nearby enemies within a moderate range. Tethered enemies are dragged toward the rod, which is protected by a force field that inflicts moderate resonating force-damage to anyone in contact with it. If the force-field is ruptured, it explodes in a wave of resonating-force damage. If the rod is destroyed or removed from its location then it explodes in a wave of disruptive-force damage. Dimensional displacement, such as teleportation, severs the tether. Untethered enemies who enter within range of the rod become tethered. Only one force tether rod may exist at a time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shimmering tethers of force shot out to every spider in range, which was almost all of them given how close Belinda had allowed the mass to encroach on the team. There were so many it seemed less like a series of tethers and more like a wall. All the spiders were plucked from the walls, ceiling or where they had fallen to the floor and dragged toward the crystal rod. The constructs were so light and weak that they all were yanked right up to the tip of the rod, piling into a ball at the end of the shaft like the head of a dandelion. The innermost spiders were constantly damaged as they were dragged against the force-field surrounding the crystal rod.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not every one of the spiders had fallen within the range of the bolstered tether, but it was the significant majority. Belinda followed up with another power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: center"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Ability: [Pit of the Reaper] (Trap)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Conjuration (dimension).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cost: High mana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Cooldown: 2 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Current rank: Iron 6 (14%).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgba(0, 128, 128, 1)"&gt;Effect (iron): Conjures a dimensional space pit on any horizontal surface. The surface does not need to be solid or supportive. Anyone inside the pit suffers ongoing necrotic damage. If this spell is cast again while a pit already exists, the existing pit vanishes, depositing anyone inside upon the surface on which the pit was conjured.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rod fell into the pit that opened up underneath them, dragging the spiders down. Having moved from its original location, it detonated. The force field around the crystal rod blew up first, then the rod itself shortly after, both blasting the spiders with force and crushing them against the sides of the dimensional pit. Some were launched back up and out of the pit, although they landed inert and unmoving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team moved to clean up the spider constructs that had escaped the tether-pit combination, clearing out the rest with wand, staff, sword and, in Sophie's case, boot. It wasn't long before everything was done. The pit vanished, and the destroyed construct remnants disgorged up from the vanishing pit and into a pile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Does anyone else feel like that was a bit anticlimactic, after all that talk?" Neil asked, and Jason immediately let out a groan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why in the world would you go and say something like that?" Jason asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What?" Neil asked in turn. Suddenly there was a grinding sound as large sections of the floor started to descend, leaving large holes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's what," Jason said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think they would have opened, whether I said anything or not," Neil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well, now we'll never know."&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">498242</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 23:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/syndication/26294</link><description>Latest updates of (He Who Fights With Monsters)</description></rss>