<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>WuxiaWorld</title><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 560: Pretty Useless Bastard (6)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-560</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Choi Han looked at the weak and skinny hand on his shoulder before smiling toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's there to smile about?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was grumbling, but his face was unable to contain the emotions flowing inside him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Seung Won who walked up to Cale looked at this with shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was extremely rare for Kim Rok Soo to show his emotions like this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Park Jin Tae was even more shocked than Lee Seung Won.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'For Kim Rok Soo to have such an expression-'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that Kim Rok Soo was trying his best to get rid of the gratitude and emotions visible on his face was shocking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There had been many things to be shocked about thanks to Kim Rok Soo today, but nothing was as shocking as this look right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Who is this? Is it someone he knew before? He seems extremely happy to see him.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's eyes started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was shocked by Kim Rok Soo, but he was also shocked at this new person that had shown up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae barely managed to open his mouth to ask the same question again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Kim Rok Soo, who is this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo, who was trying to calm his emotions, looked toward Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo's eyes clouded over at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae was cautiously looking at Choi Han without being able to directly look at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae could see Kim Rok Soo smile while looking at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae realized it after seeing that smile on Kim Rok Soo's face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Ah. This bastard really does know.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This bastard really knew about his other ability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo launched a confirming blow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's wrong? Are you scared, sir?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's mouth opened and closed without being able to say anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale chuckled at this response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's second ability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That ability was quite abstract but in some ways, extremely detailed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Pressure based on the opponent's strength.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae could tell whether an opponent was stronger or weaker than him based on the pressure he felt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was less pressure if they were weaker and stronger pressure for stronger opponents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why he had quietly done his job without complaining while Lee Soo Hyuk who was stronger than him was at this central shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That's also why the death rate during Park Jin Tae's hunts was 0%.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were times when they came back without any food, but at least nobody who went hunting with Park Jin Tae ever died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was because Park Jin Tae avoided all the strong enemies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'But he hid this from everyone.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He hid his second ability from everybody else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Cale knew about this special ability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was because of the past when the central shelters were destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim had said the following to Park Jin Tae as the shelter was falling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Jin Tae! It will be fine if we all fight together!'&lt;br/&gt;
'No! It won't matter!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae had opposed it very firmly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why are you saying that without even trying?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim asked back and Park Jin Tae looked around at Grandma Kim and the others who didn't want to run before almost shouting at them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I can tell!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae was extremely annoyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actually, thinking about it now, it was fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…It's doable now, but we can't deal with the bastards behind these bastards! We must run away!'&lt;br/&gt;
'How would you know that-?'&lt;br/&gt;
'I told you I know! It's my ability! I'm able to tell whether something is strong or weak based on the pressure I feel!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae had shouted at the top of his lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I've never felt such pressure before! We'll all die if we don't run!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the punk who said that didn't run away until the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He did that even though he should have known that he was going to die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on Park Jin Tae's strength at that time, the pressure he felt was probably extremely heavy to the point of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would have felt the strength of the Grade 1 monsters charging at them like a tsunami.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had only one term to describe Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Crazy bastard.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae was quite a crazy and funny bastard, but Cale could now understand why he had not run away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was planning to do the same thing himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale quietly observed Park Jin Tae who was quietly staring at him with a piercing gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's clenched fists were probably full of sweat right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on the cold sweats on his forehead, his back was probably covered in sweat as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He must be feeling an overwhelming pressure right now.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pressure that the current Choi Han gave Park Jin Tae must be severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale put some strength into the hand placed on Choi Han's shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked at Park Jin Tae and Lee Seung Won as he started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is my dongsaeng."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han looked toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"His name is Choi Han."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale pretended not to see Choi Han's gaze and continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And he's the strongest person here on this ground."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's Lee Seung Won eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will definitely not lose if this punk is with us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had a bright smile on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae and Lee Seung Won could see the total trust in Kim Rok Soo's eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can chat here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae was peeking at Choi Han even as he said that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…The strongest person on this ground?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He wondered whether Kim Rok Soo was telling the truth, but he had no choice but to accept it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He's definitely stronger than anything I've seen.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae had felt an incomparable pressure coming from Choi Han that was worlds apart from the Grade 1 monsters they discussed earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Even Lee Soo Hyuk can't match him.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Soo Hyuk would be nothing in front of this punk named Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How could such a person-'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He thought that they might be able to survive through the horde of Grade 1 monsters as Kim Rok Soo expected, especially with such a person here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Of course, I don't know for sure.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This Choi Han character was stronger than one Grade 1 monster, however…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grade 1 monsters were going to come at them like water flowing through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He couldn't expect how Choi Han would compare to a large number of monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you very much."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked away from Choi Han after hearing Kim Rok Soo's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Enjoy your conversation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae then closed the door and left the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The space Park Jin Tae provided for them was quiet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was good enough for the two of them to chat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sit."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale sat down on a chair and pointed to the chair across from him while saying that and Choi Han sat down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them silently looked at each other until Cale opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tell me in detail about what happened."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to speak as if he was expecting that question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Currently, the Gate to the Demon World… Well, the Endable Kingdom is impossible to approach right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sinkhole. The entrance to that hole was covered by a black barrier right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Naturally, it is impossible to teleport into the Endable Kingdom as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale immediately started to speak after hearing that it was not possible to teleport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What about Eruhaben-nim and Miss Rosalyn? What about Bud?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I knew you would worry about the others first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han shook his head while looking at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How can I not be worried? Hurry up and tell me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han resumed speaking at Cale's urging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You remember Deputy Chief Priest Cotton, right?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes."&lt;br/&gt;
"That person was the God of War's Holy Maiden."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Ho. She was a Holy Maiden?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale didn't think Deputy Chief Priest would be a simple priestess as she could use the God of War's divine item, but he had never expected that she would be the Holy Maiden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There was a shelter that she had created."&lt;br/&gt;
"…The place she had kept the Ranger Brigade members imprisoned?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, that place. Eruhaben-nim and the others are currently sheltering there. It is apparently not budging even at the White Star's side's attacks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han recalled the conversation he had with Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"According to Eruhaben-nim, that place has the God of War's blessing, so it should be able to last for at least three months."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Originally, the Temples of the God of War were shelters for the weak during times of war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were said to have extremely strong defensive capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although that place was not an official shelter, it had the god's blessing and was created by the Holy Maiden, so it should be able to last three months as Eruhaben mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Something is weird."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Cale felt that something was weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Gate to the Demon World was one of the Eastern continent's Three Restricted Areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought the hands of the gods couldn't reach there?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was what Duke Fredo had said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Originally, that is the case."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Are you saying that there are exceptions?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Like what?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han hesitated for a moment. Cale became tense while wondering what he would say and Choi Han finally started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't know."&lt;br/&gt;
"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to frown. Choi Han avoided Cale's gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry. I didn't have time to hear about it. I had to rush here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was at a loss for words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What could he say when Choi Han didn't hear the explanation because he came to save him?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Choi Han peeked at Cale before quickly adding on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should be able to hear about that from Eruhaben-nim or Deputy Chief Priest Cotton once we return."&lt;br/&gt;
"Okay. I can hear about it later."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han continued to speak as Cale accepted the situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, Cale-nim. Based on what Eruhaben-nim told us, you've been unconscious inside the black orb for three days so far."&lt;br/&gt;
"Hold on!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale stopped Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Did you say three days?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes."&lt;br/&gt;
"…But I've only been here for about a day?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was time flowing differently here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I don't know much about that part, however…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han hesitated for a moment before starting to speak again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…The White Star and his subordinates have a tight formation around the black orb you are stuck in, making it impossible for Eruhaben-nim nor anybody else in the Endable Kingdom to approach."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han held back a sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Similarly, the others and I tried to approach from outside the sinkhole, but we could not break the black barrier covering the sinkhole. And then-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han stopped for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Don't tell him.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He remembered what Alberu told him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Don't tell him too much about what is going on over here. He'll definitely push himself too hard because he is worried.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu was the busiest person around Choi Han right now. He was doing a lot to make up for Cale's missing spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Choi Han. Yes, first of all, you… You go and help Cale. Help him with that test or crap or whatever. I don't know the contents of it, but I want you to help him quickly finish it and prevent him from becoming a member of the Demonic race.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han had told Alberu about what he was going to offer the God of Death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu had added on to Choi Han who was walking away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'm sorry. You, you really are an amazing instructor.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han knew why Alberu was apologizing to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Anyway, that was the situation before I came here to rescue you, Cale-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale brushed his face with both hands after hearing that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sure that's not everything. I guess you don't plan on telling me what else is going on?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…Yes."&lt;br/&gt;
"The others told you not to tell me?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…You're very astute."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bitter smile appeared on Choi Han's face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had not said it because Alberu told him not to say it, but Cale already seemed to have an idea about what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han made eye contact with Cale as he was getting upset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Tell me. Tell me what the God of Death told you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han closed his eyes for a moment before opening them and starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"According to Miss Cage, Cale-nim is currently inside the 'Enemy of the gods' who is the 'nameless god' and also the 'sealed god's test.' "&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…The enemy of the gods? The sealed god?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale thought about those blood-colored eyes that said it was wickedness, despair, and solitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was able to chat with the God of Death after that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to reveal the conversation he had alone with the God of Death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He said that you must overcome the test in order to survive that god's test."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He hesitated for a moment before adding on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But nobody has been able to overcome the test without that god's help until now, which was why I came here to help."&lt;br/&gt;
"Why you of all peo-"&lt;br/&gt;
"Because I have the longest lifespan. I had extra lifespan that I could use to make a deal."&lt;br/&gt;
"…There's no such thing as extra lifespan."&lt;br/&gt;
"I had it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han smiled at the frowning Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The God of Death said he needed compensation in order to get involved in the affairs of another god, even if that god is sealed. That is the rule."&lt;br/&gt;
" 'Rule' my ass. They do whatever the hell they want whenever they want."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han shook his head at Cale's comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Miss Cage said that the God of Death needed to make a sacrifice as well. This god is strong even if he is sealed, so the God of Death had to pay a steep price to meddle in that god's test. Don't hate the God of Death too much. That is what Miss Cage said."&lt;br/&gt;
"Don't worry. I hate both the God of Death and the sealed god equally. There's no hating one more than the other."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han awkwardly chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale nonchalantly asked the laughing Choi Han a question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…By the way. Can that sealed god bastard change this test as he pleases?"&lt;br/&gt;
"That is not possible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked toward Choi Han in shock after hearing such a confident response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I asked. I wondered if that was possible since it was called a test."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han had asked the same question to the God of Death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He said that there are rules for a god to approach a human. Those rules are absolute and even gods cannot change them, although the method a god uses to approach humans is all different."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale suddenly recalled how the World Tree told him that the gods share their will with this world by making deals or contracts with humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One of the absolute rules for the God of Death is to make a vow of death. Similarly, this sealed god can create tests per his absolute rule, but he cannot mess with the contents of that test."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han held some information back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The God of Death told him not to mention it for now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That sealed god was sealed because he broke a rule once. Of course, it was not a test-related rule.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the reason the God of Death cooperated with Choi Han who said he wanted to come here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cale-nim. What is the test?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han had not clearly heard about the test from the God of Death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He just came to help Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The background seems to be Cale-nim's past."&lt;br/&gt;
"That's right. This is my past. It's when I was twenty years old."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked deep in thought as he continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I don't know for sure, but… I think I just have to overcome my past despair."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han nodded his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cale-nim. The God of Death told me to tell you this if it seems as if you don't know much about the test."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han's quiet voice reached Cale's ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The past cannot be changed. However, you can overcome the despair of the past that remains in your heart."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale subconsciously started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Ha! The despair that remains in my heart."&lt;br/&gt;
"The God of Death seems to know about the test."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was silent after hearing Choi Han's comment before he nodded in agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then hesitated for a moment before starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Choi Han, we are going to be fighting quite a bit here as well."&lt;br/&gt;
"I'm aware."&lt;br/&gt;
"I can't use any powers here to battle. You will have to do everything."&lt;br/&gt;
"I'm aware."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale couldn't help but grumble at Choi Han's calm response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…That makes you happy?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes. I'm very happy."&lt;br/&gt;
"You crazy bastard."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han innocently smiled back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I don't know everything for now, but…'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was obvious that Choi Han had not told him everything he knew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'll need to focus on overcoming this test first.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was worried about the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He felt the need to move efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he still had no plans on rushing things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would take care of things one by one in order, just as he had planned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale stood up from his seat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There will be a big battle tomorrow. Many people's lives depend on the results of that battle."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, Cale-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han stood up from his seat as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are going to head to Seomyeon, Busan after that."&lt;br/&gt;
"I understand."&lt;br/&gt;
"You'll be able to meet Choi Jung Soo."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could see Choi Han's shoulders shake a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And there will be an unranked monster there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a reason the unranked monsters brought fear into the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unranked monsters were capable of destroying the new central shelters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why the future society that used the central shelters as its foundation feared the unranked monsters the most and considered them their biggest enemies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seomyeon, Busan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was where the new central shelter would appear and the unranked monster would try to destroy that central shelter and kill all of the humans in the nearby area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That monster is extremely strong."&lt;br/&gt;
"Even stronger than me?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Of course."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was certain about that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You won't be able to defeat it alone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then quickly added on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And that monster might appear in our world as well. The chances of that are high."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han's face stiffened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked at the stiff face and continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Along with seven even stronger monsters."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them looked at each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm going to kill that monster."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was planning on saving the central shelter in Seomyeon, Busan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Choi Han."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, Cale-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'We are guaranteed to defeat the first unranked monster if you are by my side.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale held back what he wanted to say and said something else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can't even feed you properly here."&lt;br/&gt;
"Cale-nim, I-"&lt;br/&gt;
"Call me hyung. Everybody will think it's weird if you call me Cale-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale reached his hand out to Choi Han who flinched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are older than me, but… I'm twenty years old."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han quietly looked at that hand before reaching his own hand out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I understand. I will call you hyung. Rok Soo hyung."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them shook hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale felt as if he could finally breathe a little better and felt relief from the sense of responsibility and burden he felt here for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;11 am.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The central shelter would lose its powers in one hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-559"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-561"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-560</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 04:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 559: Pretty Useless Bastard (5)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-559</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min was the one to break the silence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…A, are you out of your mind?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could speak easily now that he opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice slowly started to get louder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I always thought this son of a bitch was crazy! How dare you spew such bullshit without knowing what you should and should not say? Huh?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min approached Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked ready to grab him by the collar at any moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Enough!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's loud voice filled the room at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's enough, Lee Chul Min."&lt;br/&gt;
"Leader-nim!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Be quiet!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min's anger instantly subsided after hearing Park Jin Tae get angry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae looked toward Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Explain it in detail."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned away from Park Jin Tae and looked at Grandma Kim and the siblings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Hey."&lt;br/&gt;
"Hyung…this-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The siblings looked at Cale with flustered expressions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, Grandma Kim was the calmest person in the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She gently smiled toward Cale. However, Cale could tell that this was a forced smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She didn't want to show that her mind was completely chaotic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was putting on a front for Kim Rok Soo who was speaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She smiled as best as she could before starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, Rok Soo. You know the weight of your words, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why Cale had no choice but to respond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, ma'am, I do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked back toward Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is exactly as I said, sir."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow at noon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A solar eclipse would happen throughout the world at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That alone was enough to realize that this was no regular solar eclipse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And one minute later…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the sun shone down on the world again…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every central shelter on Earth would disappear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae recalled what Cale said word for word before repeating the last part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Finally, the monsters will charge in like a tsunami and attack the central shelter."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They all heard Kim Rok Soo's voice again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The monsters will not randomly attack together. They will attack based on their Grade."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Grade?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir. Grade. It is based on a monster's strength and abilities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Monster Grades-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grades had yet to be determined at this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale knew this was the case as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, people had investigated the issue of the central shelters and the monsters later on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It had been based on what people remembered, but they were able to gather a lot of information that way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of them was the Grades of the attacking monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It starts with those at Grade 3 and below. Then the Grade 2 monsters will come. Finally, the Grade 1 monsters will attack. Of course, Grade 1 monsters are the strongest."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why there was talk in the future about whether this pattern was some sort of training for humans to be able to fight against the unranked monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, the reality was hell for it to just be training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae looked toward Kim Rok Soo with difficult emotions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I definitely felt that something seemed different, but…'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo had felt different than normal after being hit earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the reason he had chosen to chat with him, but…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was too difficult to accept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"… Are you out of your mind?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the only way he could ask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then heard a response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you questioning my ability? Would you like me to tell you more?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That response made Park Jin Tae shut his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'You're an ability user with multiple abilities, right?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard the thing Kim Rok Soo whispered in his ear once again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was such a large secret that he couldn't even get angry at the fact that Kim Rok Soo was speaking informally to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae looked toward Cale again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He pointed to himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tell me one more thing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tell him one more of his secrets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale chuckled at the gesture and walked over to Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's grip tightened on the couch as he watched Cale walk over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He'll definitely tell me about the ability I'm hiding.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae started to get nervous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo whispered at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are going to fight in the frontlines, putting your life on the line, if danger arrives at this place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's pupils shook even more than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're going to say that the old and weak people are getting in your way of fighting and evacuate them first. Then will be people like me who don't have any abilities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice was extremely calm as if he knew he was telling the truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo had already experienced it once before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The last. Once it is the last moment and everybody else is gone… That's when you will run away."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale moved away from Park Jin Tae's ear and looked at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them made eye contact and Cale started to speak again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's the kind of person you are."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae slowly started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ha, hahaha-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His laughter filled the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was laughing so hard that he was starting to tear up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Haaa."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then caught his breath…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And started to speak with a smile also as if he was sighing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Looks like I had an even bigger secret found out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then heard Kim Rok Soo's voice again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm going to save you too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's eyes opened wide. He looked at Kim Rok Soo with a piercing gaze before finally starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What is your plan?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Leader-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min who had quietly been standing there raised his voice as if he couldn't let this continue, but Park Jin Tae didn't even give him a glance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was only focused on Cale's lips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slowly started to speak as if to respond to that focused gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We must create an attack team. We will then initiate a defensive battle. The center of the defensive battle will be-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could not continue speaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Leader-nim, are you really going to believe this bastard-"&lt;br/&gt;
"Silence!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tap!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sound of his hand slapping down on the wooden armrest sharply echoed in the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min looked toward the person in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was the one who had told Lee Chul Min to be quiet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Rok Soo, keep going."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, ma'am."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae showed his agreement with Grandma Kim by remaining silent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The center of the defensive battle will be Jang Man Soo. It needs to be him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everybody in the room flinched at this sudden name that was mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was not a name they had expected to hear at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The mister's ability specializes in defense."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae subconsciously started to mumble after hearing what Cale said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Mr. Jang Man Soo awakened an ability?"&lt;br/&gt;
"That's right. You can confirm it tomorrow."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extremely calm voice made it seem as if he was telling the truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale then continued to speak to Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And Park Jin Tae, you will be the center of the attack team."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae gulped and started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But isn't it better to go to a different temporary shelter rather than protecting this central shelter?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He thought it would be better to move to a temporary shelter and avoid the monsters' attacks that way instead of defending if a horde of monsters were going to attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well, we would need to go to multiple temporary shelters to fit everyone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The central shelters were much larger than the other shelters. That was why they would need to split up and go to different shelters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They would then have to keep moving to different temporary shelters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had no idea when any temporary shelter would disappear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were not going to stay safe forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale shook his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is not a good idea."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Why?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Unfortunately, the monsters will attack the temporary shelters as well. Of course, the number of monsters attacking those shelters will be less than here at the central shelter, but it will not be a small number as it will be based on the number of people who will be at the temporary shelter."&lt;br/&gt;
"Ho."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone let out a gasp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what Cale said next put the people even more at a loss for words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale calmly stated the things that ended up happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Furthermore, the temporary shelters will gradually lose their abilities once the central shelters disappear."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even Lee Chul Min did not bare his fangs at Cale this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…So, you're saying that in the end, all shelters will disappear?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min's voice was shaking after hearing Cale's firm response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…That will be hell."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice could not help but shake as he imagined hell on earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The world will only be without any shelters for three hours."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae looked toward Cale again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale continued to speak as everybody's gazes were focused on him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A different looking central shelter will appear one day after these central shelters disappear."&lt;br/&gt;
"Then we can go there!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale nodded his head at Lee Jin Joo's statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As long as we can survive one night that is."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae brushed his face with both hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't question whether Cale was telling the truth or not anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had all faced this unbelievable situation known as the cataclysm already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They always had to prepare for the worst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was especially the case if the worst-case scenario was going to be hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Does a Grade 1 monster have to be as strong as the bastard with three horns?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monsters did not have names yet and were called out by their characteristics at this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale nodded his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That monster is one of the Grade 1 monsters."&lt;br/&gt;
"And those things will come attacking like a tsunami?"&lt;br/&gt;
"After the Grade 3 and Grade 2 monsters go by."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min subconsciously started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"O, our attack team can't handle it if more than four of them come at once! We will die! But they're going to come like a tsunami? How is that possible?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Of course, there will be less of them than the Grade 3 and Grade 2 monsters."&lt;br/&gt;
"That's obvious! There aren't as many of those strong bastards! Even still, even still, there has to be at least more than ten of them, right? Especially if all of the ones around us come to attack!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Definitely more."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min's eyes were full of fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Park Jin Tae's stern voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can't last through that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is impossible. All of us can't survive."&lt;br/&gt;
"No."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was stern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will persist."&lt;br/&gt;
"…How are you so sure about that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike Park Jin Tae's voice that was full of hesitation, Kim Rok Soo's voice had no hesitation at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can move to the new central shelter without any of us dying."&lt;br/&gt;
"…How?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How are you able to say such things?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was what Park Jin Tae's eyes were asking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The skinny young man with a sharp gaze started to smile brightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood-colored eyes bastard had made a big mistake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Data."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae subconsciously asked back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Data?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ability that Cale had awakened while he was Kim Rok Soo could not be used 'right now.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that did not mean that the memories he had gathered had disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His power came not from the present nor the future, but from his experiences in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was important to awaken his ability, but there was a reason he thought that this battle at the central shelter was doable even without it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had a power that came from experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have all of the data regarding those monsters."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale who was in Kim Rok Soo's body right now, the man who had lived as Kim Rok Soo until he was thirty-six and then lived as Cale continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Weaknesses, movement patterns, attacking styles, and destructive force. I also know the order in which the monsters will attack."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice was starting to get stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All of that information is in my head."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The records he had gathered while facing despair in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was a way to have hope right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can win because we have data."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That had been the foundation for how humans were able to create societies on Earth again, the thing that allowed them to go from being weaklings to proper opponents of the monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please trust my data. Then we will all survive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of them looked toward Kim Rok Soo with complicated expressions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But at that moment…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have always trusted you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One person walked over to Kim Rok Soo and grabbed his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Grandma."&lt;br/&gt;
"You're a good kid. You also have a strong will. Who would I trust if I can't trust someone like you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Park Jin Tae's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lee Chul Min."&lt;br/&gt;
"Y, yes sir?"&lt;br/&gt;
"We are changing to emergency status immediately."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae got up from the couch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked out the window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sun was already setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He walked past Cale and headed out the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't have much time so we will trust your prophecy for now, Kim Rok Soo. Lee Chul Min!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Call over all of the ability users with attacking abilities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min opened his mouth to speak as if he was a trained soldier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes si-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They heard a loud explosion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They could feel the old building slightly shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Aaaaaah!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Seung Won plopped down on the ground in shock as he shouted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"O, outside!"&lt;br/&gt;
"What? Did a monster already appear?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min who was also shocked responded to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What is going on? I don't have any memories of this happening.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked out the window after hearing this sudden explosion as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the first time he heard an explosion like this since coming here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see the sunset outside the window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…T, this crazy!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He quickly rushed toward the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, what's going on?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae was shocked at his action but Cale pushed Park Jin Tae aside and ran out the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Lee Jin Joo mumbling behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…A black dragon?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to frown even more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why is that here?! Why is that here right now?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black Yong shooting up into the sky was the culprit behind the explosion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a sparkling black Yong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why is this punk, why, why?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale didn't have any time to think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He quickly ran down the stairs and headed outside the building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, hey! Kim Rok Soo!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Jang Man Soo who was waiting on the first floor calling his name, but Cale didn't have any time to look back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Park Jin Tae and Lee Seung Won's voices behind him as well, but he still could not look back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale ran outside the building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sparkling black Yong that was shooting up to the sky was turning faint and disappearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cale ran in the direction of the Yong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could run without worrying about anything as there were no monsters near the central shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Park Jin Tae's voice far behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey! You're about to step outside the boundary!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would soon be past the boundary and it would not be weird if monsters appeared at any moment to attack Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Cale could not stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see someone walking over to him in the distance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…You-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slowed down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could not believe what he was seeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the distance between him and the approaching person slowly became smaller.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person had started to move faster as Cale slowed down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And finally, the person stopped in front of Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…You…why are you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other person started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You seem to be around my age right now, when is this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale finally managed to open his mouth that was difficult to open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Choi Han."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han was standing in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sparkling black Yong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was Choi Han's skill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…How did you……?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I found a way to squeeze in."&lt;br/&gt;
"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han quietly looked at the skinny and shabby Kim Rok Soo as he continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cale-nim, you are currently unconscious and imprisoned inside a black orb."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice was calm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I went to the Endable Kingdom, but I was unable to get near it. It is impossible to get near it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What was he talking about?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's mind started to become complicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'm imprisoned inside a black orb right now?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His gaze was focused on Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His clothes did not match this world, but his physical appearance that was perfect for Korea was looking at him, at Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is why I found a way to squeeze into Cale-nim's mind, into the test."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was shocked that Choi Han knew about the test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How can you get involved-"&lt;br/&gt;
"I made a deal with the God of Death."&lt;br/&gt;
"…What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I made a deal with the God of Death so that I could get involved with this test."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then quickly added on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I needed to help you, Cale-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to frown even more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han calmly continued to speak while looking at his frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Isn't it better to do it together than to do it alone?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale suppressed his emotions that were trying to make him tear up and opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…What did you offer him?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What did he offer the God of Death to make the deal?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale asked and Choi Han answered as if it was nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He said that I would live longer than Raon. I didn't want that. I didn't want to be left alone. So, I matched my lifespan to Raon's."&lt;br/&gt;
"…You offered a part of your lifespan to the God of Death?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes. Only the time I would end up living alone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale couldn't help but say the following.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You crazy bastard!"&lt;br/&gt;
"That's what I wanted because I didn't want to be left alone. I didn't want to experience solitude anymore."&lt;br/&gt;
"Are you crazy?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An innocent smile appeared on Choi Han's face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Unfortunately, I haven't been normal for a long time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale heard people approaching behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who is this?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Hyung, who is this person?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han smiled brightly and responded once he heard Park Jin Tae and Lee Seung Won who had followed Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm someone who came to pay for his meals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had to bite his lips after hearing that because of the emotions filling his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He barely managed to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the only thing he could offer Choi Han right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And thank you. Really, thank you very much."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-558"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-560"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-559</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 05:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 558: Pretty Useless Bastard (4)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-558</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo could only respond in one way to Kim Rok Soo's comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Y, you're lying……!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then quickly added on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"N, no! Rok Soo, I'm not saying you're lying about having an ability! It's great if you got an ability! You're qualified to get one! But, that-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could not speak properly. He then continued to speak after seeing Kim Rok Soo's firm gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Knowing people's abilities and the future…it's hard to believe that such an ability exists."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo said that and then lowered his head for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then raised it back, looked at Kim Rok Soo's gaze, and sighed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…You're being serious."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo's gaze did not seem as if he was lying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess that you aren't the type to lie."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo didn't know what else to say. Of course, there were a lot of things he wanted to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, he had too many things he wanted to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He figured out my ability? Did he awaken an ability that lets him know other people's abilities? No.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That would not explain everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He also prophesized the future.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said that the central shelter would be destroyed soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He guessed my ability correctly, so there's a good chance he's telling the truth about the central shelter too.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was living life day by day without thinking much about it, but that was why Jang Man Soo had been able to observe the people in this shelter while sitting off to one side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Kim Rok Soo is not the type of person to lie about something that involves people's lives.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he was to do something like that, then it would have to be someone else wearing Kim Rok Soo's skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Are you really Kim Rok Soo?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Hey mister, do you want me to say the things you say when you sleep? Or maybe you want me to imitate your snoring?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Ahem. I guess you really are Kim Rok Soo based on how you are nagging me like that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo continued to sigh in disbelief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Haaa."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked toward Cale with a complicated expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…The cent-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo stopped midsentence and looked around. Everybody seemed to be doing their work as nobody was paying any attention to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He continued to speak quieter and stealthier than Kim Rok Soo had done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The central shelters are really going to end up like that?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The response was simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo's lips started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was thinking about the terrible scene that would play out if the central shelter was destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale then put a hand on Jang Man Soo's shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, mister. Please help me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo was necessary for this task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I probably won't be much help-"&lt;br/&gt;
"That's not true. Mister, you still don't know the strength of your ability."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Cale mentioned, Jang Man Soo knew that his ability had awakened but had never used it before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was thinking that a shield was useless for someone like him who couldn't even walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…More than that… I just didn't want to live a fierce life.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo did not want to say this thought out loud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His mind started to become complicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Everybody here might die.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't care if he died alone. But to watch someone die again?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Especially people who had helped him even when he couldn't walk properly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then recalled something Kim Rok Soo had just said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I plan on letting everybody here move to the new central shelter without dying.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without anybody dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those words struck deep inside Jang Man Soo's mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He thought of his dead daughter. His daughter would have started college and showed the world everything she had if the world didn't end up like this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That daughter and Kim Rok Soo were the same age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why he wanted to give even one thing extra to Kim Rok Soo who was trying his best to survive after having already lived a difficult life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He asked Rok Soo a question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Will I be of any help?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see Rok Soo smiling at his question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He truly seemed to be happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, sir. I definitely need your help."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale really needed this man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'The mister doesn't know yet.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't know the strength of his ability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…It'll be hard for me to even move properly if a battle breaks out……"&lt;br/&gt;
"That's not important."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo could feel Kim Rok Soo's hand that was on his shoulder pushing down. Kim Rok Soo's hand seemed to be cheering him on while his voice was full of certainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shields are only cool if they stand firm without moving."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo suddenly felt his mind start to fluctuate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His mind that had been still without any movement was causing small waves every time Rok Soo said something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And don't worry, I'll carry you around, mister."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo chuckled at that and joked back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Bad! How can a stick like you carry a husky person like me?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I guess that is true."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo could see Rok Soo chuckling as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, Rok Soo."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I will also help you."&lt;br/&gt;
"Thank you very much."&lt;br/&gt;
"No, thank you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo truly meant that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He finally realized it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'My time is finally starting to move again.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The time that had stopped on the day of the cataclysm, no, the moment he got home and saw the terrible state of his family members, was starting to move again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I will create a different result this time.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had made up his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to think while looking at Jang Man Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo didn't know about his ability yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was going to make it so that he could use his power effectively and efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that could happen…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Then I'll definitely be able to save over half of the people.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo working with Cale meant over half of the people here could live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, mister. I will give you a detailed explanation now."&lt;br/&gt;
"Hmm? Yes, yes. I should listen."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir. So, let's go talk outside the back door."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were no monsters there because it was right by the shelter, but more importantly, there were no people there. It was a perfect spot to have a secret discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Okay. I'm going to need you to help me though."&lt;br/&gt;
"Of course."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale carried Jang Man Soo on his back and walked out the back door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, Cale's body staggered a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I'm sorry."&lt;br/&gt;
"…No. You know I've always been weak."&lt;br/&gt;
"…I guess that is true."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He staggered at first, but they were quickly able to get outside as their spots were by the door. Thankfully, nobody seemed to be paying attention to the two of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale put Jang Man Soo down on a flat area of the destroyed building next to the back door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Click.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The old back door was closed and Cale started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You must listen carefully to everything I'm about to tell you."&lt;br/&gt;
"Okay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo looked at Cale with both nervousness and determination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The central shelter will be destroyed tomorrow."&lt;br/&gt;
"What?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo's eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tomorrow? It's happening tomorrow?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir."&lt;br/&gt;
"T, This! It's going to suddenly happen like that?!"&lt;br/&gt;
"I did say it would be soon, didn't I?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Hooo!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo patted his thigh with his hand over and over as if he didn't know what to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh, and the new central shelter will not open until 24 hours after this central shelter is destroyed."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Huh?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked at the blankly staring Jang Man Soo and calmly continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Basically, to put it in the simplest of terms…a maximum of 24 hours. That's how long we need to survive in this building that will no longer be a shelter.&lt;br/&gt;
"Wait, what kind of-"&lt;br/&gt;
"That also means we need to spend one night."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo was at a loss for words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes looked at Cale who seemed completely calm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That calmness made Jang Man Soo barely able to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…W, what is the plan?"&lt;br/&gt;
"The first goal is achieved since you said you will help me out, mister."&lt;br/&gt;
"…What is the second goal?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second goal was simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's the same as the first goal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked toward the third floor of the building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I need to convince other people."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Are you planning on meeting with Park Jin Tae? Do you think that bastard will believe you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked back toward Jang Man Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo realized that Kim Rok Soo had changed after seeing this smile every so often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It made him think that this punk really might have gotten an ability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, sir. He will believe me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo could not help but nod his head after hearing this voice that was full of confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drip. Drip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A drop of blood flowed down to his chin and fell to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Huuuuuu."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man took a deep breath before looking down at the person blocking his path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you want?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae who had returned from hunting was looking at Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have something to say."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min, one of Park Jin Tae's subordinates, started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey! You mindless bastard! Can't you see that we just got back from hunting? Hmm? Can't you see our conditions?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slowly looked around at the people who had gone hunting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of them looked like messes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were many injured people as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why he could tell that this hunt was neither a game nor predators hunting easy prey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a desperate hunt to find food for survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could see a few bags in their hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They probably went to a mart or grocery store to gather the food that was still edible. It was usually canned food or ramen, but those were very precious as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale responded to Lee Chul Min who was glaring at him as if he wanted to pierce a hole through his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can clearly see it. That's why I'm thankful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's eyes clouded over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Lee Chul Min's face turned red.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wow. Did this bastard speak informally to me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He seemed to have gotten angry at the fact that Kim Rok Soo who was two or three years younger than him spoke informally to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Cale's gaze was cold as he looked at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Lee Chul Min, this bastard was the first to run away.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had run away while Park Jin Tae was helping the weak and useless people escape first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The weak who were being led by Lee Chul Min became frantic when Lee Chul Min ran away and the situation turned even more chaotic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had made up his mind as he clearly remembered that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'You won't be able to run away this time, you bastard.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min had the third strongest attacking ability in this place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shouldn't he properly use such a precious asset?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of Cale's lips started to go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please and thank you."&lt;br/&gt;
"What? Did this bastard go crazy?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min's face viciously scrunched up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing a normally vicious bastard's face becoming vicious made him seem very heinous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae raised his hand at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Enough."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min shut his mouth. Of course, Cale didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have something I need to tell you, sir."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae carefully looked at Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was very tired after coming back from the hunt, but…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You said something you 'need' to tell me?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir. Something I must tell you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae nodded his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fine. Let's go to my room."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min was shocked at this response, but Park Jin Tae started to walk toward his room on the third floor as if he said everything he needed to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Kim Rok Soo's voice behind him at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to call a few other people over as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae looked back toward Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae started to walk again in a few seconds as he responded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Call them all over."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir. I will be up shortly."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned away from Park Jin Tae and motioned to Grandma Kim and the Lee siblings who were anxiously watching him chat with Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They needed to hear as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He needed them to be with him as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, what is it you need to tell me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae sat down on a couch that was extremely rare in this world and looked at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min, Grandma Kim, Lee Jin Joo, and Lee Seung Won were in Park Jin Tae's room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim sat down on the chair to Park Jin Tae's right, but everybody else was standing as they looked at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their gazes were all full of questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cale paid no attention to the gazes focused on him and just made eye contact with Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I awakened my ability."&lt;br/&gt;
"……!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's eyes opened wide almost instantly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…That is completely unexpected."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even Lee Chul Min looked at Kim Rok Soo up and down in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This bastard got an ability?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Grandma Kim's face was glowing. It was the same for the siblings as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My goodness, Rok Soo! That's wonderful!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Wow, Kim Rok Soo!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Hyung!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is why I am able to see the future."&lt;br/&gt;
"…What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Silence almost immediately filled the area again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, of course, I'm also able to see a few pieces of information other people are not able to see."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min mouth opened without him thinking about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What nonsense-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked toward Park Jin Tae at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min tried to keep Cale away, but Park Jin Tae raised his hand to stop him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked right up to Park Jin Tae without any hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Kim Rok Soo."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale lowered his body and whispered quietly so that only Park Jin Tae could hear as Park Jin Tae quietly said his name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're an ability user with multiple abilities, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until Park Jin Tae died…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was his secret that nobody else in the world knew about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…You-, you!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's pupils started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale took one step back at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then continued to speak in a calm voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tomorrow at noon. There will be a moment when the sun is covered by a shadow."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The room was chaotic because of Cale's revealed ability and his interaction with Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It will last one minute."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was the only calm person here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After that one minute, all central shelters around the world would become ineffective."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice stabbed into everyone else's ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The nearby monsters will all start to attack the central shelters that are no longer useful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was the only one speaking in this terrible silence with all eyes focused on him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The monsters will come charging forth like a tsunami."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A suffocating silence filled the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-557"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-559"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-558</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 04:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 557: Pretty Useless Bastard (3)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-557</link><description>&lt;p&gt;He needed to first figure out today's date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I also need to check who is here.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He needed to figure out the people who would fight based on the present and his information of the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And most importantly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I need to change myself first.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He needed to get his abilities awakened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, an ability awakening was something nobody could predict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's abilities were only awakened after he started working for his company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why, realistically speaking, it would be close to impossible for Cale to awaken his future abilities as he pleased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…But I've experienced the sensation that comes with abilities being awakened.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It felt as if he was seeing a new world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he thinks about that sensation and does similar things as to when his abilities actually awakened, couldn't he potentially get them awakened sooner?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…It's fine if my abilities don't awaken while I'm at the central shelter, but it would be great to have them when I go up against the unranked monster.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's expression stiffened and Grandma Kim tightly grabbed Cale's hand that was over his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shaaaaaaaaaaa-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale then saw a yellow light surround his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He subconsciously started to speak with urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Grandma, I'm okay!"&lt;br/&gt;"You're not okay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could feel the pain in his stomach disappear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any bruises or injuries on his stomach probably healed right away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was grandma's healing ability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…How can you use your power for such a useless thing?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim's abilities could only heal external injuries and had limited uses per week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could use it as many times as she wanted for small injuries such as bruises, but she had a strict limit for injuries such as bone fractures or significant blood loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The amount of healing power necessary was different based on the type of injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why Park Jin Tae wanted Grandma Kim to use her powers for healing his precious attack team members who could fight against monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim smiled gently after hearing Cale's comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is not useless, it is important."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The grandma got up and motioned for Cale to get up as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, Rok Soo. Let's go inside."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slowly raised his body after seeing that warm smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't have any pain anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, you stupid idiot!"&lt;br/&gt;"Hyung!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned toward the voice calling out to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see people rushing out of the shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two students, one who seemed to be in college and the other in high school, rushed over and started to support Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, are you okay?"&lt;br/&gt;"Hyung, are you okay?"&lt;br/&gt;"Ah."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These people were here as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Jin Joo. Lee Seung Won.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These two were siblings and ability users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Of course, they have abilities that other ability users look down on.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their abilities were seen as useless abilities right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…And these two.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale suddenly felt as if someone was clenching his heart and found it hard to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm fine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But his face and voice did not show any signs of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Aigoo. Look at you acting all tough!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Jin Joo snorted, but her eyes were full of concern as she checked to make sure Kim Rok Soo was okay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale gently pushed Lee Jin Joo and Lee Seung Won away and walked in front of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go inside."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The siblings blankly looked at Cale for a moment before shaking their heads and following him inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should just let us support you. Why are you walking so slowly?"&lt;br/&gt;"Hyung, we're going to go back in first! We came in the middle of work!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people inside the central shelter all had work they needed to complete every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, those jobs were only given to people who had Park Jin Tae's approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo did not have his approval, which was why they always tried to start shit with him in the name of running errands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Isn't it so nice to see them relying on each other?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim smiled while looking at the siblings who were walking away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked at the siblings instead of responding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It made him think of On and Hong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Grandma."&lt;br/&gt;"Hmm?"&lt;br/&gt;"What is today's date?"&lt;br/&gt;"Today?"&lt;br/&gt;"Yes, ma'am."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim looked at him with confusion while wondering why he was asking such a thing before answering in a soft voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Today is the 24th."&lt;br/&gt;"October?"&lt;br/&gt;"Yes? Why are you suddenly asking about the date?"&lt;br/&gt;"Just because."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;October 24th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale recalled today's date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Fuck."&lt;br/&gt;"…Hey, Rok Soo."&lt;br/&gt;"I'm sorry. I just suddenly thought of something that made me angry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He smiled toward Grandma Kim who was looking at him with concern after hearing his coarse language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim, who had not seen Rok Soo smile in a while, opened her eyes wide in shock for a moment before gently smiling and nodding her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale repeated the word in his mind as he continued to walk next to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Fuck fuck fuck!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only thing on his mind was swearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one day…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During day time on October 25th…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central shelters around the world will be destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the start date of the incident that would fill the hearts of the people who barely started to adjust to the changes since the cataclysm with despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I only have one day?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked into the central shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm going to go work now too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim headed for her post while Cale took in the sight inside the central shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It really is the early stages.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were a lot of different people doing their jobs on the first floor of the building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of them paid any attention to Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'They're all busy doing their best to survive.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale continued to walk and headed for his spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a fake wall that came up to his waist once he got past the entrance area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see people pretty much right next to one another once he got past that fake wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These people were in a similar situation as Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had not awakened their abilities and didn't have any skills nor techniques that were necessary in the world right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Of course, people will realize that is not the case later on when society is revitalized.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were also doing the work assigned to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Step step.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked past them and kept moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second floor of the central shelter was where the ability users and useful humans resided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Lee siblings had a bedroom on the second floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Well, it's too shabby to call it a bedroom or lodging.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a time when any spot that allowed someone to escape the rain and wind was considered lodging and any nice cloth they could find was used as blankets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were lucky to find enough food for one day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'The Park Jin Tae group did share though.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae and his lackeys went out to find food for the group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did it while dodging and running away from monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'They did fight against some, but unlike the future, this was a time when even grade 3 monsters were difficult to handle.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People had awakened their abilities but still could not use them properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abilities could be used for many things, and this was called 'development.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'But right now is not the time to attempt that.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The foundations of society had crumbled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There wasn't even any electricity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were surrounded by darkness every night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only things that kept it from being completely dark at night were the fireplaces around the shelter that had fires that never went out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked down at his hands as he walked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'They're so skinny.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His body was extremely skinny right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's lackeys only gave just enough so that they did not die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That's the only way they can spread it out to everybody inside this shelter.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was not easy to find food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo managed to survive on the bare minimum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'The people of value received more food.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why the ability users who had good relationships with Kim Rok Soo would offer him some of their shares from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…The world is not bleak.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though the times seemed hopeless, the hearts of the people living through it had not gone completely dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why Cale didn't think Park Jin Tae was a bad person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'There are many places that don't even give out food like this.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people didn't care whether others starved to death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In such a situation, although Park Jin Tae looked down and messed with people like Kim Rok Soo, he still gave them enough food to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Well, he does beat up resistant people like me though. No, he just really hated me.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he still gave out enough so that their legs would have enough strength to run away if they ever ran into a monster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bastard had turned this central shelter into his own kingdom, but he still kept himself humane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He did not cross the line a fellow human should not cross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He at least gave them their share of food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had realized something about it once he became older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'The fact that Park Jin Tae pushed the skillful people up might have been the reason this system was able to be maintained.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All societal systems had been destroyed at that time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How many ability users would want to share the food that they worked so hard to find?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But since Park Jin Tae treated the ability users well, they stayed with this food sharing system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'And Park Jin Tae is currently a very strong attack-type ability user.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a reason team leader Lee Soo Hyuk left the place to Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae was a very strong dealer and a decent tanker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min and the others who followed Park Jin Tae were not bad for the early stages either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I will use Park Jin Tae.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was slowly planning things in his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'There's also Grandma Kim, Jin Joo noona, and Seung Won.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were also many other people he needed for this task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale returned to his spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo's spot in this central shelter…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at the edge of the first floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was right next to a crumbling ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was right by the back door of the first floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…The rain leaked here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo's spot was the only spot in the building where rain leaked through the cracked ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why are you talking to yourself like that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard a voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a husky and aged man's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You chose that spot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had chosen this spot as that person mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae placed the ability-less Cale to the first floor and he chose this leaking spot as his spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's wrong? Do you suddenly want to move elsewhere? What happened to pretending like you were sacrificing yourself for the others?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale sighed and turned his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey mister. Why don't you go elsewhere if you want to talk shit?"&lt;br/&gt;"Kekeke! Who says I'm talking shit?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked toward the middle-aged man lying on the next spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was nothing under his knees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was one of the people that team leader Lee Soo Hyuk had saved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His name was Jang Man Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey! I heard you got beat up by Park Jin Tae and his gang. Are you okay?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo raised his neck and leaned on the wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those terrible bastards. Where is there even to hit such a skinny kid? They'll be punished by the heavens!"&lt;br/&gt;"It's fine. Grandma healed me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked next to Jang Man Soo… and sat down in his spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm? Grandma did? Aigoo, why does that grandma care about you so much? Why did she heal a good for nothing like you?"&lt;br/&gt;"Are you saying you're upset that I got healed?"&lt;br/&gt;"Oh come on~ Of course not. Kehehe! I just said it! It was a joke, a joke!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale quietly looked at Jang Man Soo who was joking with him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was someone who lost his entire family because of the cataclysm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had a wife and two kids and was on his way to work when it happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He barely managed to get back to his house only to see that all of them were already dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He saw the monster that had killed his family there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He apparently ran for his life from monsters to get to his house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There had only been one thing on his mind as he did that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was thinking that his family was alive at home and that he would take his family somewhere safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he charged toward the monster the moment he saw that his family was dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The thought of running away never ever crossed his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He just felt as if he could only continue to live if he ripped the monster in front of him to pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The monster took both of his legs and Jang Man Soo was planning on dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't think there was a reason to live in this world without his family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the team leader saved him and Jang Man Soo was someone who was barely alive and living on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey mister."&lt;br/&gt;"What is it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale quietly observed him before lowering his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He got closer to Jang Man Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey mister."&lt;br/&gt;"Why are you suddenly acting like this, you punk?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Jang Man Soo looked toward Kim Rok Soo who was acting differently than normal with confusion…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale quietly whispered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please help me out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo looked confused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Me? You're talking to me? What help can I be? Did you go crazy after getting beaten up?"&lt;br/&gt;"Mister."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale whispered quietly so that nobody else could hear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your ability awakened not too long ago, didn't it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo's pupils started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His jaw dropped and he looked astonished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to smile while looking at his reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed to be a sad smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo also died in the past when the central shelter disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He died fighting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Kehehe! I'm relieved! This time, I'm going first after protecting people!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His ability apparently awakened not long before the central shelter was destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His memory of Jang Man Soo remained with Kim Rok Soo that once he became Cale…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first thing he chose to get was a shield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mister, your ability is a shield, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo stiffened up and could not say anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How did he realize that my ability awakened?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People didn't look different even after awakening their ability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why there was no way to tell unless they saw the person using the ability or the person told them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were some ability users whose appearances changed with it, but Jang Man Soo's case wasn't like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'But Kim Rok Soo realized that? And he knows what my ability is as well?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How could he not be astonished in such a situation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale whispered to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The central shelter will be destroyed soon."&lt;br/&gt;"W, what?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His mouth that had closed back in shock dropped once more at this even more shocking comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo raised his voice with an extremely shocked expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shh."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale quieted him down and whispered very quietly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And I know where the new central shelter will appear."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What is this punk saying right now?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo was looking at Kim Rok Soo as if he was looking at someone he had just met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mister."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Kim Rok Soo's eyes were more serious than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One word after another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each word that Kim Rok Soo said to him struck Jang Man Soo's ear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I plan on letting everybody here move to the new central shelter without dying."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jang Man Soo barely managed to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You- you, how do you know about those……?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I got an ability too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a very strong ability where he knew the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-556"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-558"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-557</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 03:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 556: Pretty Useless Bastard (2)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-556</link><description>&lt;p&gt;But he didn't have time to sit around with a burning gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale immediately raised his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He couldn't help but groan because of the pain he felt throughout his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the people looking down at him started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey. Why did you have to run your mouth instead of doing what we told you to do?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale, no, Kim Rok Soo ignored that comment that was directed at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I don't have time for this.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He put some strength into his shaking legs in order to stand up little by little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was when Kim Rok Soo's body was weaker than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe that was the reason, but this weak ass body of his was this helpless after only being kicked once by an ability user.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he heard someone sneer…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale fell on the ground again after someone kicked his calf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was flat on the ground looking up at the sky again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone crouched down beside him and made eye contact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why do you think you're being beaten up like this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale recalled the name of the man looking at him from deep inside his memories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Was his name Park Jin Tae?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This bastard was the leader of this shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shelter was a place in the early days of the cataclysm where monsters never approached, a safe place in this hell where monsters could appear at any moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People considered the shelters a gift from 'some being' to allow them the chance to fight against the monsters, similar to how that being had given some people abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'And Park Jin Tae is the ruler of this shelter I'm in right now.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This bastard was a tyrant who did everything as he pleased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He clearly treated the ability users and regular people differently, treating the ability users much better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, he would approve of you even if you were not an ability user, as long as you were useful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why people who were on Park Jin Tae's good side got to rest peacefully inside this shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo's early twenties started at the lowest spot in Park Jin Tae's shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was hated by Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Kim Rok Soo, are you not going to answer me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Park Jin Tae was smiling gently and speaking in a warm voice, he was coldly staring down at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked into those eyes and started to think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What is going on right now? Is it an illusion? Was it one of those dreams he's had until now whenever he fainted?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That didn't seem to be the case, as he could move as he wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then thought about those blood-colored eyes that called itself solitude and despair and had sent him here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I will make you want me.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was what the bastard had said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Call me when you need me. Only I can destroy your despair for you.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It sounded as if it was going to show Cale despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was telling him to follow it if he didn't like that despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It made him want to laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The God of Death…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This blood-colored eyes bastard…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why do they all do whatever the fuck they feel like doing?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It made him annoyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, Kim Rok Soo. Did you not hear the leader-nim telling you to answer him?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the men behind Park Jin Tae scolded Cale. He lifted his foot up and looked ready to kick Cale again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Huuuuuu, enough. That bastard might die at this rate."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, Leader-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae shook his head before starting to speak again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, Rok Soo."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale stopped looking at the sky and looked around him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the building walls were crumbling or cracked, and they were barely standing with their tall shapes mainly gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were many buildings where the metal frames were barely standing as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among those buildings…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see a three-story building with one corner destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the rest of it was fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It didn't seem very different compared to the other buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae whispered to him while laughing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, that building you are looking at right now. Don't you want to go back to the shelter?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That building was the shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It didn't look special or different even though it was a shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But humans barely managed to find that shelter to continue living.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…The shelter that has been maintained for the longest time in this area since the cataclysm."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, that is why it is the most comfortable place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The damn shelter locations changed every so often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shelter with no monsters one day could become overloaded with monsters the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When that happened, a different building became a shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the shelters continued to bleed the humans, as if to tell them that there was no eternal sanctuary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this place…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three-story building Cale was looking at had remained a shelter since the first day of the cataclysm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Each area had one of these locations.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why people called these shelters the 'Central Shelter.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae continued to whisper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And I am the owner of that central shelter."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned toward Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'You weren't the owner from the beginning.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale went through his memories one by one before saying one of the facts he recalled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo's calm voice flowed out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Park Jin Tae is the king of this place right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's expression turned odd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would normally have been angry at the fact that Kim Rok Soo called him Park Jin Tae instead of leader, but Park Jin Tae's anger subsided because Kim Rok Soo had accepted him as king in his calm and confident voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the first time that this arrogant and venomous bastard had accepted Park Jin Tae as the owner of this place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How dare you call the leader-nim by his name? Do you really want to die, you bastard?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae continued to look at Kim Rok Soo who was looking at him even as his subordinate started to shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Jin Tae."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A grandma walked out of the shelter building at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's subordinates started to frown at her appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They seemed more uncomfortable than angry or annoyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The white-haired grandmother cautiously walked over to Park Jin Tae and Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why don't you stop? I'll make sure to talk to Rok Soo."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's eyes teared up at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was someone whom he could never see anymore except in his distant memories because she had passed away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody knew her first name. They just knew that her last name was Kim and called her Grandma Kim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was the only person Park Jin Tae could not treat horribly in this shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale avoided Grandma Kim's gaze as she looked at him with concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than getting kicked in the stomach as soon as he opened his eyes…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than having his calf kicked…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This hurt more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale then heard Park Jin Tae's low voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Looks like you finally realized the reality of the situation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reality that Park Jin Tae was the king.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae did not say that latter part out loud while Cale calmly agreed with him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's right. I need to accept my reality."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was thinking to himself without realizing that Park Jin Tae was looking at him with an odd gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Yes, let's consider this to be real.&lt;br/&gt;
Whether it is the blood-colored eyes' test or whatever…&lt;br/&gt;
Whether this situation was an illusion that'll disappear later…'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slowly raised his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Let's get rid of any regrets.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would get rid of all of his regrets during this chance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked into the eyes of Grandma Kim who was looking at him with concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then recalled one very important fact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This shelter will be destroyed soon.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't know when exactly it was right now, but…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was around the end of fall and the start of winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As if it was an alarm announcing the appearance of the unranked monsters…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All central shelters that existed on earth during this time lost their special properties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That meant that the central shelters were attacked by monsters and destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And they would attack differently than normal, as if they were trying to invade the shelters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These monsters would attack the central shelters in waves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That also means that there will be new central shelters.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central shelters that looked different than before would appear exactly 24 hours after the first central shelters were destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He did not like Park Jin Tae and his lackeys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he could not let the people here die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Himself, Kim Rok Soo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, there was Grandma Kim. Oh, there were some other people as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People that team leader Lee Soo Hyuk had saved were here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before Park Jin Tae showed his greed…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Soo Hyuk was in charge of this shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'But the team leader has already left.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Team leader Lee Soo Hyuk who had now left for more dangerous places had been the 'center' of this central shelter before Park Jin Tae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'And the team leader left this place in Grandma Kim and Park Jin Tae's care.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both Grandma Kim and Park Jin Tae were good people at that time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Of course, Park Jin Tae revealed his true nature as soon as the team leader left and started to rule over this central shelter like a tyrant.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The central shelter had to create a new system under the person who was the strongest attack-type ability user after Lee Soo Hyuk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that system was one that Park Jin Tae wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…But even Park Jin Tae found it difficult to handle Grandma Kim.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae could not treat Grandma Kim, who had healing abilities, rudely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He slightly bowed to the grandma and looked toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It'll be smart to act with that reality in mind next time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae offered him his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale grabbed that hand and stood up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae watched Kim Rok Soo sit back down before letting go of his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then turned around and walked away from the shelter building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are going to hunt."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His subordinates followed behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min who was Park Jin Tae's right-hand man caught up to him and started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you going to let Kim Rok Soo go like this? Shouldn't we beat him to a pulp when we have the chance?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae's fox-like eyes turned sharp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Chul Min's shoulders slightly shook after seeing that gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae quietly looked at him for a while before finally starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That bastard was the only one."&lt;br/&gt;
"Excuse me?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…Kim Rok Soo is the only initial shelter member who still considered Lee Soo Hyuk, the person who has still not returned, to be this shelter's king."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people came and went from the central shelters since the beginning of the cataclysm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were some people who had survived since then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These people were called the initial shelter members and Park Jin Tae just considered them 'Lee Soo Hyuk's people.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it had been over 10 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Soo Hyuk who left to help a different region that was having difficulties had not returned, and Grandma Kim, as well as the rest of Lee Soo Hyuk's people had started to accept Park Jin Tae's system one by one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They probably had no choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They wanted to survive as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Kim Rok Soo…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This useless bastard without any abilities never accepted Park Jin Tae as the owner of this place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, that bastard is someone who didn't accept the concept of, 'king' in the first place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honestly speaking, Kim Rok Soo's acceptance did not matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was the same as the other useless parasites that were surviving in this shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he found that venomous gaze annoying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why even an ability user like Lee Chul Min was worried that he got on Park Jin Tae's nerves just now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Kim Rok Soo was different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ha, haha-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae started to refreshingly laugh out loud for the first time in a long while.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He did not look toward where Kim Rok Soo was anymore and headed for the hunting ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hunting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's what it was called, but it was more of a difficult battle for food that could result in them losing their lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it was his responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim confirmed that Park Jin Tae was moving away before putting her hand on Cale's shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Aigoo, why didn't you just run the errand for him?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slowly remembered why he had been beaten up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Errand. In other words, starting shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Grandma Kim mentioned, Park Jin Tae always made Kim Rok Soo, who didn't accept him as king, to run errands for him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He seemed to have been beaten up today after trying to not do that errand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Whether this is an illusion or whatever…'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale touched his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It hurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anything that hurts was real.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Let's change it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you think it will go as you please?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flinch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's shoulders shook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was that bastard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood-colored eyes. It was the voice of the bastard who sent Cale into this situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for me if you want to escape this despair. Then you won't have to face these past despairs any longer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale responded internally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Is he plotting something? I need to go back quickly.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other being must have heard it as it responded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will not plot anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Then you'll just sit back and watch?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes, I'll just watch. Until you ask me for help, that is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Will this situation end if I ask you for help?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes. And you will need to let me in if you receive my help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Let you in?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I mean that you will become a member of the Demonic race and carry on my will.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Become a member of the Demonic race?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard the blood-colored eyes' voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm sure you don't want that right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;But will that continue to be the case? Will you be okay while you are helpless and facing these despairs again?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I will just sit back and watch all that. I will wait for the day you come to me with delight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale quickly asked after hearing the voice become faint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Is this real? Did I return to the past?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I do not have the power to turn back time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The voice sounded as if it was laughing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is just an endless despair that will repeat itself without ever ending, and a test.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The voice sounded as if it was looking forward to something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flail around in despair. I will give you the power to escape from despair.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He did not hear the blood-colored eyes' voice any longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, Rok Soo."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale felt a warm hand over his hand that was on his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim cautiously continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I like your temperament, but can't you be a little more flexible?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She knew that Park Jin Tae was in the wrong, but she could not attack him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All she could do was treat the injured with her healing abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She might be the reason Kim Rok Soo managed to survive under Park Jin Tae since team leader Lee Soo Hyuk left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll need to stay on good terms with Park Jin Tae for now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim's eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Do you mean that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slowly nodded his head and looked toward Park Jin Tae's back in the distance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That bastard was a dictator and treated people differently based on their abilities, however…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the day the central shelter was destroyed…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He protected this place until the end.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae fought until the last moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was how Kim Rok Soo and some other people who had no abilities were able to escape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What are you doing? Why the hell are you so slow? A bastard like you without any abilities should at least run! Get lost! You're in my way, so hurry up and run!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale recalled the things Park Jin Tae had shouted to him in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae ended up dying while fighting to the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grandma Kim had lost her life in that battle as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Park Jin Tae was a bad bastard and he hated him, but…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'In some ways, he saved my life.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo was able to survive in the past thanks to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked toward the shelter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would erase his regrets one by one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would save this shelter, and then…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'll go meet the team leader and Choi Jung Soo.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seomyeon, Busan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was where an unranked monster first appeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale subconsciously blurted out loud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I wonder if everybody is okay-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He started to recall the faces of his friends one by one, starting with Raon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How would he be in the real world right now? Would he have fainted?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He started to become concerned about his friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honestly speaking, he was most worried about them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I need to find a way out of here first.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There had to be a way to get out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There had to be a way to get out of here without accepting the blood-colored eyes' offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He recalled the last thing the blood-colored eyes told him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Flail around in despair. I will give you the power to escape from despair.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of Cale's lips started to go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale clenched his skinny hands into fists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Flail around in despair? That won't happen. I'll just make it not a despair anymore.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had no way to know for sure, but he felt as if he would only be able to return if he destroyed the despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It's just a feeling.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was his intuition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there was a good amount of analysis in it as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was because of what the blood-colored eyes told him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I will give you the power to escape from despair.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Didn't that sound like he would be able to get out of this situation and return to the real world if he had the power to destroy the despair within it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It had also called it a test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale thought that it was a reasonable thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And looking at this situation with that in mind…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It's doable.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current Cale was able to destroy these despairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was worth trying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-555"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-557"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-556</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 555: Pretty Useless Bastard (1)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-555</link><description>&lt;p&gt;"What do you mean by that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han heard a voice behind his back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu was standing there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Who?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cage did not recognize Alberu who was wearing a mask and changed his voice and looked at him with wariness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to speak at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sounded almost as if he was shouting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's no way that-!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Lower your voice."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu squeezed Choi Han's shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peek. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu then peeked toward the closed strategy room door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had followed behind Choi Han because he found it odd that Choi Han suddenly left the room with an odd expression and managed to hear part of what Cage said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Their vow of death with Cale disappearing means-'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It meant that he was dead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu quietly whispered to Choi Han who was looking at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you want Duke Fredo to hear everything? You want the enemies to hear everything? You want them to know about this situation?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han's open mouth closed shut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han then peeked toward the closed strategy room door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu continued to whisper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I closed the door as soon as Cale was brought up, so they shouldn't have been able to hear inside."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han finally sighed in relief after hearing Alberu's comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But then he immediately started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to go to the Endable Kingdom. We need to hurry over to the Endable Kingdom."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han's fingertips were shaking. The same words continued to come out of his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to hurry over to the End-"&lt;br/&gt;
"Be quiet!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han could see Alberu's expression after hearing him shout in an annoyed voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han's eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Has Alberu Crossman ever been so openly annoyed or angry before?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Never.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han realized that Alberu was stressed out as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu continued to mumble in an annoyed voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm thinking. Thinking. I'm thinking about what to do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Cale Henituse died? He suddenly died like that? He died even with Eruhaben and Bud by his side? Was that possible?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu heard the strategy room's door slam open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then groaned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu could see a shaking black Dragon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"T, the human!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raon approached them while holding a video communication device with his shaking paws.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crackle. Crackle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black mana was fluctuating in an irregular manner around Raon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crackle!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video communication device was starting to crack because of the mana. The mana continued to get bigger and stronger as it fluctuated around Raon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raon barely managed to speak after seeing Alberu's stiff expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…T, they said that the human d, disappeared. G, Goldie gramps- gramps, he-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu took a deep breath after seeing Raon being unable to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked inside the strategy room past Raon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lord Sheritt, Duke Fredo, and the Dragon half-blood were inside the strategy room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredo had his arms crossed as he observed them with an odd expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…You son of a bitch."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Cale Henituse. Just what the hell are you going around doing? Did something happen to you? …First of all.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu thought about Eruhaben's description of how Cale had disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'We don't know if he is dead.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that case…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Choi Han."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir."&lt;br/&gt;
"You go to the Endable Kingdom."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu looked at Fredo and took off his mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His skin, eyes, and hair color all changed at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"……!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu continued to speak as Duke Fredo's eyes opened wide and his jaw dropped in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will go to the palace first and then head over too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han and Alberu made eye contact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then I will be heading out first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han and Alberu started to walk in different directions after that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale couldn't breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…It's hard to breathe……'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He wanted to breathe, but he could not take a breath properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He couldn't open his eyes and his ears felt numb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He couldn't even smell anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I remember getting caught by the black hand and being dragged somewhere…'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he couldn't remember anything after that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some odd reason, Cale was breathing even though he felt as if he was suffocating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Cale tried his best to move his body in this situation…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Damn it! What the hell is going on?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It'd be one thing if he could even squirm, but his body wasn't allowing him to make any movements at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Child who has escaped the hand of god and his fate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale felt his heart sink after suddenly hearing the chilling voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first of his senses to be permitted back to him was his hearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. Boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His heart was beating wildly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humans, no, living beings are meant to be born and then eventually die. That is the law of nature and their fate. You've gone against that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Who is this? Is the black hand talking? What is the black hand?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Furthermore, time is warped for you as well. You are you, but also not you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;His body started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second thing Cale was permitted to do in this situation was to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was an instinctual fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cale Barrow. I thought that only that child was qualified to carry on my powers. But you are the same.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale suddenly felt as if his ears suddenly opened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then had a strong urge to talk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His mouth then opened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who are you?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Me?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard a low laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Just as the Divine race worships the gods, there are beings the Demonic race worships as well. I am a being the Demonic race worships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'A being the Demonic race worships?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I've been in a deep slumber, waking up for a short duration of time over and over after being sealed by the gods a long time ago.&lt;br/&gt;
"…So, who the hell are you?"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale suddenly felt a large hand caressing his back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a terrible fear filled his body each time the hand touched him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That voice whispered in Cale's ear at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am wickedness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale took a deep breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The voice continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am solitude. I am despair.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A being that was wickedness, solitude, and despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am all things that humans like you do not want.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was a being that brought out a human's instinctual fear and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A being whose presence itself turns into fear, but something that still exists somewhere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's eyes suddenly opened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He made eye contact with the thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That is who I am.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood-colored eyes were looking at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Mmph!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He instantly felt as if he could not breathe again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have faced solitude, resigned in front of despair, were in pain, and had to face the wickedness surrounding you many times. Furthermore, you escaped your fate and the hands of a god, your time is warped, and you are you but not you at the same time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Kim Rok Soo, he had lost all things that were precious to him and escaped his fated death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, he was both Kim Rok Soo and Cale Henituse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Child.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood-colored eyes smiled as it whispered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you want me as well?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His lips were shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He managed to speak even as they shook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you crazy?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of Cale's lips were shaking as one corner started to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My dream is to be a rich slacker. You crazy bastard."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'm a human who even rejected becoming the Saint for the God of Death.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hahahaha-&lt;br/&gt;
"Ugh!"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale felt as if his ears would rip apart at this laughter that was shaking the area. It felt as if his eardrums would truly burst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the other being seemed to enjoy this situation quite a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Funny, very funny.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The eyes got closer to Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are more entertaining than the other child.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale and the eyes looked at each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How could the two of you have moved in such different directions while being placed in the same situation?&lt;br/&gt;
"So what?"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I also find it entertaining that you keep talking back without giving up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood-colored eyes moved back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale suddenly felt as if his body was being pressed down from all directions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The eerie voice whispered to him at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will make you want me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Call me when you need me. Only I can destroy your despair for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale then felt as if his body was being sucked away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood-colored eyes started to become distant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Where am I going?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Ugh!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then clenched his eyes shut after feeling terrible pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His senses became paralyzed again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All connections he had with the world started to break once again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale desperately moved in order to try to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Huuuuuuu!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And once he could breathe again…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale felt a terrible pain at his stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His body flew up into the air before falling down to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh, ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's body rolled backward on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What is going on?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone had hit his stomach as soon as he returned to his senses, making him fly up before rolling on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale reached his hand out and grabbed the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes focused again and he realized something was odd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Cement?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was cracked and partially destroyed, but he could see the cement floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This material was something that did not go with Cale Henituse's world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey! You bastard, can't you even stand up straight? Where did that arrogant attitude of yours from just now go? Hmm?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Kekeke! Hey, hey, control yourself. You kicked him so hard that he can't even get up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were speaking in Korean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Uggh……..!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale tried his best to hold back his groan as he flipped his body over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see a grey ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…When was it that my body was this weak?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had no strength in his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see his thin wrists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale then saw people step between him and the grey ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, this bastard looks like a mess."&lt;br/&gt;
"That's why he should have just done what we told him to do, instead of acting up!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These people who were sneering at him and looking down at Cale with scorn…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were Korean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ha!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale remembered them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He remembered their faces… He remembered this situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a time when it wouldn't be weird for him to be beaten up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…It's those bastards."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It's one of those bastards who hit me at that time.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He… hehe."&lt;br/&gt;
"What the hell? Did this bastard go crazy after getting hit once?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was less than 1 year since the world was flipped over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winter of the cataclysm had passed, spring and summer had come by, and then it was fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was that first fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was late fall when the unranked monster appeared in Seoul and filled the world with fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turned the world into chaos and the largest number of people died at that time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How dare a young bastard like you glare at me like that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the fall when the pretty useless Kim Rok Soo was the most useless in his life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had opened his eyes as Kim Rok Soo at the end of that fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood flowing out of the corner of his mouth told him that this situation was real.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Damn it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Whether you are wickedness, despair, or solitude… That black hand bastard…'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's eyes were full of fire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How annoying."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people surrounding him started to frown after hearing that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What? What nonsense is this lunatic spewing now?! Do you want to die?"&lt;br/&gt;
"This bastard! How dare a bastard who could easily die at any moment look at us with such a gaze?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale let those comments in one ear and out the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The place the unranked monster first appeared…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people died at that location.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Death and fear that could not be compared to what they faced since the cataclysm had swept the area where that unranked monster had appeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why the world started to gather together again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, that terrible incident let the world create societies again and stand back up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few of the people who made it back alive from that incident location ended up becoming the central figures of the Korean society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Team leader."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Team leader Lee Soo Hyuk was one of the people who had experienced that incident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Hey, do you know where I saw our team leader in the past? I'm someone who survived that incident as well. You remember that terrible incident? I survived that incident. I also saw our team leader fight.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Jung Soo had been there as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them managed to survive that situation, but many lives were taken by that unranked monster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Jung Soo had spoken with a teary expression in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I really thought that I was in hell when I saw that.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fire in Cale's eyes started to burn even brighter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-554"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-556"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-555</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 05:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 554: You should have watched your back (8)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-554</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A dull noise echoed in the hall along with the black smoke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom! Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two people's bodies slammed into the wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh! Why did you suddenly use your wind, w, what the…?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton groaned at the sudden impact and her eyes opened wide as she tried to look at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her eyes were focused on the black smoke on top of the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black smoke was spreading thick and quickly, looking as if it could fill the whole area in an instant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Damn it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the other person who also crashed into the wall… Cale glared at Gersey who was on the other side of the black door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was almost tricked."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then looked back at the black smoke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This black smoke must have been the way to provide the feed to the monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It can't get out of the platform."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black smoke only roamed around the platform and did not flow out of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton walked up to the platform and tapped on the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tang tang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It looks like there is a transparent barrier separating the platform and the area underneath the platform once the black smoke came out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She roamed around the platform and nodded her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess it needs to be like this so that Gersey can provide the feed and then he and his subordinates could safely get out."&lt;br/&gt;
"But doesn't it seem like it would be impossible to steal the sculptures like this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale got up and headed next to Cotton. He was now underneath the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey who was outside the black door could not see him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Gersey clicked his tongue as if he could see what was going on. He had more blood flowing out from his mouth than Eruhaben did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How disappointing. I guess I have no choice but to overdo it a bit."&lt;br/&gt;
"Hehehe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He turned his head after hearing someone laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud was laughing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you sad that you failed to give the feed to them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of Gersey's lips started to go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But thanks to that, you are unable to steal nor destroy the sculptures."&lt;br/&gt;
"…What do you mean?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud who didn't know about the black smoke and the transparent barrier started to frown while Gersey laughed and turned around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, you're here, your majesty?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben's eyes started to sink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star was walking over in the distance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He spoke to Bud in his mind while Gersey greeted the White Star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is bad. Looks like we need to escape.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud silently nodded his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard the White Star's voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's so noisy starting the first day of the festival."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben retorted back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's only loud because you are making it that way, isn't it?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Hahaha, is that so? Well, it looks like I need to get rid of you first before Cale Henituse can steal those things."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chhhhhhhhhh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A red sword shot out from the White Star's hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will destroy the wall, your majesty."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey grabbed his fan and charged toward the gold wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tatap!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He lightly kicked off the ground, jumped up into the air, and struck down with the hand holding the fan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fan touched the gold wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaaaaaang-!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fan started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey stumbled as he landed on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large cave started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That shaking had started from inside the black door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey instantly thought about something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on Cale Henituse's past actions…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is he using his ancient powers to destroy it-?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He might have used his ancient powers to their limits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would the barrier be able to withstand his attack?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was he planning on destroying this whole cave at the same time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Chief Priest!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard the White Star scold him at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can't you even feel what power it is?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Power?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey looked back toward the black door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a gap on the door, but it was not wide enough to see everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he could feel the aura flowing out through the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…P, perhaps-"&lt;br/&gt;
"That 'perhaps' seems to be the case."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey turned pale after hearing the White Star's response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"W, why is that honorable power coming right now-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was no longer an issue of their big plan being destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The honorable power had responded to Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why? That power should not be able to respond to Cale Henituse?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey's mind started to turn white.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looked like both their big plan and the current situation might end up twisted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll go first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star walked past Gersey who was somewhat out of it and swung his sword toward the gold wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I never expected that power to respond to Cale Henituse!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His relaxed expression had turned urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why he was using the sword at full power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wall was easily split.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben coughed up blood and moved back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, he had been preparing to escape, so he was not injured too much from the wall breaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he had no choice but to open his eyes wide and turn around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How could such an enormous amount of power-!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could feel a strong power behind his back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fuck!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also heard the White Star's angry shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben could see the black door and the wall exploding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's body was curled up as she was flung out of there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shit!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud caught Cotton as he shouted in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell happened?!"&lt;br/&gt;
"T, the barrier broke and a weird power- a scary power-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud was about to urge her to respond until he realized that her body was shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He quickly looked toward where the door had been.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud subconsciously started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…What the?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then took a step back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had chills all over his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a natural reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cale!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see Eruhaben stumbling as he charged forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud had never seen Eruhaben moving so urgently before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Damn it! No!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star was also shouting as he urgently rushed forward and passed Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His face showed both anger and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Ah!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud finally thought to look for Cale. Cotton had been flung out, but Cale had not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He overcame the fear that was filling his body and looked back toward that direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He saw Cale there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had plopped on the ground right in front of the thing that was giving him such terrible fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…What the hell is this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's eyes opened wide as he sat there on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had not been flung out with that explosion just now, but he was on the ground because he fell down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He lowered his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What's going on?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His whole body was shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unranked monster that had killed all his teammates… A pressure that was much worse than when he had gone up against that monster was overwhelming him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale lifted his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The thing giving him that fear was right in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a black hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hand was so large that it could almost touch the ceiling of the hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What could be going on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What is happening all of a sudden?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale recalled his actions just now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'All I did was get close to the platform.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All he did was move toward Cotton who was observing the black smoke and the transparent barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the black smoke inside the transparent barrier… That had suddenly disappeared and a large black hand shot up from the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The power of that hand made the transparent barrier explode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Cale was looking at that black hand right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The eight sculptures?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He wasn't paying them any attention right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He thought it was weird that they didn't have a scratch on them after such a large explosion, but he had no time to look into that right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. Boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His heart was beating as if it wanted to explode and he had chills all over his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kiiiiiiiiiiiiiii-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black hand started to move while making that odd noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The palm stopped in front of Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You disturbed my slumber.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before Cale could even think about the meaning behind those words…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cale! Dodge!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's mind was filled by a voice that seemed to come from the black hand as Eruhaben shouted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here is another punk who has found a way out of god's hand and escaped his fate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black hand reached out and surrounded Cale while making an eerie noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had instantly fallen into darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bang, bang bang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock had a confused expression after hearing someone banging on the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tiger warriors stationed outside would not knock like this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who could it be?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock debated whether he should open the door or not. He wondered if he should call the adults who were all gathered in the strategy room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard a voice from the other side of the door at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please open the door!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Huh?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He recognized the voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It made sense why the Tiger warriors would have let this person through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock quickly opened the door as he was relieved that it was someone he knew and welcomed the person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cage-nim!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Huff. Huff. Huff."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cage was outside the door trying to catch her breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's been so long!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock warmly welcomed her but Cage didn't even respond to his greeting as she urgently rushed into the black castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Did something-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock was trying to ask what was going on in shock before stiffening up after seeing what, no, who, was in Cage's hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"W, wait- this person is?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock who barely managed to get some words out looked toward the person who was being dragged by the collar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's been a while."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This person was Saint Jack who looked as if he didn't know what to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was suddenly dragged here and I don't even know wh-"&lt;br/&gt;
"Dragon!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saint Jack gave an awkward greeting, but… His greeting was drowned out by Cage's shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cage looked toward Lock and started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Where is the Dragon? The Dragon?!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Excuse me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A Dragon that can cast long-distance teleportation! Or at least Miss Rosalyn! No, it needs to be a Dragon, a Dragon!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Just what-"&lt;br/&gt;
"Young master Cale was cut!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Excuse me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock became anxious after suddenly hearing her mention Cale but Cage looked around as if things were urgent before running toward the stairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock followed behind her as Cage continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You know about the vow of death, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cage continued to look around as if she couldn't even see Lock who was anxiously following behind her and then resumed speaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She seemed to be looking for someone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Young master Cale and I made a vow of death, you know? There's a power you feel gathering around your hand when you make a vow. It is the power that lets you know whether that person kept or broke the vow."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the eerie feeling that seeped into the bodies of the people making the vow of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But that was just cut off."&lt;br/&gt;
"Really?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jack who had been dragged here without knowing why looked toward her in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cage didn't respond to his question and just continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There should be someone else who is feeling this right now. He should be feeling that something is weird."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screeeech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They then heard a door opening on the second floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lock turned toward the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han was walking out of the strategy room with a confused yet serious expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Didn't hyung say that he had a lot of things to do?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han who said he had important business to take care of was coming out with a serious expression before finishing his work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, Miss Cage!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked extremely happy to see Cage. It was as if he had found the person who could answer his question for him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han stepped onto the stairs and walked toward her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Miss Cage, when did you get here? You see, umm, I made a vow of death with Cale-nim once-"&lt;br/&gt;
"The presence that entered your body when you made the vow disappeared, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han flinched and looked at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cage let go of Saint Jack's collar and continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People who make a vow of death are able to tell whether the vow was kept or broken by that power in their body."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Death was the result if the vow was broken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence inside the body would tell the other person that the vow was broken and that the other party was dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But there are times the presence itself disappears from a person's body. That means that the vow of death is cut."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cage slowly walked over to Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her voice echoed through the staircase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's only one reason that a vow of death would be cut."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her face stiffened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is when the vow becomes useless."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was only one reason a vow of death would become useless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That means that the other person is dead."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All expressions disappeared from Choi Han's face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-553"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-555"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-554</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 553: You should have watched your back (7)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-553</link><description>&lt;p&gt;"Cale Henituse, what is it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton anxiously looked at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why is he suddenly acting like this?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was completely pale and sweating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't even seem to hear Cotton calling his name as he just stared inside the black door with a piercing gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What is inside that is making you react like this?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton slightly pulled on Cale's shoulder and tried to look inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's gaze moved to Cotton potentially because of her action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why does he look so vicious-'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton couldn't help but flinch at Cale's gaze that looked ready to beat someone to death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale pulled her arm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He pulled firmly enough that Cotton frowned before her eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He's shaking?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's hand that was pulling her was shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton finally realized that there was something else in Cale's eyes in addition to this anger to beat someone to death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hurry up and look inside."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale sounded stoic as usual, but his tone sounded urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton looked inside the door at his urging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could see an octagonal platform, eight altars, and eight sculptures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Deputy Chief Priest, do you know what those sculptures are?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale waited for Cotton's response with a shaking heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. Boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His heart was slowly starting to beat faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why, just why?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why were the monsters he saw in Korea here as sculptures?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's mind moved past complicated to chaotic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Six of them.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had records of six of those sculptures, no, six of those monsters, in his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were the monsters that were evaluated to be the six strongest monsters in Korea and the world. The ones on the altar looked exactly the same as the ones recorded in his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'My record is never wrong.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When he was in Korea, the records of these unrankable monsters had been shared via video throughout the world and Cale was the person in his company who remembered the most information about these monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I memorized every single piece of information about them.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once Team Leader Lee Soo Hyuk, Choi Jung Soo, and his other team members had died, Kim Rok Soo had recorded every piece of information he could find about monsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He couldn't let something like that happen ever again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was his duty as the new team leader to keep his team members safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was especially true because his new team all had family members waiting for them, unlike himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why Kim Rok Soo had gathered more information about monsters than anybody else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foreign records, research, videos… He found anything he could get his hands on and recorded them in his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monster rankings, appearances, battle patterns, attacks, he didn't even disregard the trivial information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why he knew very well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He knew how terrible these monsters were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also knew how many lives they had taken in Korea and the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Motherfucker!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to frown while looking down at his shaking hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Cotton's voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I don't know. I've never seen those before."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton looked toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those creatures do not exist in this world."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale clenched his shaking hands into fists. He shared the thoughts that had been on his mind since earlier once his hands stopped shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Are they monsters from the Demon World?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something that Gersey and the White Star might be preparing that wasn't from this world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wasn't the Demon World the only explanation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Does that mean monsters from the Demon World appeared on Earth? Why?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's mind started to become complicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see Cotton hesitate for a moment before responding to his question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't know. There's a chance that that is the case, but I can't be sure."&lt;br/&gt;
"Huuuuu."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale subconsciously let out a deep breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He turned back toward the gap in the black door that was wide enough for a person to walk through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Deputy Chief Priest, according to what you said earlier, the White Star and Gersey brought them 'feed.' They brought feed for monsters, but I don't see any living creatures inside there."&lt;br/&gt;
"…That's right."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's heart started to beat with an ominous feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What if it really is a monster from the Demon World?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That terrible thought made her stomach churn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton and Cale made eye contact. The two of them realized that they were thinking about the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was the first to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those sculptures are probably those monsters. This sculpture state should be the seal. The White Star and Gersey are planning on removing those seals… During the ritual on the last day of the festival."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both of them imagined the terrible sight that would happen after that even without discussing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, Cale imagined a much worse situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disasters that had struck Earth rushed past his mind like a movie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By the way…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned toward Cotton after hearing her voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…The altars with the sculptures are all slightly different in height. Do you think there is a reason for that?"&lt;br/&gt;
"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked back inside the black door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'They're different!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The altars were different in height as Cotton mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Hey. You don't look very good."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton could see that Cale was starting to look even worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Shit!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cale couldn't even hear Cotton's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The altars were different in height as Cotton mentioned. That was why they looked so uneven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I missed that because I was too focused on the monsters.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale focused on the parts he missed before getting the chills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sculpture on the lowest altar…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That monster was the unranked monster that was ranked sixth of the group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next lowest altar had the monster ranked fifth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the monster that was said to be the strongest monster in the history of Earth…was on the third highest altar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Does the height of the altar show the strength of the monster?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that case…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…There are two altars higher than the highest-ranked monster on Earth.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That meant…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Those two are even stronger?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale got the chills. The strongest monster in the history of Earth was truly a calamity. But there were two that were even stronger than that one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cale Henituse. What are you planning on doing? Should we go in first?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could hear Cotton speaking to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton was worried about Cale's complexion but continued to speak as they needed to take care of this problem first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to destroy that seal, well, this facility. We don't have much time. We have no time to hesitate. You know that too."&lt;br/&gt;
"…That's right. I know tha-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned around in shock after hearing an explosion that was loud enough to make his ears go numb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Craaaackle, crackle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The half-transparent gold wall was starting to shake while being hit with a grey current.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eruhaben-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could see the bleeding Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He subconsciously started to move toward Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Don't come here!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he soon had to stop walking because of Eruhaben's shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben glared to the other side of the gold wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey was on the other side of the half-transparent wall, removing his fan that was covered in grey aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're enduring better than I expected."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One corner of Gersey's lip twisted up while looking at Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oooooo- oooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The grey aura was gathering above Gersey's head and forming a large orb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben peeked toward the grey orb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…This is bad.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey had attacked the gold wall just now with about one-third of the aura from this grey orb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He somehow managed to block it, but Eruhaben was worried about what came next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I can't hold on if he uses the rest of that aura to attack."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wall would fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben knew that that would be the case, which was why he started to shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why are you all standing around like idiots?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice thundered down on the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cale, why aren't you going inside? You need to hurry up and destroy it so we can teleport and run away!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was preparing for the worst and thinking about running away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale headed back to the black door after hearing that. Cale had to show decent results when Eruhaben was pushing himself so hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hurry up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale put a leg through the gap in the black door. His foot touched the bottom of the large hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shaaaaa-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An ominous chill immediately overwhelmed him, but Cale had to go in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I must know.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He needed to know what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale grabbed and then let go of the golden top's whip before pushing the rest of his body through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'll let them know!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Chaos, destruction, peace. Don't worry.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale who confirmed that the Elementals who had stealthily followed them were there and then motioned to Bud with his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll help you, sir."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud walked next to Eruhaben and pointed his aura sword at Gersey who was on the other side of the wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale heard Gersey shout behind him at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The seal will be released if you destroy it!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben who had been listening to Cale and Cotton's conversation started to shout again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shut up! It seems like you are trying to summon a monster from the Demon World based on their conversation, but the summoning should be impossible if we destroy the location of the summoning! How dare you try to lie!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smirk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey sneered at Eruhaben and opened his fan again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chhhhhhhh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who said anything about summoning? Those sculptures are prisons with the monsters sealed inside. The moment you destroy that prison…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The open fan started to absorb the grey orb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hell will start in this world."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fan that absorbed over half of the orb was pointed at the wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey calmly added on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tsk. It's not yet time. All that'll be left is destruction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He's being serious.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben could tell that Gersey was telling the truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It's bad news for both the White Star and us if we destroy the seals!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What could they do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As his mind became complicated…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then, what if we don't destroy them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Cale's calm voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was looking at Gersey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess it's fine as long as we don't destroy them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey kept his mouth shut. The corners of Cale's lips started to go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His body was already over halfway into the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then moved completely in through the black door. He looked at Gersey through the crack in the black door and continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What if I don't destroy them and just steal them?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey's pupils started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale did not miss that reaction. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smirk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of Cale's lips started to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If they are prisons holding the monsters captive, then I just need to run and take the prisons with me."&lt;br/&gt;
"Y, you crazy bastard-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fan started to shake furiously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cale! That's enough provoking! I don't care if you steal it or whatever, just hurry!&lt;br/&gt;
"If you don't push yourself too hard, sir-"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sure, sure! I won't overdo it and I will get out of here alive! So hurry! We can just leave everything and run away if all else fails!&lt;br/&gt;
"As long as you promise, sir."&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale leisurely responded to Eruhaben's urgent voice before he quickly started to head toward the octagonal platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His expression was completely different than when he had just leisurely responded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. Boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His heart was beating fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why had the monsters suddenly appeared on Earth?&lt;br/&gt;
Furthermore, why were those same monsters here, and what was their relationship with the Demon World?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The truth seemed to be in front of his nose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Haiyah!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale heard Cotton climb through the door behind him as well but did not have the time to look back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He needed to hurry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale stepped on top of the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then quickly started to compare the sculptures' appearances with his records.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also looked around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…There's nothing else here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sculptures were the only things in this place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The eight sculptures were positioned in a circle on top of the platform and the center was empty without any sort of magic circle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were no traces of a magic circle ever being there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…How did they provide the feed?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A thought flew past Cale's mind like a streak of lightning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also looked at Gersey who looked like he would swing his fan to attack him but was instead just glaring at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Did you find something? Do you think we really can't destroy these things?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton stepped on top of the platform and walked toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale pushed her back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was using the Sound of the Wind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chhhh, Gersey's fan shot out grey light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Creatures born in the darkness, hunt down your feed!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black smoke started to rise from the empty center of the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-552"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-554"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-553</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 552: You should have watched your back (6)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-552</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Cale quietly observed the fear in Cotton's eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why is she so scared that Gersey is chasing us?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben started to speak as Cale remained quiet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Will we need to capture Gersey?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton shook her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is not a good idea, sir."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was speaking respectfully to the ancient Dragon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Based on Gersey's personality, he would have immediately contacted the White Star after suppressing my subordinates. He will only enter the underground passage after doing that. He does not make rash movements. He is the thorough type."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben understood the meaning behind those words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're saying that it is better to destroy this place before the White Star comes rather than handling Gersey?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir, that's right."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton took a map out of her pocket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In order to destroy the cave, it is best to destroy it from the innermost area."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She looked at the map as she started to walk to the inner area of the cave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, she was running.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The third location is the most important place, so it is most effective to destroy that spot!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not getting all this dead mana was a pity, but it was not a facility that needed to be destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom! Boom! Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They heard noises coming from the top of the stairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…It must be Gersey's trusted subordinates! Hurry up!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She became anxious and started to move even faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Aaaaah!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She suddenly felt as if her body was starting to float up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her two feet actually did leave the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She looked toward Cale who was now next to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to go quickly if we need to hurry. We'll be late if we ran."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were whirlwinds at the tips of Cale's feet and her feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud and Eruhaben looked ready to quickly shoot forward as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton looked down at her feet for a moment before nodding her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Okay! I'll guide you!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She started to move even faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was up there next to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes observed the numerous glass containers full of dead mana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could feel the numerous lives that were lost in order to create this much dead mana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That is why I need to completely destroy this facility.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale made up his mind as he started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why are you in such a rush? You seem extremely scared."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton stopped biting down on her lips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I told you that the third location was the most important, right? I also said I have proof that is the case."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. Boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They could still hear people rushing down behind them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who the hell were Gersey's trusted subordinates that they were making so much noise heading down?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale noticed a wall and door at the end of the glass containers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to speak while looking at that door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We received dead mana from many places."&lt;br/&gt;
"The Mogoru Empire?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, The Mogoru Empire was one of those places."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud asked in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You received it from other places too?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to frown as she turned her head toward Bud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't have time to explain all of that right now!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She looked at the map over and over as she continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The underground facility was created when the white castle was created. I participated in its creation, but the innermost area of this facility… I couldn't hear anything about the third location."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's expression turned odd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had heard that it took a long time between the beginning of the Endable Kingdom's construction and the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the Deputy Chief Priest who seemed to be in her twenties had participated in all of it and was still alive?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…I guess I can't trust her appearance.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale finally fully understood that she was an illusionist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I did think that it was an important place at first, but I didn't suspect anything after that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale focused on what Cotton had to say again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But once our grasp on the Mogoru Empire ended, Gersey started to enter the third location very frequently."&lt;br/&gt;
"It hasn't been that long then."&lt;br/&gt;
"Haaaaa."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could see Cotton sighing in response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She quietly looked at Cale and responded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Was it short even if 24 lives disappeared every day?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's face stiffened as Cotton started to speak faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It happens every eight hours. Gersey brings his trusted subordinates with him and brings 'feed' to the third facility."&lt;br/&gt;
"That 'feed' was humans?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…Sometimes it was humans, but there were other living beings as well. Regardless of their origin, they brought eight living beings three times a day."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton who was extremely sensitive to Gersey's movements and had been observing his daily routine had picked up on this odd routine at some point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How did you know that if you can't go to that area?"&lt;br/&gt;
"His subordinates find the feed from outside. Gersey isn't with them at that time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed that although Gersey was always with his subordinates to come in here and deliver the feed to the third location, only his subordinates went out to find the feed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Once I figured that out, I cast an illusion and stealthily followed them once."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton let out a small sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I heard one of the subordinates talking at that time. He's the only one of Gersey's trusted subordinates who can talk. This is what that bastard said."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's feet landed on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She grabbed the lock on the door to the second location as she continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was repeating the things Gersey's subordinate said at that time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He said, 'we need to hurry up and find the feed for those monsters!' "&lt;br/&gt;
"…Monsters?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes. He then quickly added on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale made eye contact with Cotton.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;" 'The day those terrible things are no longer sealed… We must give everything we have to fulfill our liege's orders as that day will be the day our liege and our majesty's dreams all come true!' "&lt;br/&gt;
"…And then?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I got caught."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ring on her finger started to shake along with the lock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Click click. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She started to move the lock around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I had to quickly run away because Gersey's subordinates found me. I barely made it back alive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud, who had been thinking about what she just said, started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All of their dreams will come true on the day the seal is removed. It seems like…the third location is very important as the Deputy Chief Priest mentioned."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale nodded his head and started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have a feeling that the seal will be removed on the last day of the festival."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was thinking the same thing. That is why we need to hurry up and destroy that place first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud hesitated for a moment before asking a question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you think we can destroy it if those terrible monsters are there? Aren't we in danger?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Do I look weak?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud flinched and waved his hands around after hearing Eruhaben's question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah, Eruhaben-nim, It's not like that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben chuckled at Bud's reaction and added on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It shouldn't be too dangerous if they are still sealed and Gersey and his subordinates are able to freely come and go to give the feed."&lt;br/&gt;
"I was thinking the same thing, sir."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And that is why we have to hurry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He made eye contact with Cotton again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale then continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It'll get complicated if Gersey undoes the seal first. That is why we have to move before he gets here. Am I right?"&lt;br/&gt;
"That is the most important of the reasons we need to hurry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton could not stop frowning as she said that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Damn it, why the hell isn't this unlocking?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton seemed frustrated as she messed with the lock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Move."&lt;br/&gt;
"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale put his hand on her shoulder and pulled her back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's hand moved away from the lock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell are you doing when every second counts-?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Eruhaben-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton could see Eruhaben moving forward at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Step back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton was moved back with Cale and Bud each grabbing one of her hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could see a gold powder covering the wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was there for only a moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But her eyes soon opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Holy shit!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The entire wall was breaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pat. Pat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale patted her shoulder as he whispered to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think it's time to blast our way forward since they already know we're here?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…Crazy bastard."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'You destroyed the wall because of that? What if the cave starts to crumble?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton had a lot of things she wanted to say, but just quietly stepped forward again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale followed behind her and he noticed numerous machines and magic circles that filled this large area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to speak after seeing Cale's gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The White Star had to go through many purifications with Gersey here."&lt;br/&gt;
"Purification?"&lt;br/&gt;
"His human body needed to be purified in order for it to become a body that was suitable for a member of the Demonic race."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale pointed to the northern part of the large hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a small door there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is that it?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, that is the third location."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale nodded his head and looked toward Eruhaben and Bud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's destroy them as we go."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blue aura started to shoot out from the tip of Bud's sword.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His blade was pointed toward the devices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They're here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben looked toward the stairs at the first location that was visible through the destroyed wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could see the things that made loud noises as they entered the underground area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could not see them clearly as they were too far away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he could vaguely make them out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They're so big."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud could see five large robed priests entering the underground facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mm, I can't smell them because they're so far away. But there doesn't seem to be a mage and they don't seem that hard-"&lt;br/&gt;
"Shut up!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton shouted and Bud's eyes turned wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud was not shocked because of what Cotton just said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Son of a-!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaang- Baaaaang! Baaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard multiple explosions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud's pupils started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"T, the glass containers-!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four of the large priests destroyed a large glass container.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They then welcomed the dead mana flowing out with their whole bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group heard Cotton's voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All of them are corpses except for one! They are dead corpses with dead mana bombs inside them!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton looked disgusted as she had not expected Gersey to tell them to destroy the glass containers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four priests became even larger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They looked like bombs that had become even bigger after absorbing more dead mana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. Boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four priests started to walk toward them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…There's no life in their eyes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben could tell that they really were corpses based on their lifeless faces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's right! They have no free will! They just obey everything Gersey tells them to do!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton pulled at Cale's clothes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Follow me! The second facility isn't the problem! We need to get to the third location right now!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale followed her as he asked a question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why are you so scared of Gersey's subordinates? Aren't you fine even if the dead mana bomb goes off?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton flinched for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She hesitated before she continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I cannot absorb dead mana. I'm different."&lt;br/&gt;
"Aren't you an illusionist?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…This is a secret that nobody knows."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale had a lot of things he wanted to ask after seeing her hesitate. However, he pushed those questions aside for now after hearing Bud's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Holy crap! Why the hell are those things so fast?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom-! Boom-!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large things that looked like balloons covered in dead mana were rushing toward them extremely quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shit! Those corpses!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shaaaaaaaaaaa-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's body shot forward at an explosive speed at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ahhh! Hey!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Be quiet!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A whirlwind was surrounding the two of them. Cale had grabbed Cotton's collar and thrown her into the wind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them had almost instantly arrived at the door heading into the third location.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They heard someone shouting from behind them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Block them!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey was pointing at Cale with his fan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes were extremely red.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chhhh!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grey aura started to gather above his head as he opened his fan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud, who had seen that power in the northern mountain, channeled more of his aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His aura that was now shooting up over 3 meters long was pointed at the approaching subordinates and Gersey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Bud, destroy the machines and the magic circles."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben stepped forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then stomped with his foot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold powder scattered in front of Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Block them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A half-transparent gold wall instantly appeared and blocked the cave path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spot where the wall dividing the first and second locations had been was now filled by Eruhaben's gold wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben started to speak to the others behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will hold on for as long as possible, so hurry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes looked toward the grey aura gathering above Gersey as he said that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That is not from this world.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was highly likely that this was a power from the Demon World as Saint Jack explained to Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…I'll hold on for as long as I can.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could a Dragon win against a power from the Demon World?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Especially when that Dragon could not use his full power because he was close to the end of his lifespan?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben pushed aside these questions he had about himself. He could not show any weakness right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hurry up and open it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale put Cotton in front of the small door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was just a black door with nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton didn't even respond to Cale as she put her ring up against the black door's lock right away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale suddenly thought of something and asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…You know how to open this door even though you can't go inside?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I don't know."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's eyes immediately looked concerned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was feeling Bud and Eruhaben's movements behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaang! Baaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shit! Why are there so many damn machines?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud was destroying every machine he came across while Eruhaben was making his golden wall even sturdier while sweating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Eruhaben-nim!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could not let Eruhaben push himself too much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Should I not have brought him?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason Cale brought Bud and Eruhaben with him was because he thought that Bud could use his sense of smell to figure out the identities of the mysterious things from the Demon World while Eruhaben's wisdom would be extremely helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But she didn't know how to open this lock?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Cale quickly started to frown…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm going to rip this door."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Cotton's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Rip?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How do you rip a door?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to look confused before he saw Cotton take something out of her pocket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a small dagger marked with odd markings and covered in bandages so that the blade could not be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom! Boom! Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spatial pocket bag inside Cale's inner pocket started to rumble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What's going on?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to speak as Cale started to think about each item that was in his pocket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can't open this door because the power of the Demon World is infused in it. However, I can rip it with this item."&lt;br/&gt;
"…What is that item?"&lt;br/&gt;
"A divine item."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale took a deep breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton removed the bandages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dagger appeared and she walked toward the door with the dagger in her hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her voice reached Cale's ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The God of War."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The watering can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale immediately thought about that item.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the God of War's divine item that he found in the storage room by the field in Clopeh Sekka's residence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Why do you have that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton had that god's other divine item?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton just smiled at Cale's question before starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those who serve the God of War always hide themselves in the midst of wherever there is a war."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She then swung the dagger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riiiiiiiiiiiip!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could see the firm door starting to rip as if it was made of paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mm!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale subconsciously stepped back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ripped door slowly spread apart as a cold aura flowed out through the gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gasp!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale body curled forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey! Are you okay?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shocked Cotton tried to support him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swipe!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Cale pushed her hand away and walked over to the widening gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. Boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale could feel his heart beating wildly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cold and ominous air that he had felt ever since walking into the area by the sculpture in the Temple of the Demonic God…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That air had become even worse once he got underground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cale pushed this ominous feeling aside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He just had to take on each danger as they arrived.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the moment he felt the thing flowing out through the gap in the door…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale, no, Kim Rok Soo immediately realized what that ominous feeling had been.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smell, touch, and sight. This was an 'emotion' from the past that even his 'Record' that recorded everything could not remember.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the emotion of fear and helplessness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked inside the black door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a large area with stones giving off light in the ceiling looking like stars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a tall and wide octagonal platform in there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were eight eerie octagonal altars on top of the platform. Those altars were large enough that three humans would need to hold hands in order to fully surround it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there was a black sculpture on top of each of these altars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of them looked different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They weren't humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They weren't animals either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale moved closer to the black door to see what they were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom. Boom. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His heart was beating fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale, no, Kim Rok Soo's hand that was on the gap of the black door subconsciously tensed up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the past, Kim Rok Soo had used his ability to anticipate the arrival of the second strongest monster to invade earth one hour prior to its arrival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Kim Rok Soo had said the following after he was the only survivor after team leader Lee Soo Hyuk and Choi Jung Soo had died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Reporting in about the current situation. I will now start explaining about the battle patterns of this unranked monster.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's pupils started to shake as he looked at one of the black sculptures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Why?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why was the monster he had seen in Korea over here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How could this be?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The monster that had killed all of his teammates was visible as a statue in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-551"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-553"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-552</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 551: You should have watched your back (5)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-551</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tang! Tang! Tang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chains fell to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ranger Brigade members started to stretch their bodies that felt light after finally having their chains come off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peek peek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They continued to peek somewhere as they did that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were peeking at Deputy Chief Priest Cotton.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flip, flip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was quickly flipping through the document in her hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her chubby hands that were holding the document were shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tap!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She finished reading and handed the document to Solena as she turned toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She then started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Such crazy shit……!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Can a Deputy Chief Priest talk like that?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale gently smiled. However, Cotton's gaze was fierce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…He got it good.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She wanted to grab Duke Fredo by the collar and shake him right now because of this sudden change in plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it had already happened. She had no choice but to go along with this new plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Most importantly, it's not a bad plan.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She looked away from Cale Henituse who had a sly expression on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale chuckled in response and turned toward Bud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go."&lt;br/&gt;
"Okay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud walked toward Cale, Rosalyn, and Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Leader?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud smiled at the Ranger Brigade members who were looking at him in confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sniff sniff. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sniffed with his nose like a dog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They need my power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rosalyn walked past Bud and stood next to Glenn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud pointed at Rosalyn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She'll be taking my place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rosalyn smiled and shook Glenn's hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She looked toward the Ranger Brigade members and Cale as she started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will finish all preparations so that we can move as soon as we get your signal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale slightly bowed toward her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll leave it to you."&lt;br/&gt;
"Thank you. See you later."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rosalyn waved her hand while Cotton's baggy priestess robe fluttered as she headed toward the entrance of the underground hideout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Follow me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She handed priest robes to the people who followed her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These are my trusted subordinates' priest robes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were small markings on the shoulder of those robes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She handed them masks and hats as well as she continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It should be easy changing your hair colors with magic, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was talking to Cale but her gaze was focused on Eruhaben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben lightly snapped his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snap!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale, Bud, and Eruhaben's appearances changed with that small snap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They all now had the common brown hair. Of course, the shades of the hairs were all different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale brushed his light brown hair back and put the priest robe over his clothes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screeeech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deputy Chief Priest opened the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are heading to the Temple of the Demonic God. Follow me closely."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Deputy Chief Priest's true trusted subordinates were already waiting outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale, Bud, and Eruhaben headed to the center of those trusted subordinates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton took the lead and the trusted subordinates followed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale, who was standing at the center of the formation, looked toward the center of Section 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see the oddly-shaped white marble temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the Temple of the Demonic God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I, I cannot do that!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock shook his head with a pale expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the person standing in front of him slightly tilted his head to the side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are you in a position to say that you can't do something right now?"&lt;br/&gt;
"What kind of-"&lt;br/&gt;
"You're dead if you can't do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lips underneath the black half-mask smiled as beautifully as a painting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This crazy-!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock glared at Informant Bob who was smiling at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he soon groaned as the rope binding him tightened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then heard a firm voice behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Can't we just kill him?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock's face turned pale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He wasn't afraid of the Dark Elf half-blood in front of him. This bastard was unique because he could use magic, but that wasn't a big obstacle for Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he could not say the same for the woman behind his back right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just want to get rid of anything related to the White Star."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pressure she then gave off was even stronger than Dragon Fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock was sweating bullets because of this pressure that was focused solely on him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hoo hoo. Count Mock, you look terrible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock started to frown at Duke Fredo who was smiling at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…You damn traitor-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sharp sword appeared in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You talk too much. Just hurry up and answer whether it is possible or not."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han's sword was pointed at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Motherf*cker!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock truly felt upset at this situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How did I, the great Mock, end up like this?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His insides felt like they were flipping over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody cared and the weakest but most heinous bastard pushed a document toward Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Here, that's your script."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu gently continued to speak to Count Mock who was glaring at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just report to the White Star following the script when I give you the signal later."&lt;br/&gt;
"…How can I lie to my liege that I conquered this Black Castle?"&lt;br/&gt;
"What's wrong? It's not that hard."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock was at a loss for words at Informant Bob's response. Alberu didn't care as he got up and patted Count Mock's shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're dead if he finds out because you're so stiff like earlier. Let's practice a lot so that you look natural. You have to do it naturally. Got it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's shoulders slumped down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu left him in the room and walked out with Duke Fredo and Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was because Lord Sheritt said that she would watch over Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three of them walked into the next room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raon, who was sitting in front of a video communication device, fluttered his wings as soon as they came in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The human hasn't contacted us yet!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the strategy room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu pointed to a seat in the strategy room next to Duke Fredo, who still thought that he was actually Bob.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why don't we sit down and wait?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu, Choi Han, and Fredo all sat down inside the strategy room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They just had to wait for Cale to contact them now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Deputy Chief Priest-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A priest slightly bowed toward Cotton with a solemn expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please work hard a little longer as it is a tiring but happy day."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She gently cheered on the priest whose arms were full of gifts for the citizens and entered the Temple of the Demonic God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her trusted subordinates were walking right behind her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, her trusted subordinates were holding gifts and other items as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah! Deputy Chief Priest-nim! Did everything go smoothly with what you needed to do?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Of course. I brought back everything we needed."&lt;br/&gt;
"Oh! I'm relieved!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every priest they passed talked to her or respectfully greeted her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton heard someone right behind her start to whisper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Amazing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton quietly whispered with a smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shut the hell up."&lt;br/&gt;
"You're quite an amazing talker, Deputy Chief Priest."&lt;br/&gt;
"This much is good for the enemy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton lightly responded to Cale who was following behind her while disguised as a priest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was stealthily looking around rather than looking at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The atmosphere here is not as evil as I had expected it would be.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Eruhaben's voice in his mind. Cale nodded his head without making it look too visible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Temple of a Demonic God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This place that the Chief Priest was said to take special care to maintain was pretty empty even though it was festival time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Most of them are in the garden outside the building.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Temple of the Demonic God had set up close to a hundred long tables in the garden to treat the visiting citizens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sniff sniff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Bud sniffing behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton headed deeper into the Temple as Bud's sniffing became more frequent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's stop here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton stopped walking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those who are carrying things, deliver the goods to their respective locations. The rest of you come with me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She gave orders to her trusted subordinates and over half of them started to move elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton only took Cale's group and a few of her trusted subordinates as she walked forward again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It must be over there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale heard Eruhaben's voice and observed the large door in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A black door that did not fit this white building was blocking their way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Deputy Chief Priest-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple priests stationed outside the door holding swords and spears recognized her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are working hard even during a day like today."&lt;br/&gt;
"Not at all. Deputy Chief Priest-nim, did you come to pray?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton nodded to the priests who were serving as the guards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a joyous day, so I wanted to show my respects before it became busier."&lt;br/&gt;
"I understand."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The priests opened the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The door seemed to be so heavy that multiple people had to push it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screeeech-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The door slowly opened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Ho-'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale barely managed to hold back his gasp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What is that?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the large empty area…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a seriously heinous looking human sculpture on the high platform at the center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton walked into the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale matched the trusted subordinates' movements as he walked in as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…It's cold in here.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This area was cold unlike the outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The air in here was colder than in the other parts of the temple. That temperature and the heinous human sculpture together gave him the chills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black door closed again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned toward the closed door. He heard Cotton's voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nobody bothers my prayer time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He turned toward Cotton. Her trusted subordinates quickly walked over to the black door and stationed themselves there as she motioned with her hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, they took weapons out of their pockets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Since this place was created, the rule is that nobody opens the door while Gersey, the White Star, or I am praying in here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That was the only way for the White Star to progress with becoming a member of the Demonic race without any disturbances. And that is going to be advantageous for us right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She finished speaking and started to head toward the sculpture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are going to go underground using the hidden passage in this sculpture. Just wait a little bit."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked at the sculpture as he waited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud walked up next to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who is that?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I'm not sure either."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben was the one who answered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was looking at the sculpture as if he found it odd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This human's face looks extremely heinous and as if he has fallen into despair. But I cannot tell who it is."&lt;br/&gt;
"Me neither. But it must be someone related to the White Star if he would create this sculpture."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud agreed with Eruhaben's assessment before turning toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you know who that is?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was just asking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sort of."&lt;br/&gt;
"…What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud, Eruhaben, and Cotton all looked toward him in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You know who that is?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton was the one with the most shocked reaction. She stopped opening the passage and turned toward Cale in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When did you see him?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I have no plans on telling you, so just open the passage."&lt;br/&gt;
"Ha………."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to frown as she resumed moving the device to open the passage. It seemed to require a special power to activate, as the ring on her finger was giving off some kind of power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who is it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale shook his head at Eruhaben's question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The White Star's face without a mask."&lt;br/&gt;
"Ho-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben gasped in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How shocking.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben who had been looking at the sculpture while wondering if a human being could have such a heinous expression had to look at the sculpture in a different light now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What…is making the White Star have such an expression?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He felt an odd sensation as a question filled his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Deputy Chief Priest had mentioned…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How does Cale know about the White Star's bare face?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben had not heard about the information Cale had gathered from Duke Fredo yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He has such a vicious expression. He wouldn't look so heinous if he had a regular expression on his face."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was Bud's assessment of the sculpture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for Cale, he was looking at the sculpture of the White Star's bare face with an odd sensation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'My face really looks despicable with that kind of heinous expression.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing this face on a sculpture made him really think that Kim Rok Soo and the White Star looked quite similar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I need to make sure to destroy this thing.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Rok Soo never had such an expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked up to the sculpture with an iffy expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Did the White Star want people to worship him?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale found it laughable that such a sculpture existed at the center of the Temple of the Demonic God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It made him think that the White Star really was out of his mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked a little closer. He wanted to take a closer look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screeeeeeeech, screeeeech-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale saw the sculpture move up at that moment. He stopped walking and turned toward Cotton.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton pointed to the passage that appeared now that the sculpture had moved up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm going in, so follow me closely."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She walked into the passage without any hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to hurry because you wasted some time with the hostages."&lt;br/&gt;
"Isn't it still plenty of time before one hour is up?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…Did you not look at the information Duke Fredo gave you?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I did."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale responded as he walked down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed like a typical underground passage, however, it was extremely large. It was wide enough for ten adults to walk side by side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Something is weird.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coldness he felt in the area above became even colder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could clearly tell that the temperature here was much lower than outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…This is weird.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some odd reason, it made Cale start to have an ominous feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This unexplainable sense of uncertainty swept over him. It gave him the chills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why do I feel this way?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard Cotton's voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As the information Duke Fredo gave you should have said, the underground facility is divided into three locations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She quickly walked down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gersey and the White Star can go to all three places. I am only allowed in two."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tap. Tap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sound of the four people walking down echoed through the passage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But the most important place is the third location. The place I can't go. We must go in there and destroy it today."&lt;br/&gt;
"What proof do you have that the third location is the most important?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale asked since the reasoning was not mentioned in the information he received last time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why was Cotton emphasizing that the third location was the most important?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They reached the end of the staircase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton started to speak with a serious expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't have time, so I'll explain on our way over. I definitely have proof to back me up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her eyes seemed confident that the proof she found was reliable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is the first location."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the staircase… This place looked like a naturally constructed cave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the things inside were not natural.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is a dead mana storage facility. The White Star absorbs the dead mana here periodically."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The numerous large beautiful glass containers were full of black liquid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These were all someone's life in the past."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud had a bitter expression on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cale calmly counted the number of glass containers as he started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We should move all these black liquids elsewhere."&lt;br/&gt;
"Looks like I need to step in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben walked toward the glass containers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please."&lt;br/&gt;
"It's easy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben said it was easy, but it was actually difficult. There were quite a lot of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shh. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben put his hand on one of the glass containers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeep- beeeeeeeeeeeeeep-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sharp noise echoed around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Shit!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton turned pale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They found us!"&lt;br/&gt;
"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked over to her in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton took an orb out of her pocket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is the signal my trusted subordinates were to send if they were caught! Who is it? Who found us? It's not the White Star!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She looked at Cale and urgently continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gersey! I'm sure Gersey is the one who found us! My trusted subordinate would not have been able to send me a signal if it was the White Star! They'd be dead long before they could do that!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She bit down on her lips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why? Gersey was supposed to come an hour later, so why did he come here earlier? He's kept this rule for many years, so what changed?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her eyes looked chaotic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beeeeeep- Beeeeeeep-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The alarm started to get louder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud who was watching this walked over to Cale in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hey, what do we do?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crack!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cracks were starting to appear on the orb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Damn it!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton threw the orb into the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The orb then exploded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…This orb is connected by the power of those who serve the Demonic race. Only another priest could destroy it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's eyes filled with fear and urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm certain. Gersey has found us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She looked at Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He will chase after us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-550"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-552"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-551</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 550: You should have watched your back (4)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-550</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The white castle that was located at the center of the sinkhole and the only place that received direct sunlight in the Endable Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star who was looking out from the highest point in that castle started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Looks like everyone is enjoying themselves."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then turned and looked toward a video communication device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;My liege!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Elf Count Mock was visible on the screen with a stiff expression on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He seemed to be in a section of the forest as he started to speak in a low but confident voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It looks like we will be able to conquer Cale Henituse's base soon!&lt;br/&gt;"You're working hard."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock was still busy looking around him rather than at the White Star as he continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don't see the Tigers here, as I confirmed in my information.&lt;br/&gt;"I see."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star noticed that Count Mock was not saying anything and just quietly looking at him after hearing his reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star laughed internally seeing the slightly nervous and desperate gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I guess he really wants me to approve of his merits.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star held back a sigh as he started to speak with a serious expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Work hard. I trust you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;T, thank you very much!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock did his best to smile before bowing to the White Star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then I'm hanging up now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;…Yes, sir.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video communication device was immediately turned off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star looked toward the deactivated video communication device and started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"His face was quite stiff."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chief Priest Marquis Gersey who had been in the corner started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He is probably nervous about achieving great merits and moving up to a higher position, my lord."&lt;br/&gt;"I guess that's true. Count Mock is extremely greedy for title and power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star started to shake his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He needs to be more relaxed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then looked toward the Chief Priest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gersey, how about you relax a bit too? You can't have any fun just staying here. Why don't you go out and enjoy the festival?"&lt;br/&gt;"That's okay, sire. I can't really relax and enjoy the festival right now."&lt;br/&gt;"I guess that's true. You and your people are extremely busy right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each demonic temple had to hand out a lot of things to the citizens during the festival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, many of the citizens came to visit the temples and look around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why the priests were busier than usual right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey started to speak after seeing the White Star's gaze that seemed to be asking if it was okay that he was here when it was such a busy time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I left the festival-related tasks with the Deputy Chief Priest so that I can slack off like this."&lt;br/&gt;"Ha! The Deputy Chief Priest will be upset if she hears that."&lt;br/&gt;"Hahaha, do you think so, sire? But I'm just so full of anticipation. I can't focus on anything else right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey smiled brightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am extremely looking forward to the true day of the festival."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star's gaze sunk down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey looked at him and continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The last day."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last day of the festival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That day will be a festival for me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pfft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star chuckled at Gersey's comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Gersey, half the people here will die. Is that entertaining?"&lt;br/&gt;"But that means that you will be that much closer to becoming a transcended being, my liege."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them looked at each other and their smiles became thicker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star started to speak again in a low voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;" 'Those things' are safe, right?"&lt;br/&gt;"Yes, sir. They're fine."&lt;br/&gt;"And their feed?"&lt;br/&gt;"We are feeding them properly. I do need to go feed them again in an hour though."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey continued to speak with an expression that seemed to be saying that he was extremely fidgety from excitement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can't do it, sire. I must go check on the 'feed.' Those terrible things cause such a ruckus when we don't feed them and they are very scary to look at."&lt;br/&gt;"Aren't you usually the type to follow the rules?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star looked at Gersey as if this was odd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey was the type who was always strict about being on time and following the rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would normally move according to the schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not sure. I can't sit still today because I'm so excited. It must be because the moment I've been waiting for is one step closer, my lord."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is called being capricious."&lt;br/&gt;"Is that so, sire?"&lt;br/&gt;"That's right. You are being capricious. Mm, I feel bad for making you take care of the feed. It must be hard."&lt;br/&gt;"It is doable as I am doing it with my trusted subordinates instead of alone. Plus, who else can do it other than me? I have to do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey walked to the door and bowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My liege, please excuse me as I go check on the feed and go underground prior to returning."&lt;br/&gt;"Sure."&lt;br/&gt;"Until later then, my liege."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gersey quietly opened the door and disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Silence filled the area now that the White Star was alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star continued to look out the window once Gersey left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was pretty empty around the palace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he could see the citizens of the kingdom enjoying the festival in all directions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their excited faces did not bring any joy to the White Star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wasn't as if he could feel or taste anything anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A smile appeared on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It'll soon be hell for them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star started to imagine his kingdom that will turn into hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be a glorious step toward the future he desired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that moment, in the Roan Kingdom's Forest of Darkness…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pat. Pat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock turned toward the hand patting his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good job."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Informant Bob was smiling warmly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han who was standing behind Bob started to speak to Alberu who was still Bob.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go in."&lt;br/&gt;"Yes, yes. We have a lot of things to do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu sounded gentle as he started to speak to Mock again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shall we go?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu slowly whispered to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Respond."&lt;br/&gt;"…Yes, sir."&lt;br/&gt;"Ah, I only feel relaxed when people speak respectfully to me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu laughed and picked Count Mock up by grabbing the back of his collar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This evil bastard! Does he not know anything about respecting his elders?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock looked away from Alberu in disgust. It was a small gesture to say that he did not want to speak to this bastard who was drying out the Dark Elf blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, there was nobody here who respected his desires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was looking at an old house he visited once before at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…He was telling the truth. I guess everything Duke Fredo said was true."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He approached the woman who was truly wowed to see him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You are the Deputy Chief Priest?"&lt;br/&gt;"Yes, I'm Deputy Chief Priest Cotton."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton offered her hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm sorry, I don't dare to grab the enemy's hand even if we are working together."&lt;br/&gt;"Is that so?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She smiled at Cale's response and lowered her hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She licked her lips with her tongue as she did that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Fredo. That Vampire really does his job properly.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale Henituse was next to Solena who brought him here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton could also see two people behind him who were covered from head to hip with a robe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was looking at them while trying to figure out who they were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Enough observing. Shouldn't we get to work?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could see Cale's stoic gaze looking down at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'So, this guy is the one who has been giving the White Star the most trouble? Should I try casting an illusion on him?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Cotton had that thought…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think we've shown enough trust on our side by ignoring the illusion cast on this place. What are you suspicious about that you keep observing us like that?"&lt;br/&gt;"……!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He realized that there is an illusion?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cotton was truly shocked at what Cale said next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I wish to rescue the Ranger Brigade members as well."&lt;br/&gt;"…How did you know about that? Did Duke Fredo tell you?"&lt;br/&gt;"Do I need to have heard that from that bastard?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's expression was saying that he didn't need to hear from such a bastard to know that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I saw them with my own eyes instead of hearing it from Fredo. You showed them to me yourself.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He walked past Cotton who was looking at him in shock, crouched down, and tapped on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tang. Tang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It sounded empty inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I knew this spot seemed weird. I can sense people underground over here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton kept her mouth shut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She didn't trust everything Cale was saying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Duke Fredo must have told him about it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that he knew the exact spot must mean that he knew about it prior to coming here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She quietly sighed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can rescue them on the way back from destroying the facility. It's impossible to move so many people even if you rescue them now."&lt;br/&gt;"But I don't want to."&lt;br/&gt;"Huh?"&lt;br/&gt;"I'm going to save them now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people standing behind Solena removed their hoods as Cotton started to frown at Cale's response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton's eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Rosalyn! The ancient Dragon!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person and Dragon whom even she knew about as they were individuals of interest revealed themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton immediately read Cale's thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Are you going to teleport them away?"&lt;br/&gt;"Yes."&lt;br/&gt;"…I understand. We will rescue the Ranger Brigade members as you wish, however!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton continued to speak with a stiff expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to get in and destroy it within the hour. Gersey is going to head to the underground facility in one hour."&lt;br/&gt;"I got it. It won't take long."&lt;br/&gt;"……Okay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She opened the door leading into the underground hideout after seeing Cale's extremely relaxed demeanor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Ranger Brigade members are down here."&lt;br/&gt;"Thanks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton had an odd expression after hearing Cale thank her, but Cale did not notice as he followed behind Cotton down into the underground area. Solena was behind him while Rosalyn and Eruhaben came behind her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bang, baaaaang! Bang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike last time, the underground area was loud as soon as he walked down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You evil bastards! Let us go!"&lt;br/&gt;"Damn it! These chains won't come off!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ranger Brigade members who saw Cotton through the bars were shouting in anger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the f*ck are you planning to do?!"&lt;br/&gt;"How long are you going to keep us here?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did not hesitate to bare their fangs at Cotton, unlike last time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was because it was weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had not responded and continued to feed them properly and let them rest no matter how they reacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that just made them feel even more ominous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'She won't harm us for most actions.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ranger Brigade members who came to that decision were raising their voices because of the fear this weird situation brought them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the members in the cage closest to the hallway shouted toward Cotton who got closer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Take these off right now! We will never submit no matter what you do-uh?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, his voice trailed off in the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Huh?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He saw a familiar face behind Cotton.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, it wasn't familiar to be accurate. However, he had heard about this person so much from Bud that his ears almost bled and he had seen a picture of this person's face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked somewhat disrespectful and had bright red hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Hero Cale Henituse-?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brigade member could see the red-haired man starting to frown after hearing his comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton responded on his behalf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, that hero came here for you guys."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Silence filled the hallway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the banging on the bars and the shouting had disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…A hero?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale wanted to sigh at how the brigade member addressed him, but he held himself back. Maybe that was the reason, but his lips were tense and his face looked stiff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked around the hallway with that stiff face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Ah."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ranger Brigade members gasped in admiration as he looked at each of them with a firm gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'In order to save us-'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He came to the center of the enemy territory to save them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hearts of the Ranger Brigade members who had lived peacefully but full of uncertainty in these small cages started to beat wildly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Deputy Chief Priest, open all of the doors. Remove their chains as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a firm but calm voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, that made the Ranger Brigade members' hearts beat even wilder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cale was not done talking just yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eruhaben-nim, Miss Rosalyn."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said two names the Ranger Brigade members were familiar with and they could see a magic circle that filled the hallway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The air underground started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's connected."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The magic circle Rosalyn cast with Eruhaben supporting her started to glow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paaaaat-!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bright light filled the hallway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;br/&gt;"Mm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ranger Brigade members subconsciously closed their eyes after seeing the bright light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, they had to quickly open their eyes again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell? Why did these punks get so fat? Why do they look so healthy?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They heard a voice they've longed to hear so much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the light voice they always heard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, that voice was slightly shaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why do you look so shocked?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mercenary King Bud and Glenn had appeared together on the teleportation magic circle and were looking at them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"L, leader!"&lt;br/&gt;"Leader-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ranger Brigade members' eyes started to tear up. It was the same for Bud who was looking at them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Damn it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud bit down on his lips realizing that he was tearing up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'They're all healthy.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The kidnapped Ranger Brigade members looked healthy and did not seem injured at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A deep sense of relief filled Bud's body and the ominous feeling that had been filling his mind started to disappear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clap!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton clapped once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screech- screech-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bars imprisoning the Ranger Brigade members started to open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton took a key out of her pocket and handed it to Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can release the chains with this key."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale handed the key to Bud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud grabbed Cale's hand that was holding the key with both hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank you. I really mean it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He truly meant it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shut up with such useless comments."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale grumbled as he slowly removed his hand from Bud's grasp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bud chuckled at Cale who was avoiding his gaze and lightly responded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Good. Then let's quickly get the work started."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Work?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solena walked over to the confused Cotton and handed her a document.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's been a change of plans."&lt;br/&gt;"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton heard Bud's voice as she responded to Solena in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll bring Miss Tasha and everybody who is waiting to this spot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What? The people who are waiting? Who else was coming here?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cotton looked toward Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She could see that Cale was smiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second step of Operation Hunt was infiltration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-549"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-551"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-550</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 03:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 549: You should have watched your back (3)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-549</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Count Mock could not believe what he was seeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What the hell is going on?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His mind blanked out for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han, who was said to not be at the Black Castle, had shown up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That alone was shocking, but this Bob bastard who was said to be young master Naru's trusted subordinate was choking him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could only come up with one conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh, were we b…betrayed?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were the Vampire bastards and Cale Henituse working together?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the only plausible explanation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock got chills throughout his body after he barely managed to get that question out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'The mana orb!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the Vampire bastards truly had betrayed them…!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If they really were working together with Cale Henituse…!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then it was obvious where that mana orb would go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mana orb then slowly headed toward the Black Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then the being that had been covered by the large mana orb was revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…The Black Dragon!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale Henituse's black Dragon that had been hiding behind the mana orb was revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Ah."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's head started to hurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Choi Han and the black Dragon were both here…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then Cale Henituse was bound to be here as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"H, how-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could not speak properly as he was being choked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the person choking him finished his sentence for him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;" 'How was this possible?' "&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock who had been looking at Choi Han slowly looked toward Bob who was choking him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's eyes were asking Bob for an answer. He wanted him to quickly tell him what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu slowly responded to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What good will knowing how it happened do for you, you bastard?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock suddenly felt like Bob was looking down at him from above instead of looking up from below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the unique type of pressure he had felt when in the White Star's presence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why was he feeling that type of pressure from a damn informant?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's body shot up into the air at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mmph!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could finally breathe properly for the first time in a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he was still groaning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swooooooosh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A chain made of wind appeared and bound him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baaaaaang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, there was an explosion where Count Mock and informant Bob had been standing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Shit!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han, who saw the explosion, started to run toward Alberu contrary to their original plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people who launched the attack angrily started to shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Change the target!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the Dark Elves stood up and pointed toward Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few of the Dark Elves had stealthily planned a surprise attack the moment Mock ended up in Bob's hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their attack that was aimed at Alberu was what caused the explosion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rustle-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black arrows that suddenly appeared were pointed at Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Rescue the Count-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of them shot up into the air as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wind was swirling at the tips of their feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Count-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the Dark Elves in the air flew toward Count Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll release you right away, sir!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock whose neck was now free started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's not over yet!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Excuse me?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elves who had jumped into the air had to hear the shouts of their Elementals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oooooong- oooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Elementals that had created the wind at the tips of the Dark Elves feet were warning them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were telling them to look down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elves looked down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the dust from the explosion disappeared…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The masked Dark Elf was pointing a large spear toward them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Magic!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Dark Elves shouted in shock after looking at the large magic spear…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Go."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That spear started to move toward the Dark Elves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dodge!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elves quickly moved away from Count Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock could feel the current fluctuating behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crackle. Crackle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spear of light stopped right behind Count Mock's back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Count Mock's body will be filled with electricity if you try to get close again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elves did not dare to approach the chained Mock after hearing Alberu's threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Also, make your Elementals stop moving. Did you really think that I wouldn't be able to tell that they are moving?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elves had no way of knowing whether Alberu was lying or telling the truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the chances of this half-blood's statement being true were high as he still had some Dark Elf blood, so the Dark Elves could not send the Elementals around the forest as Count Mock had ordered earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can't ever put my guard down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu finally waved his hand and pushed away the dust around him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elf who had given the command to attack was grinding his teeth as he glared at Alberu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How dare you attack one of your own race even though Dark Elven blood flows through your body! You're attacking those on the same side!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Ho, my goodness."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu shook his head from side to side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's no point to even answer."&lt;br/&gt;
"What?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu ignored the Dark Elf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Attack my fellow race?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How many times had the White Star and Cale's respective Dark Elves clashed already?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why had Count Mock and these Dark Elves not said anything and continue to serve the White Star through it all?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It's not because of who is a Dark Elf and who is not, it's a matter of the difference in what each group wants.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu did not say anything else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, Choi Han pulled out his sword and stood next to Alberu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elf started to frown in response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ha! You're betraying your race because of the human blood inside you!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu started to frown under his mask for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tsk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu clicked his tongue and observed the Dark Elves in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could feel their hostility. Alberu started to move toward his goal in front of such hostile enemies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your liege will die if you make any movements."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elf who was shouting toward Alberu shut up after hearing those emotionless words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He sounded like someone who would do as he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's make a deal!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock shouted at the top of his lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hooo?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu looked up at Mock as if this reaction was unexpected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock ignored Alberu's gaze and twisted his body to look at Choi Han as he continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's nobody who would destroy the area in front of their house. That Dragon won't use the mana orb. He won't want to burn this area down to the ground."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to frown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elf old man Mock's eyes sparkled after seeing this reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I knew I was right.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That large mana orb and the black Dragon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was no way that that thing would really attack this spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There would be too much aftershock for the Black Castle and the nearby area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That means that I have no reason to fear that mana orb.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's mind started to clear up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'There's still a chance.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vampires' betrayal was like a sharp dagger attacking him, but it was not an extremely dangerous attack to the point that he would die yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Squad 1 and 2 are still there.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He still had allies to the North and East.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'll need to look for an opportunity while talking about making a deal.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He just needed to flip this situation over when he saw an opening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock immediately started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Choi Han, deliver this message to Cale Henituse. Tell him that I want to make a deal. I'm sure you guys don't want to fight us in front of your territory as well, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He continued to speak to Choi Han who was quietly looking at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No matter how strong you guys are… There are bound to be injured people if we fight. And we will go until the very end if we start to fight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Then this area in front of the Black Castle will become a mess.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the meaning behind Mock's words as he looked at Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han responded to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Keep talking."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock resumed speaking at this gesture that showed that Choi Han was willing to at least listen to what he had to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Vampires."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That word caused some rustling in the forest to the west.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock ignored that and continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will return if you let us take care of the Vampires."&lt;br/&gt;
"…The Vampires have agreed to cooperate with us."&lt;br/&gt;
"They betrayed us to work with you. Why are you trying to fight us until the end while tightly clutching onto them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Count Mock! What nonsense are you spewing now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The western forest…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solena stepped forward from the forest where Squad 3 was stationed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of Mock's lips started to twist. Solena was the person who was serving Naru right now and one of Duke Fredo's trusted subordinates. Mock resumed speaking after she made her appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you mean by nonsense?! We are negotiating a peaceful resolution to end this issue!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked toward Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Choi Han. Think about it. Isn't it beneficial for you guys if we make a deal like that?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I guess so. There would be no need to fight if we agreed."&lt;br/&gt;
"Exactly! Furthermore, the Dark Elves and everybody on our side will all cooperate with you guys from here on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's heart was beating wildly as he said that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This could be extremely beneficial the more I think about it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had a lot to gain between Cale Henituse and the White Star if he used this situation properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he would get past this current predicament, pretend to cooperate with Cale Henituse, and then tell the White Star everything!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'And if I report Duke Fredo's betrayal as well…! If I take that open Duke position for myself……!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could there be a more beautiful conclusion?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock ordered his subordinates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lower your bows now! Stop attacking!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrows pointed at Choi Han instantly disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elves quietly stood there while peeking toward Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Choi Han, I am being serious."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock looked toward Choi Han with a serious and honest expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He truly wanted to make a deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han was quiet for a moment. He then raised his head and looked at the black Dragon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black Dragon moved away from the mana orb, came down, and put his mouth by Choi Han's ear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then started to speak using magic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choi Han! The human says don't act, just repeat the words the human tells you to say!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raon delivered Cale's message and Choi Han finally started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fine. We will gather all of the representatives."&lt;br/&gt;
"Choi Han!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solena shouted but Choi Han did not show any reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good job, Choi Han! The human said not to do anything!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raon praised him and Alberu started to frown as he moved away from Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's nobody you can trust."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu raised his wariness toward Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to speak again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cale-nim said that he wishes to chat with the Vampire representative as well. He said all representatives should meet to discuss a deal."&lt;br/&gt;
"Damn it!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solena started to frown and headed back toward the western forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Kehehe, I guess she's going to get Naru.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock started to sneer as he responded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will call the leaders of Squads 1 and 2 as well!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Fine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He watched Choi Han head toward the gate to the Black Castle and then turned his gaze over to informant Bob.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How about you let me go?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Informant Bob moved his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spear of light disappeared and Mock landed on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will not release the chains."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he did not release the chains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You arrogant-!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock started to frown but internally, he was at least happy to be back on the ground. He then raised his voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Squad 1 and 2 leaders, come on out! We are making a deal!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rustle, rustle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was movement in the eastern and northern parts of the forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the sign that Squads 1 and 2 which were hiding and waiting were starting to move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 1's leader Andrei and Squad 2's leader should come out soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'One is a sword master while the other is a talented assassin.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's eyes had a wicked glare to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'If the negotiation goes bad, then I'll use the two of them to capture Cale Henituse.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would take Cale Henituse hostage while everybody had their guards down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clear plan started to form in Mock's mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screeeech-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Black Castle's gate started to open wider than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rustle, rustle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He continued to hear footsteps coming through the forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock could feel his plan slowly starting to become completed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I will turn this around.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would definitely flip this situation around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock confirmed these thoughts as he relaxed his tense shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess I have to come out since they asked for all representatives."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Huh?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock who was starting to relax had to question his ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Step. Step.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock looked to the west after hearing footsteps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…How-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see the person walking out of the western forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the person who represented Squad 3 and the Vampires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This person should have been Naru Von Ejellan, but…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why, why is Duke Fredo-?"&lt;br/&gt;
"What's wrong? Is there a reason I can't come out?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredo was walking forward while wearing armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi Han started to walk back out of the castle as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock heard some suppressed groans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock did not dare to look toward Choi Han. He felt chills on his back. He felt as if there were goosebumps all over his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…C, Count-nim!"&lt;br/&gt;
"My apologies, sir! Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he had to turn after hearing someone calling out to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Squad 1 and 2 leaders are here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, what he saw were the two squad leaders who were bound and carried out by Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their titles of sword master and assassin seemed laughable right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If they were here, then what were the noises he heard coming from the east and north?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock looked toward the north and east.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hohoho. I guess I will come out as the representative since I am a resident here as well."&lt;br/&gt;
"Do you think I'm a representative too?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gashan walked out of the northern part while laughing out loud. As for the east side… Lock walked out while scratching his head with an embarrassed expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah……"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock felt as if all of blood was draining from his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the most important representative had not come out yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The last representative is coming out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock started to think about Cale Henituse after Choi Han said that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he heard an unfamiliar voice instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You dare to set your eyes on our house?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock turned after hearing a woman's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked toward the Black Castle… And saw a white-haired woman flying up above it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How laughable that you tried to destroy my home."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lord Sheritt landed on the highest spot on the Black Castle and opened her arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A deal? I do not negotiate with the enemies. I only destroy those who try to attack me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oooooo- oooooo-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of white shields started to appear in the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's face turned pale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"W, where is C, Cale Henituse?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He subconsciously turned toward Choi Han.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But someone else answered his question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredo started to laugh as he recalled what happened a few moments ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'm heading out then.'&lt;br/&gt;
'Goodbye, my son.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredo continued to speak while looking at the confused Count Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He went to our house."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The preparations are completed, young master-nim."&lt;br/&gt;
"Solena, isn't it confusing to call me that when I don't look like Naru anymore?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I guess I just got used to calling you young master-nim, Cale-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale nodded at Solena and looked out the window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How energetic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see the vibrant Endable Kingdom's capital excited for the festival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eruhaben, shall we go?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes."&lt;br/&gt;
"Miss Rosalyn, you too."&lt;br/&gt;
"Of course."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eruhaben and Rosalyn covered their faces with their hoods and walked up next to Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sparkle sparkle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video communication device in Cale's hand started to glow and then he heard someone's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All preparations are completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale motioned to Rosalyn with his eyes and Rosalyn walked up to Cale in order to turn the video communication device off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale observed the screen as she did that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This should be enough.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He saw Bud, numerous mercenaries, and his friends who were at the Molden Kingdom through the screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"See you guys soon."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The call ended after Cale said that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solena opened Fredo's bedroom door once Cale said that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Operation Hunt's second step had started.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-548"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-550"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-549</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 548: You should have watched your back (2)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-548</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Andrei could not believe what he was seeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Y, you were supposed to be in a coma-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could not even finish his sentence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why is Duke Fredo here?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had heard from young master Naru that Duke Fredo's condition was so serious that nobody other than the healers could approach him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But how was he seeing a completely fine Duke Fredo in front of him right now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You were in a coma!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's tone did not show any respect for the Duke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was how shocked he was right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was true for all of Squad 1. None of them could speak properly due to their shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredo started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mm, that's right. I was in a coma and woke up not too long ago."&lt;br/&gt;
"What total nonsense!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'How was he here if he woke up not too long ago?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei looked toward Fredo in disbelief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then made eye contact with Fredo. Fredo's gaze made him subconsciously shut up while Fredo started to speak in a calm voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, it makes no sense. But you have to believe it because I am telling you that that is the case."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Duke's face turned cold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that his lazy and bored expression was gone, all that was left was an emotionless and cold face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Andrei, it would be best if you accept the situation without thinking nor saying anything."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gulp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei subconsciously gulped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He wanted to step away, but that was not easy because he was bound.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He quickly looked at Duke Fredo, who was walking toward him, as well as his surroundings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He finally started to understand what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was a sword master.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was not a level that could be reached through training alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had been involved in numerous battles, large and small alike, and could come up with a conclusion in his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Duke, did you decide to cooperate with Cale Henituse?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer was obvious as soon as the Tigers had appeared in front of Andrei.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story about how the Tiger tribe lived close to the Forest of Darkness and served Cale was a famous story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hehe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei started to laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No wonder. I knew that there was no way that this kind of plan would come from that old Count Mock's head."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He recalled when he decided to follow Count Mock for this plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I plan on using Naru Von Ejellan. That is why there are no benefits to stick on Duke Fredo's side for this operation.'&lt;br/&gt;
'What do you mean by that, sir?'&lt;br/&gt;
'Naru Von Ejellan is my informant. He's perfect to use.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He gazed past Naru and focused on Duke Fredo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You used your son to plot all of this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's shoulders started to move up and down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shock and disbelief were making him laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Kahaha, hahaha-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, his laughter could not continue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His neck was instantly clenched by a Vampire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sorry, things might get complicated if you let out any loud noises."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see Solena who was smiling while clenching his neck. Duke Fredo's trusted subordinate. She was clenching Andrei's life away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Solena, let him go."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, Duke-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solena instantly let go of her hand that was clenching Andrei's' neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom-! Boom-!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's body that was bound by the rope tilted to the side and fell to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei who fell sideways could see a pair of shoes walking past his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He raised his head to see young master Naru looking down at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Naru then looked away from him and walked forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Y, you bastards-!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei subconsciously started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actually, he was shouting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you plan to do with us?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked around as he shouted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale Henituse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Duke Fredo cooperated with him, then he should be somewhere nearby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see a pair of shoes stopping in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Please be quiet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He raised his head. Young master Naru was looking down at him with a nonchalant gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cale he was looking for was right in front of him, but he did not recognize Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He just saw a new side to a boy he thought was just an innocent kid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boy said something else in a stoic voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You'll be the first to die if you're loud."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boy started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can't talk as you please in someone else's yard."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then looked away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Father, shall we go?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredo put the helmet back on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sure. Is Squad 2 next?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes it is, Duke-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vampires walked past Squad 1's members and headed toward Squad 2 at Solena's response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What is going to happen to us?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's pupils started to shake as he watched them walk away without any hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He soon got his answer. That was why his shoulders started to shake again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even a sword master should find it hard to break through these ropes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large shadow appeared above him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei could see the old Tiger Shaman who was looking down and smiling at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, that smile instantly disappeared and Tiger shaman Gashan started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Move all of them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tigers approached Squad 1's members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…How could this be?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei watched them with despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He never expected it to end like this without even being able to do anything!&lt;br/&gt;
Not only that, but he was also captured by the enemies and backstabbed by his allies!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Why the hell is this so hard to untie?!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could not undo the ropes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He realized the secrets behind the rope after thinking about the whole situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…It's a Dragon.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This rope must have been made by the Dragon that is always around Cale Henituse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He lifted his head up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The white gold haired Elf who should have been on the tree had disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Alright then, shall we go too, Mr. Squad Leader?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His body was easily lifted by a Tiger warrior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caw, caw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The crows were in the sky looking down at the entire Forest of Darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'm screwed.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's then lowered his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had to worry about his life now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock started to speak while hiding his body within the shadows of the forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Is it here?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person standing next to him responded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, sir. This is it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock nodded his head at Alberu Crossman's response and looked north.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He started to frown after reaching the southern side of the Black Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…I hate to say this about the enemy, but it is amazing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His voice was full of admiration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Seriously, it is amazing.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was true for Alberu as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He touched the mask that covered his nose to his forehead as he observed the Black Castle in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He said that it was the last Dragon Lord's castle, right?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock quietly mumbled as Alberu was recalling the information he had heard from Cale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess the Roan Kingdom really is nothing without Cale Henituse! They built this kind of castle for a twenty years old or so little kid who hasn't even received a noble title!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock's face started to twist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anybody would be able to tell that he was jealous of Cale Henituse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmph! This castle looks even more stylish than Alberu Crossman's palace. The crown prince leaves him alone even while knowing about this? The kingdom seems to be a total mess."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu's gaze turned cold as he looked at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…This bastard.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock didn't realize Alberu's gaze as he sneered and glared at the Black Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmph! It doesn't matter since Cale Henituse will lose this castle today without being able to do anything. Kehehe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wicked laughter started to flow out of his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a shame to destroy it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Should I take it for myself?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock's eyes were full of greed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu naturally knew this was the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…What a crazy bastard.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu's gaze turned even colder as he looked at Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock did not realize this as he started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Have the other squads contacted you?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Not yet-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beeeeeep!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu heard a quiet noise in his pocket as he was about to respond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was loud enough for Mock and the other Dark Elves in front with them to hear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu looked toward Mock with a stiff expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have, sir."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beeeee-, beeeeeeep!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard two more noises as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Looks like the other three squads are all here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, sir."&lt;br/&gt;
"Take out the video communication device."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu immediately took the video communication device out of his pocket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"None of them are emergency signals, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu sternly shook his head at Mock's question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The first to arrive was Squad Leader 1 followed by Squad 3 and Squad 2."&lt;br/&gt;
"I see."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock sighed in relief internally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I'm relieved.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked calm on the outside, but he was actually extremely tense as this plan was very important for his future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was why he had been very concerned that something would happen to the other squads on their way to their spots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But thankfully, everybody had arrived at their spots safely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It's time for the next step.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock turned toward informant Bob and praised Naru.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your liege gave me very good information."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike how he had stealthily received the map from Naru in front of the Endable Kingdom's white castle, he had openly taken the map from Naru once they got to the Forest of Darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had also used the Vampire informants without any issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Everybody here is on my side.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had not clearly explained things to everyone other than Andrei, but he had shown everyone that Naru was working with him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He showed them that they shared information with one another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This way, they will think that I have influence with the Ejellan Duchy as well.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock hid his wicked thoughts to himself as he gave Bob an order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Connect the Vice Commander right away if he calls."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir. I under-"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wiiiiiiiiiiiiing-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a different noise than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's young master Naru-nim."&lt;br/&gt;
"Connect him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A black mage who had been standing with the Dark Elves walked forward and connected the video communication device in Alberu's hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu held the video communication device with both hands as he turned the screen toward Count Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commander-nim.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naru's face appeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shhhhhhhhhhhhhh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trees surrounding the Black Castle shook because of the wind at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock looked toward the north, east, and west.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They must all be hiding properly, as he could not see them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vice Commander."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes, sir.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock continued to speak to Naru with a serious expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get started."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I understand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naru's voice sounded determined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our Vampires will create a path first.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock had almost laughed after hearing that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He truly is still young.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had given Naru and Squad 3 the privilege of attacking first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The justification was simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was his chance at revenge and a chance to be approved as the leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything had to do with those two reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Naru's chance to be in the front to attack the enemy and get revenge for his father, which would allow him to be accepted as the future leader of the Ejellan Duchy if they could take down the Black Castle with him fighting in the front.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'But there are no benefits to being in the front for a plan like this.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was better to wait in the back and take the sweetest fruits of the battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock thought that it was really easy to handle this kid as he started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, his expression was serious, unlike his inner thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Go ahead. I will continue the attack as soon as you open a path."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes, sir.&lt;br/&gt;
"Duke Fredo will be happy to hear about your courage once he wakes up."&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thank you for your kind words. Then I will get started right away.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The call ended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's heart was beating fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was his chance to achieve great merits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He raised his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock started to speak once the hidden Dark Elves saw his hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Move the Elementals as soon as Squad 3 starts their attack. We will deliver our orders through the Elementals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooo-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They started to hear quiet cries around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elves were summoning the Elemental-eating Elementals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Alberu observed everything that was going on…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They started!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock shouted energetically as a large mana orb appeared on the west.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Count-nim, there is a shield surrounding the Black Castle. We suspect it is a shield spell that can handle a set amount of damage, so our Vampires will use as many magic scrolls as necessary to destroy it."&lt;br/&gt;
'Is that so?'&lt;br/&gt;
'Yes, sir. That will signal the start of the attack.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard a voice from the western forest at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Go!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Naru's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock stood up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get ready."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moment he said that…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large mana orb became even larger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'That thing is huge!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't know that such a large mana orb could even be cast with a magic scroll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock was shocked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he also realized that the Ejellan Duchy's wealth was immense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then sneered at Naru who wasted that immense wealth on a mana orb like this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Stupid fool who only does things to benefit others.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of Mock's lips went up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard informant Bob's voice at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shall we go?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He didn't even turn his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screeeech-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was because the Black Castle's gate was opening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No. The enemies seem to have noticed our attack. We will wait for now."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Really? We're going to wait?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Hmm?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock flinched at Bob's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Commander-nim!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Count-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock groaned as he felt his body being lifted up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh, ugh. You bastard, this, cough!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He couldn't breathe because someone was choking him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His eyes opened wide as he looked at the person choking him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Informant Bob was looking at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How dare you speak so informally to me? You're just an old man and not my young master-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock could see the Dark Elf half-blood smiling at him as his face was burning red from being unable to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Only our young master-nim can speak informally to me. I am a loyal servant who only serves our young master-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock could see the completely open Black Castle behind the Dark Elf half-blood's shoulders at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock's expression changed as he was pulling on informant Bob's hand to get it off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cough, ugh- Choi, Choi Han-!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Black Castle's gate had opened and Choi Han, Cale Henituse's knight, was walking out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-547"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-549"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-548</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 547: You should have watched your back (1)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-547</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Count Mock who had been heading toward the forest turned around before leaving with Squad 4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vice Commander!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, Commander-nim!"&lt;br/&gt;
"You lead Squad 3."&lt;br/&gt;
"Please leave it to me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 3 consisted of Cale, the Vampire warriors, and the Vampire Knights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Guide!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu walked up to Count Mock and handed him four maps at his calling.&lt;br/&gt;
Mock handed those maps to the squad leaders leading the squads heading to the north, east, and west.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everybody remembers the details of the plan?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock made eye contact with each person responsible for a squad before saying one thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vice Commander."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale raised his hand at Mock's calling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three nimble-looking Vampires stepped forward.&lt;br/&gt;
Mock looked over them before nodding his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They are informants and people who have each been to the Forest of Darkness at least once."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He motioned with his hand and the three Vampires moved so that one of them was with Squad Leaders 1, 2, and 3.&lt;br/&gt;
Alberu moved next to Count Mock and Squad 4 at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock finally turned back around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's go."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 4 that was made of Dark Elves headed toward the south side of the Black Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will be on our way, sir."&lt;br/&gt;
"See you soon, Commander."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The noble awaiters who were serving as Squad Leaders for Squads 1 and 2 showed the map to their respective Vampire informants and quickly started to move as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Time for us to go too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 3 that Cale was leading started to move toward the west side of the Black Castle as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale made eye contact with Alberu Crossman who turned around and looked at him before he left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'See you in a bit.'&lt;br/&gt;
'Yes, your highness.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two of them communicated with a short eye greeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'll look after Alberu Crossman too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale nodded his head after hearing Eruhaben's voice and started to move toward the west side of the Black Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shhhhhhh- shhhhhhh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 3 started to move while matching Naru's movements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everybody should have started moving by now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale changed directions as soon as he heard Solena's voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are heading north."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was going back the way he came even though his Squad 3 was responsible for the west side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiiiiiish- Swiiiiiiiish-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His ancient powers had been hidden thanks to Fredo's armband, but the Sound of the Wind now swirled at the tip of his feet.&lt;br/&gt;
Although this power did not suit young master Naru-nim, no Vampires questioned this right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shhhhhhhhhhhhhh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vampires silently followed behind Cale.&lt;br/&gt;
The slightly over 100 Vampires all headed north.&lt;br/&gt;
Cale served as their guide in the front.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shhhhh- shhhhhhh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They brushed past branches and bushes and immediately turned north once they returned to the place they had teleported to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak once they were following behind Squad 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Come out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shhh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the large trees started to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale turned his head after hearing a loud noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Welcome, young master-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiger shaman Gashan welcomed him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crunch. Crunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large Tiger warriors slowly raised their heads from the shadows of the trees along with the sound of crunching leaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Mm!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solena had heard about this, but her hands still became sweaty after looking into the eyes of the Tiger warriors who had been hiding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It's starting now.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She tensed up after realizing that the true plan was starting.&lt;br/&gt;
She was excited as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Dark Elves' Elementals have headed south with Squad 4."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Elementals that Count Mock's subordinates controlled…&lt;br/&gt;
Those Elementals were said to eat other Elementals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So this is our chance."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The golden top's whip was in Cale's hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Just tell me what to do. Chaos, destruction, happiness.'&lt;br/&gt;
'It's been a while! I've been so bored ever since you told me to wait in the Forest of Darkness!'&lt;br/&gt;
'Sigh. It was so hard hiding from the Dark Elves' Elementals.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caw. Caw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale lifted his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three Wind Elementals and the crows started to appear one or two at a time and started to cover the sky above the Forest of Darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The operation name is 'Hunt.' "&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He ordered the first step of the operation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We will capture Squad 1 first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 1's leader was swordsman Andrei who was said to be one of the strongest of the noble awaiters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Move."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vampires and Tigers started to move north.&lt;br/&gt;
Their movements were swift but stealthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 3 started to chase behind Squad 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 1's leader, swordsman Andrei.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Squad leader-nim, it is to the left."&lt;br/&gt;
"Okay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He followed the Vampire informant and turned left with a faint smile on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Soon!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was one of the top noble awaiters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was lacking in comparison to the original nobles, but he was skilled enough to be able to receive the best treatment if he had gone to any other organization.&lt;br/&gt;
This was because he was a sword master.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooooong-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His sword started to vibrate.&lt;br/&gt;
A faint aura smoke started to appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Congratulations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked back for a moment after hearing a voice right behind him.&lt;br/&gt;
Another noble awaiter was smiling as he sucked up to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What do you mean?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei looked stern as if to ask the person who spoke what they were talking about in the middle of the plan.&lt;br/&gt;
The person who spoke smiled even brighter after seeing his expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Aw come on, you know exactly what I mean, sir."&lt;br/&gt;
"Ahem."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei let out a fake cough and turned around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Please keep the useless chatter for later."&lt;br/&gt;
"I'm only saying it because we are on our own now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei peeked toward the Vampire informant after hearing that. It was his way of telling the other person that they were not 'on our own,' with this Vampire here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ah."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other noble awaiter finally closed his mouth.&lt;br/&gt;
However, he still smiled wickedly toward Andrei.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was not the only one.&lt;br/&gt;
Andrei's subordinates, as well as the 24 noble awaiters who made up his squad, all had bright expressions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Hehe. It's not like I don't understand why he feels that way.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei understood the other awaiter quite well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Black Castle destruction plan.&lt;br/&gt;
The plan was to destroy the castle while Cale Henituse and his core group of friends were not around and take the people inside as hostages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It won't be easy.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even without Cale Henituse and the core individuals, the chances that Cale Henituse left the castle empty because there were enough defenses set up were high.&lt;br/&gt;
That was why he thought that the difficulty of the plan would be considered high between high, medium, and low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'But it is not so dangerous that I might die.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was what was making the members of Squad 1 all have bright expressions.&lt;br/&gt;
This was especially true for Andrei, who was full of anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this plan was a success…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I should receive a noble title if we succeed.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was a squad leader after all.&lt;br/&gt;
He had to temporarily become Count Mock's subordinate because of it, but he wasn't planning on quietly staying there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei composed his expression and started to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everybody focus!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then gave an order to the informant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are increasing our speed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was planning on quickly getting to the discussed location and surrounding the Black Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's desires were almost overflowing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, sir. I will increase my speed!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The informant quickly moved with the map in his hand.&lt;br/&gt;
Andrei followed behind him as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The informant's body suddenly fell forward at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What is it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei looked toward the informant in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"M, my foot-!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The informant reached for his ankle with a shocked expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Huh?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's eyes opened wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He saw a gold rope that shot out of the ground and grabbed the Vampire informant's ankle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A rope?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Is this one of Cale Henituse's traps?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His back suddenly turned cold as he had that thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'No.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He felt as if something was clenching him from all directions.&lt;br/&gt;
That was why he realized it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This is not just a simple trap!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He turned away from the Vampire who was still on the ground clenching his ankle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He happened to see something land on his arm at that moment.&lt;br/&gt;
Andrei had been quickly charging forward until now. That was why he had not noticed it earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That thing had landed on the back of his hand silently and so gently that he didn't even feel it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Powder?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold powder was surrounding him and the rest of Squad 1.&lt;br/&gt;
The amount of powder started to exponentially increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This is dangerous! I can tell that this is very dangerous!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei shouted as soon as he felt that way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Dodge! Step back!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He tried to move back as he shouted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gold powder.&lt;br/&gt;
He couldn't tell what it was, but his intuition as someone who just barely made it past the hump to become a sword master was telling him that this was a dangerous situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it was already too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Ugh! My body!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Ahhh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The powder instantly gathered together and increased in size.&lt;br/&gt;
It then started to bind the bodies of Squad 1's members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"N, no!"&lt;br/&gt;
"I can't move my body!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shining golden rope was too strong to be a regular rope.&lt;br/&gt;
It was hard for them to even twist their bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ugh! How is this so strong?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's body had been bound before he could even take out his sword.&lt;br/&gt;
It was so quick that he couldn't even dodge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Is it a trap?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was not it.&lt;br/&gt;
He quickly got rid of the thought that these ropes were traps that Cale had left behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This is someone attacking us.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This power had accurately aimed for all of them.&lt;br/&gt;
That was only possible if someone was looking at them right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was also something else he realized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'This person is strong.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was able to become the squad leader because he was a sword master, but most of Squad 1's members were quite strong as well.&lt;br/&gt;
There were mages in the group too, but this enemy had tricked all of them and had instantly suppressed them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei started to sweat.&lt;br/&gt;
He held back his fear and raised his voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Who are you?! Who dares to ambush us like this?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked around and raised his voice.&lt;br/&gt;
His hand was doing everything it could to get free and reach for his scabbard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'If I can just get my sword out!' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could just slash away this stupid rope with his aura if he could pull his sword out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Where are you looking?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei heard a foreign voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should raise your head."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flinch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's shoulders flinched before he looked up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He could see an Elf sitting on top of a thick branch on a tree.&lt;br/&gt;
The beautiful Elf with white-gold hair started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You wish to return alive after stepping into a Dragon's lair?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'What? A Dragon's lair?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei was definitely looking at an Elf, but his whole body felt chilly after looking into the Elf's eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hmm. How disappointing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heard a voice behind him.&lt;br/&gt;
Andrei slowly raised his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a familiar voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Whose voice is this?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He soon remembered the owner of this voice.&lt;br/&gt;
He was confused because the way the person was speaking was completely different than normal, but he remembered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Young master Naru Von Ejellan!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were allies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His head that had been slowly turning quickly turned in joy about seeing an ally before he could even question why Naru was here.&lt;br/&gt;
Naru was smiling and approaching him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He opened his mouth to speak.&lt;br/&gt;
He didn't sound like the pure and brave boy who just wanted to get revenge for his father. It was a cold voice that reached Andrei's ear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is very disappointing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naru was disappointed.&lt;br/&gt;
The boy's gaze headed toward the white-gold haired Elf sitting on the tree branch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How can you attack first like that, sir?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…What?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei's questioned his ears for a moment.&lt;br/&gt;
However, that suspicion soon returned with a clear answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naru looked at him and started to smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was supposed to get him first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grrrrr-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad 1 quickly heard the roars of wild beasts surrounding them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crunch. Crunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the things that came out through the bushes were the Beast men of the Tiger tribe who were much scarier than wild beasts.&lt;br/&gt;
Berserk Tigers completely surrounded them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What the hell!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei looked back and Naru and started to shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Young master Naru! What the hell are you doing? Did you betray us?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Naru did not respond.&lt;br/&gt;
Someone else responded in his place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Betray? How can you say such upsetting things?"&lt;br/&gt;
"…Who are you?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the Vampire knights who had been standing behind Cale walked forward.&lt;br/&gt;
The Vampires bowed their heads and made a path for him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The knight removed the helmet on his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You should know my face, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Uhh, uhh!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrei could not continue speaking because he was shocked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"H, how are you here?!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Duke Fredo was smiling after seeing his reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-546"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-548"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-547</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 04:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash of the Count's Family - Chapter 546: Welcome, this is our house (4)</title><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-546</link><description>&lt;p&gt;There were hundreds of warriors standing outside the White Palace.&lt;br/&gt;
The White Star looked happy as he looked at the people Cale was describing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Not bad.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The morale, nervousness, and excitement coming from the warriors were heating up the air around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, I will trust all of you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody cheered or responded to the White Star's comment.&lt;br/&gt;
They just looked at him with firm gazes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star responded to those gazes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everybody, head out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clang!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of warriors knelt down on one knee and bowed toward the White Star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star smiled at this before turning around and heading into the White Palace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will not see you all leave."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warriors raised their heads. They could see the White Star's back as he walked into the White Palace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White Star's voice etched itself into the warriors' ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"However, I will prepare a celebration for when you all return."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would not see them leave, but he would prepare a celebration for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warriors' eyes started to burn fiercely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A celebration. That meant that the White Star was certain about their victory.&lt;br/&gt;
The rewards during that celebration would be things like noble titles, power, money, fame, etc. They will receive many things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Have a safe trip."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The palace door slowly started to close after the White Star's final comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screeeeeech- boom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He did not turn back to look at the warriors as the door closed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All rise."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warriors stood up after hearing Count Mock's voice.&lt;br/&gt;
Count Mock turned around to look at them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Kekeke.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was laughing internally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of warriors.&lt;br/&gt;
There were not too many of them.&lt;br/&gt;
However, they were headed toward an empty castle in the middle of a forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was plenty of people to destroy a single person's castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'They are of the highest quality.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 48 noble awaiters were all extremely skilled individuals.&lt;br/&gt;
And he was certain that the trusted subordinates that they brought for this battle were all strong individuals as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Our kids are decent too.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dark Elf warriors that Count Mock had brought with him were talented as well.&lt;br/&gt;
It could not be helped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'These punks need to earn some merits this time too.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock was planning on making his subordinates achieve a lot of merit during this Black Castle destruction plan so that they could at least get a Baron title.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock peeked next to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Only then can I move past the others.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Hubesha who would normally have appeared at the front in her black armor was in regular clothes biting down on her lips.&lt;br/&gt;
Furthermore, Chief Priest Gersey was emotionless as if he was thinking about something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I guess he's concerned because I am about to take another step forward.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of the Dark Elf old man's lips started to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Count-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His cute but useful cooperator spoke at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, young master Naru."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boy who suited the stylish silver uniform quite well was looking at Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He's still young. He's also inexperienced.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There would not be much for this bastard to do even though he was taking young master Naru to the battlefield with him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I will take it all.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was planning on making sure that the useful of the noble awaiters who said that they would follow him and his trusted subordinates would gain most of the merits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'I also need to make sure to use the Vampires that that kid brought over.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock's eyes sneered at the Vampire knights and warriors Naru brought with him before it quickly disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He really brought the core members so that he could get revenge for Duke Fredo. I'll put them to good use.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He would put them in dangerous situations where they couldn't gain much merit.&lt;br/&gt;
Count Mock decided on how he would use the Vampires before looking toward the boy who was here to get revenge for his father and to steady his position as the leader of the Vampires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boy started to speak as soon as he made eye contact with Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everybody is waiting for you, Count Mock-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock barely managed to stop the corners of his lips from rising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Everybody is waiting for me.&lt;br/&gt;
Everybody is waiting for my order.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How sweet does that sound?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And Count-nim, here you go."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock received the map that Naru walked up and stealthily handed him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He recalled a conversation they had prior to this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'…Duke Fredo has information from the Northern Alliance?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naru had shaken his head at that question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'To be more specific, during the Northern Alliance's war, a Vampire informant infiltrated the Paerun Kingdom and stole some information.'&lt;br/&gt;
'And that information came from that Guardian Knight Clopeh Sekka's office?'&lt;br/&gt;
'Yes. That is how we were able to confirm the authenticity of the information.'&lt;br/&gt;
'What is that information?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naru had quietly informed Count Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It is a map of the Henituse territory. It had the coordinates of the Forest of Darkness as well.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chhhhhhhh-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock opened the map in his hands without any hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'It really is real.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The map had the Paerun Kingdom's crest and Clopeh's personal crest.&lt;br/&gt;
The authenticity of the map had gone up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He opened his mouth to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Prepare the teleportation magic circle!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of warriors…&lt;br/&gt;
The mages and priests in grey robes behind them started to move following his order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock watched them before shouting in a confident voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have the coordinates, so the person in charge of the teleportation should come over to confirm!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He purposely announced it like that in front of everyone.&lt;br/&gt;
He was telling them that he had all of the information related to this Black Castle Destruction Plan in his hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then quietly whispered to Naru.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just leave everything to me, Naru."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boy blankly looked at him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will make sure to give you your piece."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boy then smiled as if he was satisfied.&lt;br/&gt;
Mock barely managed to hold himself back from sneering at Naru.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Hmph. This bastard is the same even if he pretends to be a good kid.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he really was a good little punk, or if he was full of courage, then he would be difficult to handle.&lt;br/&gt;
However, Mock found it easy to handle Naru as he believed Naru had the same type of greed as his own inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Of course, I still need to be wary of him.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was Duke Fredo's son after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Commander-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A black mage approached Count Mock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock became even more elated after hearing the title of commander. However, he faced the black mage with a stern expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do you need the coordinates?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, Commander-nim."&lt;br/&gt;
"Look at this map."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black mage confirmed the coordinates on the map Mock pointed at before peeking at him and cautiously starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Commander-nim, you are amazing. I am in awe of how you managed to prepare all these things in advance."&lt;br/&gt;
"Ahem."&lt;br/&gt;
"I am envious of your insight."&lt;br/&gt;
"…We have a big battle in front of us. Focus."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black mage could tell that Count Mock was pretending as if things were nothing but was actually elated at his kissing up and responded energetically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock had a good chance of moving ahead of Count Hubesha if this plan was a success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The black mage was energetic seeing that the person he needed to look good toward was happy at what he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then we will activate the teleportation magic circle right away!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes. Make sure to teleport us to the right spot!"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock sternly looked at the black mage who respectfully bowed to him and walked away before turning around and looking at the waiting warriors with a serious gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boy looked at Count Mock and had the following thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'He's acting like a total fool.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale was working hard to not smile while looking at the excited Count Mock.&lt;br/&gt;
That was why others thought that he just looked like a nervous boy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom- boom- boooom-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale watched the large-scale teleportation magic circle shining even brighter as the priests played the drums with a sharp gaze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'There really is something to it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drums the priests were playing were normal, but he was certain that there was an item from the Demon World among them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Young master Naru."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He turned toward the voice that suddenly called out to him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Count Hubesha-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale walked over to Count Hubesha who had called him. She confirmed that Mock was busy before quietly whispering to Naru.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"…Ha. I don't know if it is okay for me to say something like this, but… Since I have a close relationship with Duke Fredo-nim…"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She seemed to be contemplating something, however, she sounded firm as she finally stopped hesitating and said what she needed to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Be careful. You never know what might happen in a battle."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale's expression turned odd. However, Hubesha read it as nervousness and calmly continued to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You need to take care of your own life. You also need to take care of your subordinates' lives. That is the job of a leader. Got it?"&lt;br/&gt;
"I understand."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale responded confidently before he heard Solena's voice behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vice Commander-nim!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hubesha looked at Solena for a moment before talking to Cale again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Have a safe trip. I will stop by the Duchy every so often in order to check on your father's condition."&lt;br/&gt;
"Thank you very much, Count-nim. But I will just receive your heart behind the offer."&lt;br/&gt;
"…Why?"&lt;br/&gt;
"My father's condition has worsened, so it will be hard to see him. Nobody other than the healers can be around him right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale answered as sadly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is why I barely managed to say goodbye to him this morning. It would have been hard to do so if I was even a bit late because he would have been in the middle of being healed. Of course, I have no idea whether father heard my voice or not."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hubesha could feel the emotions of the boy who said goodbye to his comatose father before coming here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess I will only be a hindrance if I went to visit, so I will not go. Cheer up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale bowed and walked over to Solena.&lt;br/&gt;
Count Hubesha looked at the boy for a bit before looking toward where the boy was going.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large-scale teleportation magic circle was prepared to activate.&lt;br/&gt;
All of the warriors were already in place above the teleportation magic circle waiting to move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale stood in his spot as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to hurry."&lt;br/&gt;
"My apologies, sir."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale lowered his head at Count Mock's comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No. Don't be nervous."&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, Commander-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock peeked at Cale's complexion before whispering in a quiet voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You said that there will be a guide once we get there, right?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a guide to help them through the Forest of Darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Yes, sir. I sent someone in advance so that he could work as our guide. He was an informant in the past, so he's quite knowledgeable of that area."&lt;br/&gt;
"Sounds good."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock had a satisfied smile on his face and he raised his voice after receiving the signal from the black mage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Teleport!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boom boomboom- boooom-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the drumming reached its zenith…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paaaaat!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bright light flashed and hundreds of the Endable Kingdom's warriors teleported into the Forest of Darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Forest of Darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The forest did not have physical boundaries but was instead divided between the inner and the outer regions with the strongest monsters roaming within the inner region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bright light flashed in the boundary area dividing the two regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ooooooong-!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of warriors appeared throughout the forest once the light disappeared.&lt;br/&gt;
And at the center… Commander Count Mock took a deep breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This forest truly does feel different."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Forest of Darkness was known as one of the Forbidden Regions.&lt;br/&gt;
It was a scary forest where monsters from both the Eastern continent and the Western continent appeared, as well as mutants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock looked forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Welcome, Commander-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A masked person who seemed to be a Dark Elf half-blood bowed toward him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Young master Naru, is this person your guide?"&lt;br/&gt;
"Yes, sir. This is him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The masked Dark Elf half-blood bowed toward the boy this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your servant greets the young master-nim."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale looked at the person bowing to him before looking toward Count Mock and starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He is my precious subordinate as well as someone who is very well-informed of this area."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This guide obviously was knowledgeable of this region.&lt;br/&gt;
The guide introduced himself in a somewhat elegant manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My name is Bob and I am young master Naru-nim's servant and informant."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberu Crossman who became Bob… He was obviously knowledgeable of the Roan Kingdom's terrains.&lt;br/&gt;
He had a map of the Forest of Darkness that Cale had given him in his pocket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mock took a step forward and looked around before starting to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"North, south, east, and west. We will surround the Black Castle from all directions. We will then proceed to destroy Cale Henituse's resting place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warriors' eyes sparkled at his firm voice.&lt;br/&gt;
Cale just stared at Mock's back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Welcome. This is your first time in the Forest of Darkness, isn't it?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corners of his lips slightly rose before they instantly went back down.&lt;br/&gt;
Cale heard a welcomed voice in his mind at that moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's been a while. You unlucky bastard, it must be hard acting like a little kid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was gold powder faintly spreading around the Forest of Darkness so that the enemies would not notice.&lt;br/&gt;
The gold light that matched ancient Dragon Eruhaben's hair was starting to cover the forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Count Mock started to shout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everybody, move according to the plan! Squad 1 to the north! Squad 2 to the east! Squad 3 to the west and squad 4 will move toward the castle from the south with me! Move now! This is a fight against time!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cale quietly observed Count Mock who was walking into a Tiger's den, no, multiple Dragons' lairs with his own two feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-545"&gt;
Previous Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="chapter-nav" href="/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-547"&gt;
Next Chapter
&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wuxiaworld.com/novel/trash-of-the-counts-family/tcf-chapter-546</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel><link>https://www.wuxiaworld.com/</link><description /></rss>